all
Speaker 1: right guys welcome back what a what a week wow i did not expect the week we got but that's
the week
Speaker 1: we had welcome in welcome in welcome in it's
Speaker 2: been so long i forgot how to start a podcast i'm over here going now what do i hit next what's going on next how do i start the music how do i get the microphone
on couldn't
Speaker 3: get the sound in my ears so guys welcome back it's been a wild week i am underslept uh undernourished malnourished
Speaker 3: Uh, but I missed
Speaker 4: you guys. I genuinely missed you guys. It's a, um, you guys have become part of my family. I have to outline my family at some point tonight because I get a lot of emails and a lot of congratulations for things that are not so. Uh, so I will, I will outline
Speaker 5: the nature of the family at some point in there in a few moments, but, um, yeah. So, uh, Mrs. Coleman and I celebrated 25 years or we're about to celebrate
Speaker 2: 25 years. It's going to be at the end of next month.
And
we
Speaker 2: thought when would be a good time to take some time away from the podcast and take time away from the family because we wanted to get
Speaker 6: away. Now, here's a dirty little secret.
Young, newly
Speaker 6: married couples, don't listen to the advice. Don't listen
to the
Speaker 6: story I'm about to give you and think it's advice. It's not. Mrs.
Coleman
Speaker 7: and I have taken almost no vacations in our
entire 25
Speaker 7: years of marriage. We've never had an anniversary trip. Never first, never fifth, never 10th, never 20th.
And we
Speaker 7: weren't going to let it get away from us this
Speaker 8: year. Every year we plan one or we talk about planning one, and then neither of us have any ability to plan. We're not good planners. So
we
Speaker 9: just never do it. And this year
we said, no,
Speaker 9: we're going to do it. We're going to absolutely make it happen. Well, our anniversary is at the end of
Speaker 7: June.
what my
Speaker 7: daughter was expecting by the end of June. I thought, well, that's going to be a really messy time of the year. We won't be able to do it. There'll
be a
Speaker 7: chance we'll miss something. There'll be a
Speaker 2: chance we'll be rushing back in the middle of the trip. If
you know me, I
Speaker 2: don't like being away from home. I'm a true homebody. I don't like traveling. So we picked a place that's very close
Speaker 7: to home. We limited it to three days, and we
Speaker 10: left Monday. And Monday we went. We had a great time Monday night, Tuesday night, Wednesday night, and we came back Thursday.
day.
and I
Speaker 4: thought, okay, well, that's when I put the note up. I'll do a member's show Friday. That was my plan. That was my plan. And so Friday, I put out a note, or maybe Thursday, I put
out a
Speaker 4: note. Hey, I'll be
doing a
Speaker 4: member's show
Speaker 11: tomorrow. It'll be
Speaker 7: around 1-ish. I had a good show lined up for you. I'm still
going to
Speaker 7: do it probably this week. It
was a
Speaker 7: heck of a lot of fun of a show I was going to put together for the member's show, and then I'll just do my regular show Sunday night. We'll get back into the swing of things, and then about 7 a.m.,
On
Speaker 7: Friday morning, my beautiful daughter, who was just shy of 36 weeks,
Speaker 12: texted my lovely bride and said, I think my water broke.
And we thought,
Speaker 12: well, that's not possible. It's too early. But
no, it
Speaker 12: in fact was possible. It was true. It happened. So
we
Speaker 13: gathered our stuff, headed over to her place, you know, checked in on her and then thought, OK, we got to get
to the
Speaker 13: we got to get the hospital ASAP. So.
Speaker 13: Headed to the hospital. We were at Vandy for a few days. They do a great job there. If you're remotely in Middle Tennessee and you want to deliver at a place that's just fantastic, I cannot recommend them highly enough. This is not a paid product placement. They're going to charge us out the nose. But nevertheless,
if you
Speaker 13: can't tell from my
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): sweatshirt, a beautiful, just absolutely delightful little girl was born just after
Speaker 13: midnight, Saturday morning.
And
it
Speaker 13: was such a different experience being on the grandfather's side instead of the father's side. You know, the
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): father's side, there's all these emotions that come into play of, oh my gosh, you know, it's just a different experience. I can't even describe it. But as a
Speaker 15: grandparent, I honestly hadn't even thought about what it would be like. And I hadn't really talked to anybody what it would be like. I didn't ask anybody, what's it like having your first grandchild?
it's
Speaker 7: just different. And I actually went back up there today for a little bit to drop some stuff off, um, before they checked out of the hospital and, and
oh my
Speaker 7: goodness, it was even, it was like
Speaker 16: even more, um, I can't, I can't even
Speaker 5: describe it like swelled with a love. I, not that I love the grandchild more than my children, certainly not, but it's just a fundamentally different thing. And it told me a lot about human nature. I'm sitting there.
and you know i
Speaker 17: this is the way my brain works it's i'm not a normal person i
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): don't know if you guys have figured that out
yet or not i
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): can't just soak it in and say hey i'm sitting here with my first grandchild this is my beautiful granddaughter
um you know
Speaker 17: this is it's gonna be amazing i can't do
that
Speaker 18: i have to start thinking
Speaker 17: about human nature and
Speaker 7: evolution and and or human design however you want to look at it i had to think about what is it about
Speaker 7: about being a grandfather, what is it about being a grandmother, the different hormonal things that kick in when you're holding a child versus a grandchild, even hearing the little screams as a grandfather is different
Speaker 11: from a father. It was just such a wildly different experience.
And it was emotional. I
Speaker 19: got very, very emotional several times.
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): Very emotional several. We, um,
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): i don't want to go through the whole like experience uh the night of not not anybody's business but i got very very emotional uh the night of when um when it was all
all kind
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): of taking place
Speaker 21 (lower-pitched voice): like my my wife has given birth to eight children naturally no medical intervention no epidurals
Speaker 19: no medicine no i mean just like get in there and tough it out right just just man up Let's see this thing through to the
end.
But after
Speaker 17: you've done it a few times, you kind of know what to expect. Even though each one's a little different, you kind of know what to expect. And
I'm talking from
Speaker 15: the father, not from the mother. I mean, it's just, you know, if you've never had a
Speaker 7: natural child or never been to one, let me just kind of walk you through it in two sentences. There's a quiet period where things are like slowly developing.
Speaker 7: Uh, and then there's this
Speaker 13: all hell breaks loose period that can last, I don't know, five minutes to 15 minutes to 20 minutes, however long the,
the real, the real
Speaker 1: shebang lasts.
And, um,
Speaker 1: and as a father, you always think, oh my gosh, is she going to make it?
And
Speaker 22: they always do. I mean,
I'm sure there's
Speaker 22: tragedies where they don't, but, um, the, the, the, the normal course is that they do in fact make it. And it's, it's, um,
you
Speaker 22: know everything has its purpose but as a as a grandfather man when you're when you're sitting there and you're waiting and and you got this like
anticipation and
Speaker 22: i'm telling
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): you the way my brain works is i'm sitting there thinking what
kind of
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): world is this child inheriting
everybody else is like is
Speaker 24: everybody okay and i'm like no what is going on in the middle east right now
uh is the
Speaker 25: american government still working towards uh towards the best interest of its
Speaker 26: people are we still a government of by and for the people or are we
Are
Speaker 26: we moving into some sort of totalitarian dystopian nightmare? I
Speaker 2: mean, this is all going through my mind in the midst of all the chaos, but it
was just
Speaker 27: incredibly emotional, incredibly emotional. My wife
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): and
I were
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): actually there for the
entire ordeal, for
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): the entire event, and it's just – I cannot
–
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): Cannot recommend enough soaking in the love of a newborn at some point in your life, if at all possible. There's
a
Speaker 13: helpless trust. We see
Speaker 17: that Jesus says, come to me like a little
child, and we
Speaker 17: often picture like an eight-year-old. But if you
Speaker 13: have an eight-year-old, you know that's probably not the most apt.
apt
Speaker 13: fitting age
Speaker 9: for the analogy, it's probably more like a one day old, you know, total surrender, total, no questioning, total, no ability to do anything. Yeah. I'm not,
Speaker 13: I have no say in what's going on around me. You're either going to feed me or you're not, uh, you're either going to hold me or you're not, you're
Speaker 11: either going to change me or you're not. I was holding the little baby
this morning or
Speaker 11: last
Speaker 29: night. It was
Speaker 30: last night. I think
Speaker 30: No, it was this morning. I'm holding the baby this morning. No, no, it was last night. I'm holding the baby, and I felt the
Speaker 11: big one.
And I was
Speaker 11: like, oh, no, we got one of those. And I was like, hey, hey, hey, I'm a professional. I've done this before. You, my daughter, just sit back. Let me take care of this one.
and
Speaker 7: it was you forget you you forget from child to child you forget and i i think there's a blessing in that because if you could remember would you
do it
Speaker 7: all over again if you could remember the sleepless nights if you could remember the constant diaper changes if you could mention all that um would you would
you get back in
Speaker 31: the arena and do it again so i think there's a grace and a blessing to not remembering it to not remembering how small they are to not but
Speaker 13: there's a there's a helplessness. Like, I'm holding this child, and I'm thinking...
Speaker 13: this had to be what jesus meant when he said come to me like a little child not
not a
Speaker 13: questioning inquisitive toddler not like why why why why why um you know because a five-year-old can
sin not like an
Speaker 13: eight-year-old or a nine-year-old where they get a little snot nose you know how they are um talk back a little bit wine that's mine that's mine no no no no no no no not
Speaker 31: like a nine-year-old
Speaker 13: uh certainly not like a teenager i've had
plenty
Speaker 13: of that. I got my fourth one now as a teenager. And I don't think that's what Jesus had in
Speaker 11: mind. But while I'm holding my brand new granddaughter, all six pounds of her, right? She was a little tiny thing when she was born. Under six pounds,
Speaker 32: like five and a half pounds.
Speaker 32: And I'm sitting there holding it, and I'm like, this is it. Like, it clicked. I couldn't do it as a dad. I couldn't think of doing it as a dad. But
as a
Speaker 32: grandfather, you're sitting there and you're holding it, like, this is what the big guy had in mind. This is what he was talking
Speaker 2: about. A total helplessness. A total helplessness. So, guys, while I appreciate your patience while I
Speaker 33: was away,
Speaker 33: please know we made the best of it. We had our first anniversary trip in 25 years. We did
it a
Speaker 33: month before my daughter was due so that there would be no complications. It would be no way it would possibly be interrupted. And we got home about 15 hours before, before her water broke in and we
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): kicked into hyperdrive. So that is why there was no show this week. I was out. That's why there was no member show Friday. I was with my,
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, with my family, uh, up at the hospital, just witnessing the miracle of life. I had this conversation with my son, he's, uh, gosh, 14.
And we were
Speaker 13: driving around. I said, this is, this is, I don't see how, I don't see how atheists hold babies. Like, I don't see how,
I don't see how
Speaker 13: you can hold a baby and remain an atheist. I
don't see how you can
Speaker 34: watch the birthing process and remain an atheist. I know it happens. I mean, there's billions of them around
Speaker 35: the world, but I just don't see how it's possible.
Speaker 35: I don't see how it's possible.
I don't see how
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): you can feel your heart swell up with love and think that's just matter.
Speaker 36: That's just electrons swirling around protons and neutrons and they happen to be in the right order.
I don't see how it
Speaker 37: happens, guys.
And so if your
Speaker 37: brain works like mine,
Speaker 38: if your brain is crazy and you've had a child, you've probably experienced all this before.
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): You've had a grandchild, you've probably experienced all this before. But man, like today...
When I
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): was holding her today, my wife even kind of made fun of me today for the way I was talking to her because it's
just, it's
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): unreal.
Speaker 39: It's just unreal. I don't want to sit here and berate the thing for an hour and a half. That's not
Speaker 33: the content of the show, but I am, in fact, a Morphar. It is to my granddaughter. I'm a Morphar, a real Morphar, not like a fake Morphar
like some
Speaker 33: other people that call their Farphar or Morphar. No, no, no, no, no, not here. We are...
We
Speaker 33: are wordsmiths. If it's your mother's father, which I am, I'm a Morphar. I'm a Morphar. And my beautiful bride, she is a Mormar. She's a Mormar. So we sound like we're from Star Trek, Mormar and
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): Morphar.
But in
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): fact, we are just granddad and grandma. That's
Speaker 40: what we've chosen for our children's name,
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): granddad and grandma.
Speaker 31: So if you see Mrs.
Coleman and you
Speaker 31: call her grandma, no longer is that offensive.
If
Speaker 31: you see me and call me granddad, no longer is that offensive. Uncle, I'm actually an uncle, so typically not too offended by that anyway.
Even though I
Speaker 31: know you Gen Zers call old people
Speaker 13: uncle,
and that
Speaker 13: means old. I technically am an uncle many times over.
But now
Speaker 13: I'm a
Speaker 17: granddad and I'm okay with that. So you can call me granddad. You can call me grandpa. You can call me papa, people, whatever you want to call me. But the children ideally
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): will call me granddad one day. My dad
was a
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): granddad. My dad's dad was a granddad. My dad's dad's dad was a granddad. I'll
be a granddad. So
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): yeah, it was wild.
Speaker 41: It was wild. So I wanted so
badly to
Speaker 41: share with you guys. You guys have become
Speaker 5: like an extended part of my life.
Speaker 5: And the whole time I was thinking, how could I need to like talk to these people?
Speaker 42: I wanted to go live from the hospital. I would never, trust me, would never,
Speaker 15: but I really wanted to like, it crossed my mind.
Like I
Speaker 15: need to document this. I got to get on with the audience. I, you know, I just got to get out there and just talk about it. I, I want to show them around.
Speaker 15: want to walk around
Speaker 43: the hospital with the baby live. Like, Hey guys, I
didn't do
Speaker 38: it. I didn't do it. I respect the privacy of my daughter. I didn't even publish her face when I put the picture on X of me gazing into to her
Speaker 44: eyes.
And so
Speaker 44: anyway, if you, what is that? Oh, if, yeah,
I don't
Speaker 45: know. I was
going to
Speaker 45: say if you run into my daughter, but if you actually, if you run into her, don't tell her you know her.
That
Speaker 46: happened at Trader Joe's one day. So don't do that. Don't do that.
Speaker 6: But.
Yeah. So
Speaker 6: I'm going to get into the show. I'm going to try to do a normal show as possible. I will admit I've slept about six hours in the last two days, maybe seven total. Three
hours, four hours last
Speaker 6: night, maybe three hours the night before. So I'm kind of running on fumes, but I am back at it, geared up, ready to go.
Speaker 47: I want to talk specifically today. I want to talk about the crime scene being covered up because I
Speaker 10: started going through, actually
saw
Speaker 6: a really good tweet. And if I looked for it today, I couldn't find it. But while I was in the hospital, I was scrolling.
And
Speaker 6: I found a really good tweet and it said
Speaker 27: something like, here are
Speaker 10: the parts of the case that still bother me.
And it listed a bunch
Speaker 10: of really good parts. But when I got to the item that he listed about the, I think it was a he, I can't
remember if it
Speaker 16: was a he or she, but he listed something he said about
the crime
Speaker 16: scene being covered up. And I thought, you know, that's remarkable.
Speaker 48: And it reminded me that I saw recently a podcast in just the last few days.
Speaker 48: about the crime scene
Speaker 38: being covered up. It was a smaller podcast. It did not have many views. I'm going to play a few clips of it tonight. I've got some timestamps. One, two, I got maybe four, five, six clips I want to play out of this. But it's the
guy who did
Speaker 10: the renovation. It's the guy who put the pavers
down. And he's
Speaker 10: taken a lot of heat. And I'll admit,
Speaker 49: even I initially was very skeptical of this story because,
Speaker 49: that this guy just gets a call out
Speaker 17: of the blue and he's just this random contractor. And it's like, Hey, come put down some pavers. I'm thinking, eh, who does this on a Sunday? And then I hear from people in Utah. I got several friends that I've met through this program that live in Utah or from Utah. And they said, Hey, nobody works on Sunday. Sunday is completely shut down state. It's a very religious state. And when Sunday comes, they don't do stuff like they, the place is shut down. Nobody's moving around. And I,
You
Speaker 17: know, how
Speaker 49: much weirder is that, that the state is contracting workers to be working on Sunday? And
so
Speaker 27: I want to go through a few clips of that podcast because I think it's worth noting. I will give you a slight warning. There are a few clips that I'll play that I did not edit
Speaker 7: because I think the foul language sort of adds to the story. It's not flagrant. It's not hundreds
of foul
Speaker 7: words. It's a couple.
And but I
Speaker 27: left them in there. I'm
going to
Speaker 27: play it directly from YouTube. I thought about downloading it and bleeping them out, but I chose not to do that because
And
I want
Speaker 50: you to hear it directly from him with the emphases that he has as he tells the story. And I
cannot get over several parts
Speaker 51: of the Charlie Kirk story. There's several parts I
Speaker 11: cannot get over. I cannot force myself to get over them. And actually, during this week, I thought a lot about the case. I've tried not to. I tried
to get
Speaker 11: work out of my head, but I couldn't help it.
Speaker 11: Um, in fact,
Speaker 7: the place my wife and I went was a, like a quiet retreat center where you go and you're not supposed to make a bunch of, you're just quiet, right?
Speaker 51: There's like a relaxation places. There's quiet zones. There's all these places to sit and just sit around and just be quiet. We sat out by a little fireplace and listened to birds one morning. Like it's just, it's supposed
to be a quiet place,
Speaker 51: but this, this case, this, this who killed Charlie Kirk, how and why has inundated my life for
Speaker 52: the last eight months now, eight plus months, eight and a half months.
and
Speaker 52: we're coming up on one year. Going to be here before we know it.
And as I was
Speaker 52: thinking
Speaker 53: about it, I kept coming back to the crime scene being paved. Like, I can't get over that.
And when I saw the podcast, I
Speaker 53: thought, that's
Speaker 54: it. I got to talk about this. So let me go over to show a couple pictures
Speaker 55: first, just to sort of get an idea. This is from Muppet Masher. I don't know if you guys follow him on X or not.
But
Speaker 55: I want to show you first a couple of pics he has that have not been seen or at
Speaker 51: least were not known by most people. He published, I think he got permission from somebody to publish them. He actually bleeped out a few faces here. So this is actually a picture of
the
Speaker 56: crime scene while the crew was working on it.
This is a picture
Speaker 56: of it. So.
Speaker 56: obviously we know the tent was here in the middle or actually just a little offset from this area right here, but the, the, the tent was over on the side a little bit, but this is it. This is the scene of the crime.
And
Speaker 41: there's a picture in here that is
Speaker 54: remarkable. Look at this picture. You can see how much dirt they excavated. That has to be like a foot of dirt that they've excavated out of here.
Speaker 57: Now, when he, when we do the podcast in a minute, you'll see
the guy who
Speaker 57: actually did the work, I think gives a smaller number than that. I think he says it's eight or 10 inches.
But
Speaker 57: that looks
Speaker 54: like more than 8 or 10 inches to me. That is a tremendous amount of digging down. Look at that right there. See that?
Speaker 8: There's like a red line here running across, like a chalk line or something. It looks like an archaeological dig. There's several inches above this red line and
Speaker 41: several inches below.
There's a
Speaker 41: tremendous amount of dirt that was removed. And no one's ever given an explanation.
for
Speaker 41: why this place and I went back and looked at historical aerial photography of this place and it has for many many years been
Speaker 55: all dirt
this entire area
Speaker 55: has been all grass excuse me this entire menorah area right here has all been grass for many many years and there's
Speaker 56: never
been a
Speaker 56: good explanation for why they chose this emergency to go through and
Speaker 41: add the pavers
and so as I was
Speaker 48: looking at it
And
Speaker 48: thinking about it, I ran across another tweet. It's an excellent tweet, and I want to share some of the details of it.
This is Sam
Speaker 47: Parker talking about the rapid destruction and cleanup of crime scenes being a telltale sign
of a
Speaker 47: cover-up. And then he talks about JFK. These are facts I didn't know. You know, after the JFK assassination, where the president of the United States was slain,
In
Speaker 47: Dealey Plaza in Dallas, the road was kept open to traffic after the shooting.
And that the very
Speaker 47: next day, the crowds were allowed back onto the grass and the road. They didn't keep it shut down even for 24 hours.
That the
Speaker 58: Secret Service wiped down and cleaned the limo 30 minutes after the assassination while it was at the hospital.
And then the
Speaker 47: limo was shipped off to D.C. within three hours without a forensic examination. What's this sound like?
This sounds
Speaker 47: like the J.F. This sounds like the
Speaker 59: Charlie Kirk SUV. It was
cleaned up
Speaker 59: nearly immediately, and then it was shipped
Speaker 3: off. It was sold, and we have no idea where it is. And all that survives is six total pictures
Speaker 54: that
were given
Speaker 54: to Candace Owens.
that's
Speaker 19: all that survives of it, that we're aware of. Now, the police may have taken photos, but we've certainly not seen any of those or we've not seen those listed anywhere. And
then the limo
Speaker 19: was completely repaired
Speaker 58: within three weeks. So that's the JFK thing. Now, what about RFK? My
wife and
Speaker 60: I, actually, let me pull this down a second. We
watched
Speaker 2: an excellent RFK documentary on Netflix while we were on our honeymoon, not honeymoon, whatever that was, vacation, anniversary party,
Speaker 11: excuse me, anniversary trip.
We
Speaker 11: watched an excellent four-part Netflix documentary on RFK. It was phenomenal.
This is what
Speaker 11: we do for fun.
This is
Speaker 11: what, when you've
Speaker 19: been married 25 years, this is how you spend your anniversary trip. You watch RFK documentaries. But we pulled
Speaker 54: it up. It looked interesting. We watched the first episode. We thought, man, this is compelling. And then we watched the next three after that. It was great. Well, it took us two or three days to get through it,
but it
Speaker 54: was fantastic.
It really
Speaker 61: drilled down. It actually maybe was a little too focused on his civil rights work, but it was
Speaker 51: excellent.
It
Speaker 51: left out a lot of the RFK story, but I think it was meant to tell that part of the story.
But I bring
Speaker 51: that up to say that
Sam Parker here
Speaker 3: talks about throngs of people were allowed to continue moving through the pantry
Of
Speaker 3: the
Speaker 9: Ambassador Hotel after RFK was shot in a flurry of bullets. Now, do you know who ended up owning? I learned this in the documentary. Do you know who ended up owning the Ambassador Hotel where RFK was shot?
It's now like a high
Speaker 7: school. They've turned the facility into, I think, like a shared space with four or five high schools.
It was owned by
Speaker 2: Donald Trump, of all people.
It was owned
Speaker 2: by Donald Trump up until the city forced him, I think, according to the documentary that forced him to sell it to the high
Speaker 19: school system, and they used it
and they
Speaker 19: remodeled it and used it as a high school. The wall paneling, the ceiling tiles,
Speaker 9: and the door jams were removed and collected into evidence for the bullet holes that they contained.
But
Speaker 10: then they were lost, subsequently permanently lost. And the documentary actually covered that as well, that they pulled the door jam. They had a photo where you could see the bullet hole in the door jam, and then they lost it when
Speaker 16: they went back to examine
it. And keep in mind, that
Speaker 16: scene, like Charlie Kirk, was very much disputed in the fact that it seemed like
Speaker 62: there were more bullets fired than Sirhan Sirhan's gun held. I actually did an opening statement
on this
Speaker 62: not terribly long ago.
Speaker 62: I think there were 13 or 14 documented gunshots and only eight
Speaker 10: shots in Sirhan Sirhan's bullet. So there were at least four or five other shots. And then the medical examiner said the fatal shot came behind his right ear within an inch or two. And all the eyewitnesses said Sirhan Sirhan
Speaker 11: was in front of him like three feet away. So obviously those weren't the gunshots that killed RFK, the ones that came from Sirhan Sirhan.
And
Speaker 11: so the crime scene would have been very
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): telling about who was where. That doesn't matter. They destroyed it. They took it down, much like they did the Charlie Kirk crime scene. What about MLK?
The Martin
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): Luther King crime scene. There was a large tree limb in front of a boarding house
where James
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): Earl Ray
Speaker 57: allegedly shot Martin Luther
Speaker 58: King, but it was identified as obstructing the line of sight from the bathroom window to the Lorraine Motel.
and then
Speaker 58: it was cut
Speaker 33: down the same day he reported it.
So someone
Speaker 33: calls in and says, hey, I'm not sure he could have taken this shot. There's a giant tree limb in the way, and he didn't have a clean line of sight. That's okay. They go through and cut the
limb down,
Speaker 33: damaging the crime scene. There were bushes and shrubbery behind the famed Jim's Grill, not in its current location. And eyewitnesses placed a possible shooter there. They
Speaker 58: heard shots coming from there.
Speaker 58: Well, that's okay, because they completely tore that up and raised it to the ground the next morning.
Again, destroying
Speaker 51: the crime scene within hours or days
of a
Speaker 51: contested
Speaker 63: assassination. What about the attempt on Trump at Butler? The scene where Matthew Crooks was shot was
Speaker 57: hosed down by the FBI, and then the crime scene was released within three days. Now you go to Charlie Kirk, and then it really gets weird. I
don't know.
You
Speaker 57: remember them standing on the chairs, the blood-stained, blood-soaked chairs to retrieve camera footage, the SD cards
that
Speaker 61: were removed, and then you had spectators and other people allowed to walk all over the crime scene.
In fact, one
Speaker 51: of our very own viewers sent me footage. She recorded.
This is
Speaker 51: Shelba-Leba-Dabba-Ding-Dong, whatever her name is, Helga-Leba-Dabba-Ding-Dong. I can never get it right.
She
Speaker 51: actually took video footage, and you can see in her footage other people walking, traipsing through the crime scene. I don't know if I've ever played that
or
Speaker 57: not. I have it. And
then you have the
Speaker 57: grass and dirt ripped up. We'll start about that. We'll talk about that tonight. And
then the
Speaker 57: scene was paved over on the fourth day. We'll talk about that tonight. The tiles were replaced
in the
Speaker 57: tunnel under the Hall of Flags. The
tent, the
Speaker 57: chairs, the tables not preserved. No one knows where those things are.
the
Speaker 57: necklace
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): he was wearing was not kept, collected into evidence, and the SUV he was taken to the hospital in was cleaned, repaired, and
Speaker 16: sold.
And so this is
Speaker 16: not unusual. It's not unusual in a very high-profile political assassination to destroy the crime scene. In
Speaker 11: fact, it
almost makes
Speaker 11: perfect sense to destroy the crime scene, if you think about it.
Speaker 14 (lower-pitched voice): Well,
Speaker 13: Yeah.
If it's not
Speaker 13: what we think it is, if it's not a lone gunman from the Losey Center who planned and executed Charlie Kirk on his own from 142 yards
Speaker 2: away with granddaddy's 30-06, if that's
not what
Speaker 65: it was, it makes perfect sense to destroy the crime scene. We'll talk more
about that tonight as
Speaker 56: we roll through some of the other picks. Here's some more picks that took place during the construction.
This
Speaker 55: is from Getty Images. I will pull these up and give you an idea of just how destroyed this crime scene truly was.
This is
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): a picture here. You can see the alleged trap door. I just want to be on the record. I don't believe anything happened under the trap door.
But I
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): bring it up because everybody talks about it.
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): It's still there. I think it's just a utility entrance. You can see all these other utility
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): entrances here, here, here, and here, as well as some gas vent or something right there.
You get a view from the
Speaker 55: side here of just how deep they were pulling
Speaker 38: in. Here's kind of a farther back view where you can see where they have some fencing that they've borrowed from, I think, the state fair is where they got that.
while they
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): did the work. So it's not like they were doing it in the still of the night, but, I mean, there were people there watching
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): them do it.
But I want to go
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): through a
little bit of this
Speaker 68: podcast. Let me show you who did this
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): podcast first. A guy named Jimmy Rex.
The
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Jimmy Rex podcast. If you look it up, you'll find him there. I'll turn the CCs on because I'm not sure exactly how hard this is going to be to hear.
This guy here that you
Speaker 68: see, this is not Jimmy Rex. This is the guy who did the construction project. He's the one that owns Hardscape Utah.
Speaker 69: His name is Dan Merrill. He has...
taken a
Speaker 69: lot of abuse from people who thought he was in on it, who was
part of
Speaker 69: the
Speaker 27: cover-up, his business was targeted, he himself received a lot of hate mail. As someone who receives a lot of disturbing text messages and emails, I will say this, I think it's wholly inappropriate to contact any of the people involved in this, whether they are
Speaker 27: contractors, security
Speaker 65: personnel, employees at TPSA. I think if you're contacting these people and you're not doing it for news gathering
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): purposes, in other words, you don't have a podcast, you don't have a newspaper, you don't have a TV show, you're not trying to get an interview, you're not trying to send them questions and say, hey, here's what I plan to report. Would you like to weigh in before I go? I plan to report this on Friday afternoon.
If
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): you don't go, if you're not doing that, but you're contacting people just to harass, stop, right? Don't do that.
Speaker 70: I've gotten
some really disturbing comments
Speaker 70: from people,
very, very
Speaker 27: disturbing comments from people.
Speaker 27: Uh, in fact, about 20 minutes of every day is me spent blocking senders to my personal emails. Don't send stuff to my personal emails. Don't send
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): stuff to these people's personal email. Um, you know, this guy, this guy was a contractor. If you think he has some information to share, do what this Jimmy Rex did. Contact him and say, Hey, I've got a podcast. You
want to
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): come on and answer some questions? Here are the types of things I'd like to ask you about.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Uh, but, but leaving
Speaker 38: Google reviews when you haven't used their services, I
Speaker 72: think is, is kind of low budget.
Speaker 38: Um, you
Speaker 72: know, contacting the general contractor licensing board and filing complaints when you've never had anything to do with this guy. I mean, it's just, it's
Speaker 53: just low budget. It's not who we are, right? It's not, it's not what our side should be doing. So keep that in mind as we cover this story. Don't contact
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): these people unless you're doing it for legitimate news purposes. Like if you
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Again, if you have a podcast, if you have a newspaper, if you have a magazine, if you have a television show and you want to contact somebody, fine. But
if you're
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): just trying to harass
Speaker 54: somebody, don't do that. Don't do that. Not necessary. But I want to play this
because he
Speaker 8: opens up by talking about
how he learned
Speaker 8: about what happened. And I found this incredibly intriguing. I wasn't going to play this part, but I kept listening to it over and over, and I was incredibly intrigued by this.
And he
Speaker 8: was on the scene pretty much when it happened. I
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): mean, I'll let him take it away, and then I'll give you my color commentary behind it. But it was really fascinating. It was an interesting part of the story that I thought added a personal element
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): that I wasn't expecting.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): Interestingly enough, I came and met with you about your Zen garden. That was right when it happened. I was on my way back to my shop in Provo, and I saw six different precincts flying past me in the commuter lane.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): uh and i got to you know my shop is right it's probably two miles away from uvu i grew up right there you know we walked it's where i went to grade school you know it's vineyard it's which is now uvu and i saw all the cops coming past and i got off on university uh parkway and everything was shut down and i thought what the hell right got on the phone ask google and Charlie Kirk, you know, had been shot, you know, I mean, it's, I think,
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): I
Speaker 61: think that's a really interesting personal touch. We lose sight of the fact sometimes when we're covering this, that these are real people.
And I thought this
Speaker 61: added a really personal, interesting personal touch to it because
this
Speaker 75: is a guy who was going to, now what we'll find out later in the interview, I may not play this part,
but
Speaker 21 (lower-pitched voice): what I found out later in the interview, and if you listen to the whole thing and it's, it's an interesting interview, you wouldn't waste your time listening
to it. Um,
And what I
Speaker 76: found out was they know each other. They're friends. They've known each other a long time. They grew up together. They grew up in the area. They both grew up within a couple of miles of the campus. You
know, this is
Speaker 76: their
Speaker 27: community. This is their home.
There was an
Speaker 27: international news story that we've dedicated a lot of time to covering.
Speaker 27: Um, I've
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): looked at maps of Orem, Utah, every which way you can, uh, panoramic views from all four cardinal directions. I've looked at vertical views straight up and down Google maps, uh, specialized mapping
Speaker 2: services like near map that I subscribe to, um, you know, all kinds of, of different things. I've, I've, I've, I feel like I've been there. I've
never been
Speaker 2: there. I want to go,
Speaker 10: but I've never been there.
I've
Speaker 10: never been on the ground in Orem, Utah, but I've looked at the 3D
Speaker 51: dimensional model that Gary Melton, probably the only valuable thing he's done since this case started on September 10th. This
Speaker 10: little 3D map he put together, this 3D model, you have to download it. It's kind of complex, but once you get it together and once you get used, it's actually pretty nice.
But
Speaker 16: it's a really...
it's
Speaker 16: really easy in cases like this to forget these are actual human beings. It's one of the things I liked about the RFK document. It followed these people and you forget, even though this was, what was that? Almost 60 years ago, 58 years ago, RFK
Speaker 77: was taken down. You
forget these are
Speaker 77: actual human beings. A lot of these people are still alive. A lot of these people are still, you know, they've gone on. They've had other careers. They've had a whole life since then.
Speaker 78: They've had kids and grandkids and kids.
and
Speaker 78: the story is frozen in time. Like the Charlie Kirk story to me is frozen in September 10th. You
forget
Speaker 72: that all these people that live around there, they go to work the next day.
They drive
Speaker 72: around town. This guy got caught in the traffic of
what was
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): happening on that day, and I wanted to include that because it adds a personal element
Speaker 51: to it.
Now, I'm
Speaker 51: going to get into him describing how he was first contacted and how the contact came in on a Sunday. I thought this was
Speaker 53: an interesting
Speaker 53: element to the story
Speaker 80: fast forward
uh
Speaker 53: i'm at home with
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): my family um and i get a call and i don't answer my phones on sunday they left the message and the gentleman said hey you know this is kind of weird and he was kind of hemming and hawing on on the phone this was five days later then you
said
Speaker 81: it was on sunday
Speaker 83: okay so
they've got
Speaker 82: their timeline wrong by the way they keep assuming the The Charlie Kirk event was on Tuesday. It was not. It was on Wednesday.
And
Speaker 27: so Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday, it's actually only four days later. They keep saying it's five days later. So just accept that, that they're
Speaker 17: wrong about that. And that's okay. These are just, again, these are humans. They're trying to get it right. I don't think they're trying to get it wrong. But the call came in on Sunday. It actually was only four days later. I think that's interesting.
Speaker 39: I mean, it's
a valuable
Speaker 39: data point because it shrinks the timeline by 25%, 20%.
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, on Sunday. And
he says,
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): we've got to pay for emergency.
Yeah.
I
Speaker 85: don't think those words have ever been spoken before in the human language, ladies and gentlemen.
Speaker 10: We have a paver emergency. I think that I honestly believe,
as I
Speaker 10: sit here today, what day is it? May 24th, 2026, in the year of our Lord, Anno Domini. I truly believe that's the first time in
the
Speaker 61: history of the English language those words have ever been put in that order. We have a paver emergency.
There's
Speaker 86: never been a paver emergency in the history of mankind. This
is a
Speaker 86: first. This
Speaker 86: first. I'm
like, the hell is
Speaker 87: it? When the hell is a paver emergency? Exactly,
Speaker 88: right? I'm thinking, this guy's, what the hell? You know, so anyways, I wasn't going to even respond because I don't typically do that. But I'm like, paver emergency, you
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): know, part of my MO is
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): I like
to be useful, you
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): know, where I can be helped, you know.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): So I texted the guy. I said, look, I don't work on Sundays. And again, that's what I
Speaker 51: keep hearing about Utah.
On
Speaker 10: Sunday, they shut down. Like I tend to shut down on Saturday. I don't do much work on Saturday.
I just kind
Speaker 7: of dial it back. Now, it's not Shabbat Shalom. I didn't write a book about it like Charlie Kirk did. I don't throw my phone in the drawer. You can still reach me on Saturday. I'll
Speaker 10: still tweet. I'll still be heard from. I'll
still be heard
Speaker 10: from.
But I
Speaker 10: don't do a show on Saturday. I've never
Speaker 51: made it a habit in my career before this of working very much on Saturday. It's happened, but it's not common. Saturday's sort of the dial-it-back day, sort of the family day. You may go to the ballpark with the
Speaker 10: kids, make whatever. But, you know, everybody needs a day off. And this guy's day is Sunday. And
Speaker 90: apparently the whole state of Utah is Sunday. So it didn't surprise me when he said that. Guys don't work on
Speaker 91: Sundays.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): Uh...
you
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): know i'm happy to call you on monday what's a paver emergency so he
sends me
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): pictures of of right where charlie was murdered
and he
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): says he says we need to
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): put pavers in this place so
i called
Speaker 92: him
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): and um the guy seemed like a genuine good dude he says you know look we we don't have a whole lot of answers uh
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): We're told by people above us that we've got to put pavers in today and tomorrow. It needs to be in by Monday. And we've never done pavers. We've never installed them. And we want to make sure we do it right.
He says,
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): would you come help? I said,
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): 100%.
So I went and
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): got my shit. I got my trailer. I started calling my guys. And none of my guys answered. And so I started...
Speaker 15: because it's Sunday and they don't work on Sunday. Again, I'm pointing out how unusual it is for Sunday.
Speaker 10: If your boss calls and you don't answer, that means you don't work on that day. That
just means you
Speaker 10: don't work on that day. Now, so we
have a
Speaker 10: paver emergency, but what this told
Speaker 93: me about the story was they actually started the project in such a hurry
that they didn't
Speaker 94: even know who was going to do the paving.
That tells me
Speaker 94: it wasn't about the pavers.
because
Speaker 5: they got the ground excavated.
Speaker 93: They pulled 10 inches of dirt, according to him. They pulled 10 inches of dirt out of this place. They
get all
Speaker 93: the sod rolled up. They get it all out of the way. And they
don't even
Speaker 93: know who's going to do the paving. They
don't know who's
Speaker 93: going to put the pavers down. So
what was the
Speaker 9: purpose of the project? Was it pavers or was it dirt removal?
Speaker 9: because if you listen to the official story, it's, well, we just wanted to create a memorial place. We
Speaker 95: wanted to get rid of the, you know, we didn't want people coming up. There's biohazard material. Who knows when it's
Speaker 16: going to rain? Leave it to the Lord to clean it all off.
Ladies and
Speaker 16: gentlemen, it wasn't about the pavers. It
was about the
Speaker 16: dirt removal.
I would
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): suggest it's about removing evidence from the scene of the crime. It's about destroying the crime scene. That's what it was about. It wasn't
a
Speaker 2: beautification project.
but you
Speaker 2: can't go to the public and have school open back up on Monday and just have 10
Speaker 59: inches of dirt excavated from where the tent was. People
are going to
Speaker 59: look at that and say,
Speaker 96: what are
you guys
Speaker 96: hiding? What's really going on
Speaker 97: here? Are you telling me you guys excavated
Speaker 2: the crime scene and you're just going to leave a dirt hole for who knows how long? No, no, no, no. You can't go to people and say that.
that's
Speaker 2: the definition of a paver emergency.
Speaker 61: That's why it's a paver emergency. We
want to
Speaker 61: make it look like we did this intentionally to beautify the area. The reality is we would rather get caught removing evidence from the crime scene. We would rather get caught excavating the dirt, pulling the sod, getting everything cleaned up and out of the way. That we...
Speaker 61: If push comes to shove, we'll take it up with them later. We'll explain that
Speaker 7: if we have to. We would like to have pavers down. We would like this to, you know, we now have a paver emergency on our hands. We didn't know we were going to have a paver emergency, but now we have a paver emergency.
But the fact that the paver
Speaker 16: emergency existed in the first
Speaker 61: place is excellent evidence to me. If I'm the defense team, guys, if you're
Speaker 5: listening, if I'm the defense team,
I'm
Speaker 5: arguing this podcast. I'm using this testimony. I'm bringing him into court to
Speaker 7: testify exactly
to what
Speaker 7: he just said. And
if he
Speaker 7: tries to change his story, I'm using this podcast as impeachment evidence.
Because it wasn't about the
Speaker 98: pavers. The pavers were an emergency. The emergency was created because
now
Speaker 5: we have a hole in the ground. The hole in the ground is the problem.
You
Speaker 5: took a crime scene and made it a hole in the ground before you even knew
Speaker 99: how you were going to pave over it.
We like to
Speaker 99: say, well, they paved over the crime scene. No, no, that wasn't the scandal. The scandal is they dug up and removed the crime scene. That's the scandal.
This guy helped
Speaker 99: me articulate the
Speaker 100: problem.
Let me get back to
Speaker 100: him here. He wasn't done with the story.
Speaker 101: Started calling...
my
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): other guys you know my my brothers and then i called another you know so i put together this ragtag team you know of guys that we showed up on that sunday you know within an hour and a half of when they called us with our trailer and
uh we met
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): with a couple of dudes um i was telling you there you know there wasn't a whole lot of information there was there was two guys that were kind of in charge so by this point it's all dug up and everything it's everything
what did it
It
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): was, I've got pictures, you know, I could give you pictures of exactly when I showed up, I took pictures of what it looked like.
They had
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): taken out about 10 inches of the
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): dirt around the whole place, right? You know, you can, right now you can see where the pavers are. 10 inches of dirt around the whole place.
It wasn't about the
Speaker 57: pavers. It absolutely 100% was not about the pavers.
and that's why
Speaker 57: they had to pay for an emergency.
Now, you might
Speaker 104: ask yourself who, ladies and gentlemen, would have the authority when
a national
Speaker 10: political figure is assassinated on one of the most high-profile political assassinations
Speaker 61: in more than 50 years? Who would have the authority to order such an operation to excavate 10 inches of dirt in every direction
around
Speaker 59: the crime scene?
you might be
Speaker 59: asking yourself that because I asked myself that same question. I'd heard rumors of who it might be,
but
Speaker 10: I had no actual answer. Well,
my man
Speaker 10: here is about to give
Speaker 16: us the answer. Dan Merrill is going to tell us exactly who
ordered the
Speaker 16: destruction of the crime scene. And
it's a little
Speaker 16: shocking,
Speaker 10: frankly. Before I play it, let me just go through the options. One option would be like the UVU president.
the UVU
Speaker 16: president might have a good reason to excavate it and say, hey, guys, I don't need this on my campus. Classes
are
Speaker 10: going to come back in on Monday. People are going to be walking all through this area. They're going to be retrieving their belongings. They're going to come. I mean, it's just
Speaker 72: natural when something like that happens. You want to come look. I don't need the grass there. I don't need people walking all over it. We can put the fencing around it, but someone might climb over
Speaker 27: it. And, you know, so the University of President, that's a good option.
Speaker 27: maybe the division of facilities and construction management for the state of Utah. I mean, it's, it's a, this actually, I
really
Speaker 105: liked this about Utah. They have a state department that handles all the college campuses and all really all the state property.
I like
Speaker 27: that. I
like that
Speaker 27: because you have somebody with ultimate responsibility to beautify and maintain all
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): the state owned buildings in, in the system, in the state system. I like that. I like that.
So you might think that person
Speaker 17: would have the authority. Well, that's,
That's
Speaker 17: an option. So university president, division of facilities, construction management,
Speaker 106: maybe,
Speaker 107: maybe someone with the state outside of the
Speaker 108: construction system, someone potentially like the governor, maybe. Let's
hear what he
Speaker 108: has to say, because this was an interesting, this
was an interesting touch
Speaker 108: straight from the mouth of a guy who worked on the project.
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): hope that was all it was i'm gonna go help these guys he's asking for help they
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): want to do it right he he framed it in the sense that hey we want it we want this to be done right so that's why i showed up so i mean to do pavers correctly you over excavate you get rid of the top so you do you do 100 you want to get a good base and these guys had kind of you know there was two two guys in charge and a ragtag crew um
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): One of the guys was in charge of a state-owned facility in American Fork. And the other guy was a maintenance groundskeeper on a facility in Provo. And these are the two guys I'm corresponding with. The first guy, you know, the second guy that I hadn't talked to on the phone basically said, hey, look,
we're not talking
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): to anybody. We're not saying anything to the media. He says this is above our pay grade.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): the FBI and the state, the governor and the FBI. That's what they told me. The governor and the
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): FBI said they want this done by Monday.
Why does the FBI care
Speaker 111: what happens
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): to the university campus?
Seems a little out of
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): the chain of command, if you're asking.
The FBI is a
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): law enforcement agency based out of Washington, D.C. that handles federal crimes.
In
Speaker 112 (lower-pitched voice): federal investigations,
that's the
Speaker 27: role of the FBI. So
if you
Speaker 27: have a murder in your hometown,
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): I don't
know where you
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): live, but, you know, assuming you're one of our 75 to 80 percent of people here in our audience that are inside these United
Speaker 49: States, you know, I live in a town outside of Nashville. If there's a murder in my local town,
the police
Speaker 49: chief will handle it.
They have
Speaker 49: jurisdiction, the local
Speaker 9: police in the city. The mayor directs the police. So the mayor would be involved. The county, I suppose, has
Speaker 78: sort of overlapping jurisdiction within the county because the county is the subagency of the state. Cities are just municipal corporations. They're
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): formed by citizens who get together and say, we'd like to pool our resources to provide some water, sewage, gas, whatever.
uh
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): roads
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): parks so
maybe the
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): county would have some some
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): jurisdiction over a murder in my hometown um the attorney general
of the state perhaps could
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): could take over
Speaker 17: the investigation i think in in most states the attorney general has that ability to come in and take over an investigation and that
Some
Speaker 17: towns are small, you know, you get a city of 500 or 1,000 people, the local police chief may not want to investigate the guy. If he's pretty powerful or pretty popular in town, it'll ruin your life if you investigate him. So the attorney general might be able to come in. But one person who has no jurisdiction over
Speaker 27: that crime in all likelihood is the FBI. A routine murder that doesn't
cross
Speaker 78: state lines, that just...
Speaker 78: Just one person who's a resident of Tennessee kills somebody who's
Speaker 8: in my city. The FBI really doesn't have any jurisdiction over that.
And even if they did
Speaker 8: have jurisdiction over that, the likelihood that it would make any sense to anyone observing the goings-on, that
Speaker 5: the FBI would then come in and say, oh, oh, oh, and by the way,
tear down
Speaker 5: the crime scene.
Speaker 5: excuse me, sorry,
Speaker 114: tear it down. But, but this is someone's property.
Speaker 99: This is a property here. We don't want to tear down the guy's house. You know, he's murdered in his house. I don't know. Tear it down, tear it down to
the
Speaker 5: studs, take it down to the ground, put it on the foundation, take it down to the slab.
That's a really
Speaker 5: weird request that the
Speaker 8: FBI would be going to the owner of a crime scene, the state of Utah.
and saying, I
Speaker 59: want this crime scene destroyed by Monday. This crime was committed on Wednesday. You have four or five days to get this bad boy completely destroyed. It's
enough to make
Speaker 59: you wonder, did
they have an
Speaker 59: interest in that? Beyond just,
is this
Speaker 115: something
Speaker 59: that the FBI normally does, go around beautifying campuses, recommending campus beautification and demanding that campus beautification be done on a constricted timeline? Probably not.
Speaker 59: That's probably not something that's normal. Again, if
I'm Tyler
Speaker 59: Robinson's defense team, I'm probably going to try to get the judge to allow me to raise this issue.
Why was the FBI
Speaker 16: concerned with destroying the crime scene?
And so quickly. And so quickly. Keep in mind, in the first
Speaker 30: few days, there weren't a lot of questions about who did this, how and why.
I
Speaker 116: mean, it took me a little while to start thinking this doesn't make any sense. In
fact, when I
Speaker 116: started down the Google Trends road,
Speaker 59: which is kind of how people started watching this program, when I started wandering down the Google Trends road, even though I was finding all these Washington, D.C. hits and hits
Speaker 78: from overseas on these individual bit players, I still was thinking...
They
Speaker 78: must have coordinated with Tyler Robinson. If it worst case scenario is
Speaker 16: they coordinated with Tyler Robinson to pull this off.
It wasn't for
Speaker 16: weeks that it dawned on me that this may not be Tyler Robinson at all. He
may be a
Speaker 16: role player in this thing. Sure. I mean, maybe he was there and maybe he, you know, was part of some larger scheme,
but I
Speaker 16: don't, I don't think he actually pulled a trigger and I don't,
maybe a
Speaker 16: trigger wasn't pulled at all.
That took
Speaker 16: me weeks and weeks to get to.
I
Speaker 16: don't know anyone, frankly, who was raising that issue within five days. If
they were, I
Speaker 11: don't recall. I
think one of the first few
Speaker 11: people that raised the issue that I saw was Chris Martinson, where Chris Martinson was saying, hey, wait a minute, that angle doesn't
Speaker 77: work from the Lossie Center. That
angle doesn't
Speaker 77: work at all from the Lossie Center.
In
Speaker 77: fact, that you're way off
Speaker 11: kilter from there. It would not come through
at a
Speaker 11: nine degree angle and hit his neck. In fact, I think I would estimated
Speaker 78: it like 12 degrees when I did it and it still didn't hit his neck.
And then I
Speaker 78: looked at Chris math and I like his math better. He
seemed to be
Speaker 78: smarter than I was on that issue.
But
Speaker 3: the FBI being so concerned, the FBI and Governor Cox being concerned, when I was watching this, I thought, oh, we have a real problem on our hands here. Now, he's going to go through here for
Speaker 55: the next 30 seconds or so the method
of how
Speaker 55: quickly they had to work in order to get
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): this done. And we need to get it done. We're not
asking
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): questions. We're not talking to the media.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): And so I said, okay, so I just, I just, you know, that's kind of my MO is, you know, I've been in so many car wrecks and, and, you know, I
got a
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): rollover when I was 17 and there was three girls in the car. I, I broke my back in three places, got a traumatic brain injury, but nobody has, I didn't have my seat belt on. I wrecked, we rolled down the freeway, we landed on the wheels and I got out and say, all the girls
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): were screaming. I said, who's hurt?
how do i
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): get i got all the girls
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): on the stretchers and then so it's kind of my mo is i under pressure i know how to just show up and help as best i can so that's so you guys got it done that day the next day
Speaker 118: and so we worked until night um and you know basically until dark
Speaker 119: and then we came back the next morning and start
hold on was there a
Speaker 120: cut there that i didn't see before
let
Speaker 120: me i'm not watching this just to re-watch it but did i catch a cut that i didn't see before hang on let me watch
that again how do i get
Speaker 103 (lower-pitched voice): i got all the girls
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): on the stretchers and then so it's kind of my mo is i under pressure i know how to just show up and help as best i can so that's so you guys got it done that day the next day and then so we
Speaker 118: worked until night um and you know basically until
there
Speaker 121: was a cut
there i
Speaker 122: wonder what they cut
out
that's
Speaker 124: really interesting. That's
Speaker 125: really, really interesting. I
wonder if
Speaker 125: they cut it because he was rambling, because he was
Speaker 72: kind of rambling before that, or
if they cut
Speaker 72: something and he didn't say it right and he wanted to re-say it. It's interesting. I'm
not a fan of cutting
Speaker 126: interviews, by the way. I know people do it. I
like live interviews
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): where people just talk.
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): rather than cut it up and edit it because then you know that what they said is what they said and they you know
Speaker 127: they might have rehearsed it and they might have fed you lines but
that's interesting okay so
Speaker 127: that was the urgency
with
Speaker 16: which they worked they worked all the way until night sunday night he gets the call sunday he puts together a team even though
Speaker 10: his normal team's not answering the phone they work
until night they show up to the
Speaker 10: scene the guy's like hey, we're not talking to the media, which is a little weird in and of itself.
They work
Speaker 10: until dark,
they
Speaker 126: go sleep on it, they wake up the next morning, and they work until the job is done.
Now, this guy asked a question,
Speaker 128: the interviewer here, asked
a
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): question that I think is...
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): Frankly, a pretty good question because it's a question I had. Is this normal to excavate this much dirt? Do
you
Speaker 129: think it was weird that they immediately decided to excavate and pull up a murder scene of such an important
Speaker 130 (lower-pitched voice): murder that completely doesn't make any sense with the official narrative? Don't you think that's super weird that they would immediately try to excavate all that and pull it up instead of making it a crime scene? So here's what a lot of people
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): don't realize.
is
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): is very public crime scenes don't last
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): as a crime scene very long they just don't typically speaking they come in they take all their evidence they wash it down with a with a fire truck so that people aren't coming and looking at all the blood and the gore that's fairly typical i don't know that that's what i know so this at this point that happened
Speaker 130 (lower-pitched voice): tuesday we're sunday so tuesday yeah i until sunday is a longer time i thought because but they started
Speaker 130 (lower-pitched voice): pulling it up i think yes like the next day or two
Speaker 5: days later you weren't part of yeah i wasn't part of that
so a
Speaker 5: couple things here one is the question was is it normal to excavate a
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): crime scene the next day or very quickly after and his answer was which i thought was the only real weird part
Speaker 10: of the interview for me from him was he was like oh yeah that's perfectly normal you know they typically hose down a crime scene they didn't hose down the crime scene that's not what we're talking about
Speaker 10: Like, have they come in and hosed the blood down? I get that. It's a public facility. It's a college campus. You're going to have people walking around. Maybe
you don't want them
Speaker 10: traipsing through
Speaker 49: a biohazard, for example. Not that Charlie had any kind of weird diseases, but you never
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): know. You know, you don't want blood out there. Maybe you've got hepatitis or something. You don't want someone contracting some weird disease.
Speaker 51: That was weird to me, though, that the interviewer asked a really solid question. Hey, man, don't you think it's a little unusual that they were excavating a crime scene? Not washing it down, excavating it, removing the crime
Speaker 107: scene, relocating the crime scene, digging up and removing the crime scene. Don't
Speaker 8: you think that's weird?
I
Speaker 8: mean, again, I totally agree that if somebody dies on the side of the road and they get run over and they, you know, fluids
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): and blood, you're going to probably hose it down after you take your pictures and measure and all that kind of stuff.
But that's not
Speaker 58: excavating. Let me answer the question for you. You ask me that question, sir. Is it weird they excavated? Yes, it's weird they excavated. Are you out of your mind? It's totally weird.
it's
Speaker 58: totally weird. And it looks like a coverup.
That's the
Speaker 58: right answer, sir. That's
Speaker 8: the only answer here. It's absolutely weird.
It actually
Speaker 132: probably, that makes more sense. Cause like, I thought you were part of like the pulling it up and everything else. So
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): after we put the pavers in, you know, we were working as a team, but
I was going past
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): some of the grounds guys. And I said, as you know, I just hollered at him, said, hi,
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): and he wanted to tell me about uh you
know he was
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): the one who pulled it up oh really yeah what did he have to say um do you remember his name uh i don't know i don't think i got his name but he was part of the grounds crew for uvu and he was pretty ticked he was like dude i don't know why the hell they're bringing you guys in here or why they're bringing the state in here you know they made us tear everything out um
the
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): blood and the nastiness, you know, he was responsible for the cleanup and he was a little bitter. You know, he's like, I don't know why they're bringing other state guys, other state employees to, to clean, to finish out
Speaker 133: this crime scene. So
he's not the only one that
Speaker 134: thought it was, I'm not the only one that thought it was weird. The other guy thought it was weird. The guy who actually was
Speaker 57: contracted to do it. Now I want to fast forward a little bit. I will give you a
Speaker 82: language warning here.
um
Speaker 82: there's some foul language in two or three words of foul language in this it's a it's it's it's about a 36 second clip so
it's not long
Speaker 53: um but
what i like
Speaker 53: about this is it gives us insight into his mindset there are a whole lot of people who look at this guy and
Speaker 57: think he had to be in on it he's lying he's not telling the truth he's a dishonest actor he's part of the cover-up and i understand that instinct
but I
Speaker 57: want you
Speaker 53: to hear the next 36 seconds. And I left the cuss words in there because I think it, it, I
could have downloaded
Speaker 53: out and bleeped them out. I think it adds to the story because it lets you in on his mindset about what he thinks of the Charlie Kirk case. So I want you to hear his thoughts
on
Speaker 120: this.
Speaker 109 (lower-pitched voice): I didn't want to be there, but I was trying to be useful as you look up and you see where they're saying this
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): shot's coming from. It's in plain fucking view.
Speaker 135: you can see like, but dude, I've hunted a 30. Six from that closer range
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): does not do what that bullet did. Right. You look at the videos, you see his shirt, do some crazy
Speaker 135: shit. You see his, his team catch him before he hits the fucking ground,
but yet they
Speaker 135: can't see a guy right in front of them setting up. Like it didn't make any sense to me.
I,
I think that
Speaker 136: exonerates him. Think
of all
Speaker 136: the Fed sloppers we've
Speaker 90: encountered during this process. Every one of them we've
encountered
Speaker 59: during this process has maintained. Oh,
yeah, no, that's a
Speaker 59: 30-06. You know, Martin Luther King got shot with a 30-06. Well, you know,
Speaker 22: maybe.
Speaker 22: uh, and, and the bullet didn't escape from him. Well, yeah, it did. It actually did it. It went in the side of his face. It escaped him. It went into his neck. It escaped him. It went
Speaker 94: back into his body and it then came to a rest against his scapula.
Speaker 10: It hit like three really hard bones and a bunch of internal organs. It didn't hit two or three inches of soft tissue and stop. That's not what happened with Martin Luther King. Totally different scenario. Apples and oranges. And I will, I will submit to you this. Anyone who uses the Martin Luther King example is lying to your face.
Speaker 61: They cannot be trusted.
They
Speaker 61: have an ulterior motive, and they're eating fed slop. They're eating it like Alpo.
They love
Speaker 61: the fed slop. They can't get enough fed slop.
Alpo,
Speaker 16: good for dogs, bad for humans. Same with fed slop. It's terrible for humans. Bad for your health. It doesn't taste good. You should spit it out when you encounter it. Yet there
Speaker 137: are people, many people, podcasters, TPSA employees, mainstream establishment, uniparty right wingers,
who
Speaker 10: all basically will tell you 100%. Oh, yeah, Tyler Robinson did this with his granddad's.30-06. He actually built the.30-06 on the roof, you know. He put it together, but it was still zero, just fine. He took one
Speaker 6: shot, hit him clean, killed him, ran off, ditched the gun, came back for it, and they caught him.
And I'm telling you, this guy
Speaker 17: doesn't believe the
Speaker 90: story.
This guy
Speaker 90: doesn't believe the story. He just said, I don't believe he was
Speaker 10: shot with a.30-06 from the low season. I
don't think he was shot with a
Speaker 10: .30-06 from the low season.
And so, is he part of the
Speaker 93: cover-up? I don't think so. I'm
going to
Speaker 93: exonerate the guy. I don't think he was. I tend now to believe his story. I was skeptical until he said that part.
And I was
Speaker 90: skeptical. I went
into this
Speaker 90: interview very skeptical of this guy's involvement. Was he actually part of it? I wanted to give my own independent analysis. I admit I was biased
Speaker 59: when I came into it. But
when he said
Speaker 59: that at the 11 minute and
Speaker 10: 34 second mark.
that
Speaker 10: he doesn't believe that's what happened, that his shirt made all kinds of weird movements and that wouldn't happen if you got shot in the neck and the.30-06 would do tremendous damage to somebody who gets shot in the neck.
I tend now to
Speaker 108: believe that he was just contacted to put down some pavers.
You're free to
Speaker 59: disagree. I'm not telling you what to believe. I never tell you guys what. I wouldn't do that.
In
Speaker 59: fact, if you are
a FedSlapper, I
Speaker 7: think you're foolish, but I'm not going to tell you you shouldn't believe it. I'm
going to tell you I
Speaker 7: don't believe it, and I think it's ridiculous. I think the story doesn't add up, and
I
Speaker 57: think anybody who says it is not using the full quantity of IQ that
was
Speaker 94: imparted to them at birth and developed over the course of many years of living.
But you're free to
Speaker 138: believe
Speaker 8: it.
Free to
Speaker 139: believe it.
Speaker 8: Now,
He goes
Speaker 10: back to the FBI, and why would the FBI use a small-town, small contractor on
Speaker 72: a Sunday afternoon, Sunday morning, Sunday afternoon, Monday morning, to finish an important job like this? We
Speaker 117 (lower-pitched voice): were showing up to be helpful, and that's really all there was. If somebody was covering this up, it
Speaker 119: was the FBI, it was the state, it was not...
some
Speaker 119: maintenance guys and a landscaper you know i
Speaker 140: mean what the fbi would do is they would call a random landscaper right which
Speaker 130 (lower-pitched voice): made no sense like why do you think they called you like you're kind of a smaller operation like it didn't that was the part where i was like oh they kind of used him like because they make no sense you're you're not a big operation you're not you wouldn't be the first call no you're also like a very humble quiet guy
Speaker 140: you know it's like a
Speaker 140: - I just felt like maybe that's why they picked you.
Speaker 74 (lower-pitched voice): - Yeah, and maybe that's part of what kind of blinded me a little bit, you know, is I got a call and they said, and it was like, the hell would they
Speaker 84 (lower-pitched voice): call me?
Speaker 89 (lower-pitched voice): I'm like, definitely not the most qualified, you know? I mean, I do hardscapes, but, and we were close. That might've been it, I don't know. - How close were you to UVO?
Where
Speaker 142: was your
Speaker 143: shop? - My shop is probably less than two miles away. -
Speaker 142: Okay. - So it's right there. - So that could've been just Google the closest one to UVO kind of thing. - Yeah, and I answered.
I
Speaker 142: answered the call. So do you regret doing it? No.
Speaker 144: Okay. No. And
I got to tell
Speaker 145: you, that makes
sense
Speaker 146: to me.
Now, it
Speaker 146: doesn't make sense to me that the FBI would want to excavate a crime scene. I'm not exonerating
Speaker 22: the FBI. It doesn't make sense to me
Speaker 10: that someone would want
to pave over the
Speaker 10: crime scene, put pavers down. That doesn't make sense to me.
Speaker 10: It doesn't make sense to me that you would start the excavation process without having a contracted paver on standby ready to finish
Speaker 17: it out. That doesn't make sense to me. It doesn't make sense to me that you would call some random guy on a Sunday morning and say, hey, this is a paver emergency. That part doesn't make sense to me.
But it makes sense
Speaker 9: to me that the FBI would call some random local guy.
Speaker 9: because they couldn't possibly get away with it if they had somebody already lined up or if there was some mega national company who showed up on the scene to do
this right
Speaker 57: away. That would look really, really sketchy. Really, really sketchy. Now, one more clip here, and I'm only playing this out
of love for our principal because my guy
Speaker 57: loves all over our principal here, and I got to play it. I'm not going to get through without
Speaker 55: playing this 37 seconds of him just
sharing
Speaker 55: the love
Speaker 147 (lower-pitched voice): sense this isn't adding up and so you're kind of grasping for straws a little bit like people that criticize candace owens i think it's funny because i'm like i love candace owens she's wrong about stuff but she admits it but she's not trying to get everything right she's doing what an actual investigative journalist should do you're just throwing questions out you're asking questions you're talking to people you're taking every single piece of
Speaker 147 (lower-pitched voice): you know possible clue or evidence or whatever you can and you're trying to figure out what happened like if i die tomorrow i want somebody to go to bat for me like candace owens like i don't care if she's wrong 20 of the time she is trying to get it right and she's asking enough questions
i love that i
Speaker 148: absolutely love it because that's what we do here ladies and gentlemen
Speaker 125: what are we trying to figure out who killed charlie kirk how and
why i think
Speaker 125: we're getting very close to the why I think we may have already nailed the why, frankly.
So the
Speaker 125: who kind of flows
Speaker 9: from the why. We don't know actually
the name
Speaker 9: of the person who yet. I
don't
Speaker 149: think. But
the who kind of
Speaker 49: flows from the why, the how, that's a little more difficult question. Particularly if you think there's government involvement or foreign government involvement because
they have really fancy
Speaker 150: tools. They don't always tell us about it. I
Speaker 75: mean, like...
I
Speaker 75: mean, for crying out loud, they're releasing UFO files showing us things flying around in ways that we didn't know were possible.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): I don't believe those are extraterrestrial. I
think it's
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): probably mostly government stuff, and they're releasing it to show other countries, hey, look at the cool stuff we can do.
But I like that
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): he recognizes how
Speaker 72: messy and sloppy sometimes investigations are. Now, we try to get it right
Speaker 10: every time. When I do a show, I think I'm right that day.
But if it
Speaker 10: comes out later and I look and I say,
Speaker 11: well, I got that one wrong. You'll hear it first from me. I don't wait to be called on it. I will go to bat for myself and my team. Oh,
I
Speaker 75: forgot to say this early. Let me go back to the beginning real quickly,
Speaker 22: and then I'll
Speaker 151: move on
to the next
Speaker 151: thing I was going to cover. Let
me give you
Speaker 85: the order of who's who in this program, because
I got a
Speaker 85: lot of congratulations to Daisy for having
Speaker 11: my grandchild. We're not related.
I've
Speaker 11: never met her. I've only talked to her.
Speaker 16: That is
not my
Speaker 16: child. It is not my wife. My sister is nurse Casey. That's not my child. It's not her baby either. Nor is nurse Casey, my wife. No, no, no. Mrs.
Coleman
Speaker 90: is Mrs. Coleman. Nurse Casey is my sister and Daisy is a wonderful part of our team. But there's no relation there. There's no relation there. So when I get the, um,
Speaker 90: When I get the, congratulations,
I
Speaker 152: bet Daisy's just glowing. Hey, hey, hey, hey. I'm sure she is, but it's not because she gave birth to my grandchild.
She
Speaker 153: may be glowing. I don't know. But she did not give birth to my grandchild. So let me just
Speaker 154: clear that up. I meant to clear that up before
I got
Speaker 154: going tonight, but I forgot.
Now, let
Speaker 154: me go through
some of
Speaker 154: the records
Speaker 55: we have. I have to...
Speaker 55: mute some of the music here because I have no idea why people insist on breaking news
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): this way. If you put out documents, just put out the document.
But if
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): you're going to break it this way, then don't put a bed of music behind it.
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): Then it basically becomes useless
Speaker 19: for broadcasting purposes. What I'm going to show you is a series of text messages that Project Constitution got a
Speaker 50: hold of.
Speaker 50: Project Constitution on X, he got a hold of these text messages that relate to this very construction project.
Now, Project
Speaker 51: Constitution, these texts that I'm going to show you are not texts between the hardscape guy you just saw and
Speaker 155: UVU.
That's not
Speaker 155: who they are. The texts are between, I believe, the company that was contracted to do the excavation process.
Speaker 155: and the people at
uvu so
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): as i show you these keep that in mind and notice the dates notice the times on these
so this is
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): september
Speaker 157: 13th
this is september
Speaker 68: 13th we'd
like to
Speaker 68: start this is the blue is from uvu i believe we'd like to start with a 20 by 60 paver pad
Speaker 57: in our courtyard are you coming down tomorrow i'm in route now
My
Speaker 57: guys are getting stuff together for the paver pad. Again, the paver pad. And the reason
Speaker 54: I don't think these are texts with the actual paver we just heard from is
these came
Speaker 54: on Saturday, September 13th. You can see that right there at the top of the screen. I don't know if you can see my mouse
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): or not, but I'm circling it with my mouse at 628 p.m.
So they're
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): putting the pad
Speaker 158: together.
while I'm in a
Speaker 57: meeting, do you want one of my staff to meet you? Yes, not sure where yet, though. Let's say 8 o'clock at
Speaker 8: the site on the plaza. Okay, should work. Now, I believe that's probably 8 p.m.
the night
Speaker 8: of Saturday, September 13th.
Perfect, thank
Speaker 55: you. And then apparently he says, we don't want the sod.
and then he
Speaker 55: talks about they have some fencing that's going to show up.
This is
Speaker 55: the contractor. If you remember, there was some fencing that went around the upper perimeter. Is there an on-site contact we should coordinate with? Just pull it up, unload, install. Just get her done. Thank you. And then here is Monday after it is finished, Monday afternoon. Patio is done, and
then they talk
Speaker 55: about the flag, talk about it being a loaner.
Speaker 54: um do you have anyone coming to plaster the ceiling this was interesting because the
ceiling they're talking
Speaker 54: about is that
Speaker 47: tunnel that charlie kirk walked through before
the event
Speaker 47: the tunnel that they ran through with
Speaker 53: charlie kirk's body after the event and the tunnel that a lot of people exited out of
And
Speaker 53: initially, there were some questions because they did repair the tunnel. The roofing of the tunnel had some spalling. It looks like it's concrete spalling or some sort of damage to the underside of that tunnel or the underside of the ceiling of that tunnel. And they were sort of concreting
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): over that, fixing it. And there were some questions of, well, was it damaged in the attack? Is this evidence
of a
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): bullet? Is this evidence of some sort of explosion? Yeah.
But I
Speaker 57: tracked down some really high-quality footage I'm not allowed to show because that was the deal. I was able to look at it but not show it. And the high-quality footage was taken from somebody who was at the event. And
you can see
Speaker 155: that ceiling before the event, and the damage is already there. And
so the damage
Speaker 155: didn't come during
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): the event. And my guess is they took advantage of the fact that, hey, we're already beautifying this area. Let's
just go
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): ahead and fix that while we're at it.
So that's what he
Speaker 55: was talking about. Do you have anyone coming to plaster the ceiling? Not yet. We'll get working on that piece.
Speaker 55: So-and-so's on it. He'll be on site tomorrow morning to assess with so-and-so.
Then they're
Speaker 55: talking about the flag again, I think. We do want it brightly lit. Then they brought things. This person says, when will I see something
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): from the architect? Now, this is weeks later, Monday, September 29th.
So let's go back
Speaker 55: to this here. This is somebody asking if they want the sod. We don't want that sod. You can junk that.
Speaker 55: sounds good we'll get it out of here and then he says stand by we do want some over by the
Speaker 159: event center and then
he circles a
Speaker 159: spot here on this path now i have tracked down that path on a map i know where that path is i don't believe they ever laid that sod because i had before and after picture from that very spot and it doesn't look like the sod was actually laid there so i don't know what
they did with said
Speaker 55: okay there's a couple small uh spots east of the ticket booth at the event center that did not take
it will
Speaker 55: be very obvious if they go take a look. It was too hot when we laid it. This will be around. This go around will be great timing. The sod will easily lift up. The new pieces can easily be put back in place.
Speaker 57: I looked on a map, some aerial photography
Speaker 55: taken the day of September 10th,
east of the
Speaker 55: ticket center, east of the event center, east
of the ticket
Speaker 55: booth of the event center. And it does not look
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): to me anyway as if the sod was laid down fresh. But
it's possible
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): I'm wrong about that.
Speaker 55: Maybe that sod didn't take either.
And he
Speaker 55: says, after we do that, are we okay to remove the remaining sod? Yes, we won't trash it. So if UVU needs it in the future, we'll have it. Sod is pretty cheap. So somebody still has this sod,
or at
Speaker 55: least did at the
Speaker 57: time this was
Speaker 51: sent. And then they said, this is interesting in a disgusting way.
Apparently red is something
Speaker 51: they were
Speaker 160: considering for the pavers. Now, keep in mind, a man lost his life in this location.
And
Speaker 161: red pavers were
kind of
Speaker 161: would look like blood. So
he said gray
Speaker 161: pavers on it.
And then he
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): sends a pen where the new sod needs to be placed. I don't know if it got placed there. It doesn't look
like it
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): to me. Then they talk about the irrigation, not really relevant. Then they said the media was there bothering the team.
And
Speaker 55: then he said, can you find more fencing for the top of the...
Speaker 55: kiva we'd
like it with
Speaker 55: smaller gaps add
to the temporary fencing at the
Speaker 55: top yes please okay we're on it thank you sounds like you you has some we can use if so
Speaker 57: we'll bring it down asap what's interesting about you
you is
Speaker 57: that's the university of utah their color is red and it sounds like that might have become an
issue
Speaker 55: because he said nice I'll see
Speaker 50: you next time.
we want to
Speaker 55: fully fence off the top of the plaza as it begins the stair step. Yes, the top edge. UVU has some barriers available, but they are bright red. No thank you. Any
Speaker 58: other color? Again,
Speaker 50: they're staying away from the red theme, I assume, because of the death of Charlie Kirk that took place at this very location. I can't
think of any
Speaker 50: other reason they would be
Speaker 160: staying away from red. I
know I thought the
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): same thing.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Laughy face. I mean, that's a little dark for me, if I'm being honest. I don't know
that a
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): laughy face was appropriate there, but
people say
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): weird things by text and
Speaker 51: it's hard to understand tone and tenor and meaning and all that. Tell
me how
Speaker 51: many spouses have fought or boyfriend, girlfriend, or father, child or mother, child have fought over the
Speaker 55: tone of a text, right? It happens, it happens. They
made the
Speaker 55: change of the paver color this morning.
and
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): then they've talked about being able to get some galvanized, that's gray fencing from the state fair. And
then they have
Speaker 55: 182 feet of fencing. So that's how the conversation ends.
Again, that's Project
Speaker 163 (lower-pitched voice): Constitution had that text thread up. I think he
Speaker 164: got it from Shadow of
Ezra on
Speaker 164: there, but...
It shows
Speaker 47: the amount of thought that went through this. Now,
what about
Speaker 47: the pavers? Do
we have
Speaker 47: more evidence that
Speaker 165: these pavers were put down in a massive hurry? Well, yeah, we do. As
a matter
Speaker 165: of fact, we do. Because one of the
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): FOIA requests, or they call it a Utah GRAMA request, G-R-A-M-A. I'm not sure exactly what that stands for. I'm
Speaker 54: assuming the R stands for record, government record something.
One of
Speaker 54: the requests was for the receipts for
all this
Speaker 54: work. Now we know how much it cost to do the
install and the
Speaker 57: cleanup. It was over $30,000, $36,000 they spent
Speaker 10: at the drop of the hat in order to excavate the crime scene. To
make sure the
Speaker 10: crime scene was completely destroyed so no independent investigation could ever be done. No defense team investigation could ever be done at this crime scene. But notice
Speaker 167: where the pavers came from.
Speaker 167: pavers from Lowe's. They went to Lowe's and got the pavers. Nothing wrong
Speaker 165: with Lowe's. It's a fine store. I go to Lowe's regularly. We have a Lowe's and a Home Depot here in town. I use them both. Depends
on what
Speaker 78: side of town I'm on. If
I need to stop
Speaker 78: at Lowe's, if I need to stop at a home improvement store and I'm on that side of town, I stop at Lowe's. I'm on that side of town, I stop at Home Depot. I
have no problem in the world
Speaker 3: with Lowe's. It's just weird to me that they I'll see you next time.
I don't
Speaker 3: know. I
Speaker 167: don't know where I thought these things would come from. I guess I thought there was like a place professional pavers got their pavers from. But
Speaker 41: here is the receipt on September 15th
at 4.11
Speaker 158: p.m. for the return of the pavers. These are the returns of the excess pavers here on the afternoon
Speaker 54: of the 15th. So September 10th was Wednesday. 11th was Thursday.
Speaker 54: 12th was Friday, 13th, Saturday,
14th,
Speaker 155: Sunday, the 15th. So this is the afternoon of Monday, the 15th
is when
Speaker 55: they return it.
And this is the
Speaker 55: actual purchase the day before the afternoon of the 14th
Speaker 168: at 4.30 p.m.
That's Sunday afternoon at
Speaker 168: 4.30 p.m.
And I find it
Speaker 168: interesting that he
Speaker 55: put it on
Facebook.
six
Speaker 55: different visa cards, but that's just interesting because it's weird to me. But yeah, it's amazing on a decentralized investigation with everybody asking for documents what you can actually come
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): across.
Let's
Speaker 169: see. No,
I don't want to
Speaker 169: play.
All
Speaker 170: right, now let me switch gears here.
Because there's
Speaker 171: still several things about the case. I mentioned the paving over the crime scene. I've distilled this case
to like
Speaker 47: six things that bother me. And
when I put them all on
Speaker 47: a sheet of paper and I looked at them, I
figured out why it bothered me. It bothered me because they all
Speaker 4: pointed to one thing.
And a lot of
Speaker 4: these things that bother me aren't about the actual death of Charlie Kirk. It's
actually
Speaker 95: things that took place months in advance of this death.
For
Speaker 157: example, we
start with the fact that
Speaker 172: Charlie and Erica Kirk sold their house.
They sold their
Speaker 68: house. I'm looking at the deed here. Daisy's done a remarkable job
Speaker 68: I'm not
going to
Speaker 68: show it
Speaker 82: because YouTube really gets weird when you show documents
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): that have home addresses. Even though it's redacted, even though they no longer live there, I still don't want to risk it.
It's out
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): of respect to people. They
don't want to invade
Speaker 174: their privacy if you don't have to. But
the date of the sale, if
Speaker 137: you look at the date
of the
Speaker 137: sale on here, it's January of 2025.
Speaker 65: January of 2025, they sell a
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): $5.25 million house. Now, I don't know if you've ever seen this house. I don't know that we've ever shown it on this show because of the privacy angle. This
was a
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): verifiable mansion. It's
in one of
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): the nicest neighborhoods in the entire country, frankly. A beautiful area of Scottsdale, which is a beautiful area of Arizona,
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): which is a beautiful area of the country. This
is a
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): $5-plus million house.
In terms
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): of the percentage of people in the
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): United States who live in a $5.25 million house, it's very small. Well
less than
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): one-tenth of one percent of the country lives in a house like this.
So you're dealing
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): with a very, very beautiful house.
Speaker 95: It's
got a
Speaker 95: pool. It's
Speaker 95: little guest place. It's got a little pool house. It's got a massive garage. It's
got a massive
Speaker 177: garage.
lots
Speaker 177: of bedrooms, lots of bathrooms, living rooms. I mean, it's just the whole nine yards. If you ever look it up on one
of
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): those real estate websites where you can sort of walk through the house, it's
Speaker 178: gorgeous. I mean, the place is fantastic.
They sold this
Speaker 178: house in January,
and they moved to
Speaker 178: a condo.
And if you look at
Speaker 11: Erica Kirk's interview with the New York Times,
this condo was
Speaker 11: something they owned before they sold the house.
and she
Speaker 178: referred to it as kind of a way station between the house and the
Speaker 179: headquarters, TPSA headquarters. Well, it's only like 20 minutes away. You don't need, ladies and
Speaker 160: gentlemen, a
way station
Speaker 160: when you're driving 20 minutes. You
don't need
Speaker 160: a stopping point. Like if you're
at
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): work and you have a building and an office and a really nice suite in that building, Charlie had like a third of a building to himself, a big gigantic building
Speaker 76: that was his.
If you
Speaker 76: have a building like that that you work out of and you have a $5.25 million mansion 20 minutes away, you
don't need
Speaker 78: a condo, a million plus dollar condo between the two. That doesn't make sense. But
that's what
Speaker 78: they had.
That's what
At a million plus
Speaker 78: dollar condo in a
Speaker 65: beautiful controlled access condo facility right next to the Scottsdale
Speaker 51: Airport.
between
Speaker 51: their $5.25 million mansion and the house and his work. And then they sold the house. People
Speaker 76: typically only sell a house for four reasons.
One is
Speaker 76: they're moving into a new house and they sell the house and then they move into the new house. That's option A. The
other three
Speaker 76: are tragic, death, divorce, and
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): disease. From
what we
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): can tell, neither one of them died
in January of
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): 2025. So that's not why they sold the house.
neither
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): one of them had
Speaker 63: a disease that we're aware of.
So if those are
Speaker 63: the four reasons people typically sell a house, death, divorce, disease, and moving into a new
Speaker 179: house, and they didn't move into a new house, they moved
into a
Speaker 179: condo, a substantial downsizing. So that's not why they did it. They didn't do it
for death
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): or disease. Let's
just keep that in
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): the back of your mind.
Why might they
Speaker 178: have sold the house?
Then you
Speaker 178: have from the Jesse Waters interview, Erica Kirk
Speaker 65: explaining that
the night
Speaker 65: before Charlie passed away, he did not sleep in his own bed. That was news at the time. We weren't aware of that. She shared that
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): voluntarily, and I'm not sure why she did. It made her look terrible. But
she said he
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): didn't sleep in his own bed. But there was another little
fact that she
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): dropped in that interview. It was that he was
Speaker 11: not wearing his
wedding ring or his
Speaker 11: necklace.
Speaker 11: Now, we were told he never took the necklace off for the wedding ring.
In fact, most people who wear a
Speaker 49: wedding ring don't take it off. I mean, it's just on all the time. I
don't wear
Speaker 49: one because I work out a lot. I hang on
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): pull-up bars and rigs and lift barbells and dumbbells and kettlebells, and it damages your finger. It damages the ring, damages your finger.
I don't want to take it on and
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): off and lose it all the time,
so I have
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): it in a safe place.
If I get
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): dressed up,
Speaker 11: I'll put it
on. But generally
Speaker 11: speaking, I don't. But people who wear one wear it all the time.
You don't
Speaker 11: take it on at all.
Wedding ring,
Speaker 11: leave
Speaker 76: it on. Particularly men. But that night he wasn't wearing
his
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): wedding ring.
He wasn't
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): wearing his necklace because she said he had to come back in before he left to go to Utah to grab his
necklace and
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): his wedding ring. And he did not tell her
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): goodbye. Now,
if I was going to
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): leave for several days and Mrs. Coleman was asleep, I
would be
not
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): tell her get out of bed and make me breakfast but i would say hey i'm leaving you know taking off love you
bye and
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): then leave
and open
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): one eye and
i love
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): you
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): too and then go back to bed i
think most
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): people most
people in a
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): marriage are that way
but she tells jesse
Speaker 184: waters he didn't sleep in his own bed the night before he was not wearing his wedding ring or his necklace that she gave him as a gift for his first anniversary I agree.
Speaker 185: and he wasn't wearing his wedding ring. He had to come back
in to
Speaker 185: get the necklace and the wedding ring, and he had to come back in because he wasn't in there. He was in another room. And
I started thinking
Speaker 37: of that, and I started thinking of the fact that they sold the house, and no one was dying, and no one had a disease, and they didn't move into another house.
Hmm. So I have
Speaker 186: those two things, and they're bothering me. They're bothering me about this case. They're just in the back of my head. They're constantly rattling around.
Speaker 52: Then I have that
A
Speaker 52: weird image I can't get out of my head of Erica Kirk doing
that
Speaker 187: interview she did with Glenn Beck. It
was a Blaze
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): interview. I'm
going to show you
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): the scene. I'm not going to play it, but I'm going to show you the scene. You remember this? This
interview
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): she did where she kind of got weird eyes. It was the first time we ever saw her weird eyes. It was when we noticed, I think Allie
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): Topfiles was the first one to notice his wedding picture had been removed from over her right shoulder.
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): audience left stage right it's where that scroll or whatever that is up there is
has taken the place but in that interview if
Speaker 188: you
Speaker 189: recall she's looking around the
Speaker 190: desk and she said well charlie just made notes he was constantly writing he made notes all the time and then she picks up a note
And
Speaker 190: she said, for example, here's a note he left. And it was in his own handwriting.
Speaker 187: She kind of showed the screen and she could see it was in his handwriting.
And in it, he
Speaker 187: gave two lists. It was
Speaker 191: like priorities or important things and not important things. And
the important
Speaker 191: things he said were kids first,
Speaker 192: kids and family, legacy, he said. And the things that were not important, materialism, careerism.
And
Speaker 193: loneliness. Those
are things
Speaker 193: that he did not like.
Things he
Speaker 193: did like were his kids. Family.
Kids first. At the
Speaker 195: risk of getting too theological here,
Charlie seemed to
Speaker 195: understand the Christian theology pretty well.
And I don't know how other
Speaker 196: religions handle this
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): because I'm not of another religion.
but
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): if you look at other religions, or if you look at Christianity, oh, this is great. Daisy actually found an
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): image of this, so I don't have to play it.
The blaze
Speaker 197: is really bad about making you take stuff down. To that family,
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): children, legacy, kids number one, careerism, consumerism, loneliness.
these are
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): the thing he's contrasting these two things.
And I think
Speaker 165: he's frankly contrasting them one at a time here. What gets in the way of
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): family, careerism? What
gets in the way of
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): your time with your children, consumerism? You
can kind of
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): get caught up on buying your kids stuff and not actually spending time with them.
What
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): about your legacy? Well, what can get in the way of that
Speaker 165: loneliness, right? You get kind of stuck in despair.
But look at
Speaker 178: that note and put that note in the context of he didn't sleep in his own bed the night before he passed away. He didn't
Speaker 193: have his wedding ring on. They sold the family home. They
only lived in the
Speaker 193: family home a year or two and then sold it.
but the
Speaker 189: whole kids number one thing I can't get this out of my head because in Christian theology kids are not number
one the spouse is
Speaker 189: number one
and that's a hard
Speaker 105: thing it's a hard truth for people to understand a lot of people get that wrong they get it backwards they put the kids number one and it destroys the marriage
they have nothing
Speaker 105: left because they've put all
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): their energy into their children and then one day the kids leave
And
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): they can't be at home in an empty nest with somebody because they don't, the marriage is gone. They were just parents.
And the kid's number
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): one thing tells me, now, if
he was
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): divorcing her,
first time I
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): mentioned that word, all this is kind of heading that way.
If he was
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): divorcing her, well, the kids would be number one at that point.
No longer married
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): to her.
That can't
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): be number one. The marriage can't be number one if it doesn't exist.
I don't know, just
Speaker 201: mentioning it.
And then we go to just
Speaker 201: this last week. Oh,
I hit the
Speaker 201: wrong button. Let me do that again. We go to
Speaker 165: just this last week. We
get our
Speaker 165: principal
Speaker 11: talking about some information she had that she broke for the first time that she'd been
sitting on.
and put this
Speaker 202: information in the context of everything we've been
Speaker 203: talking about. - That I hadn't shared. I actually learned this some time ago, but today feels like a good time to do so. And let me preface this with the fact
Speaker 204: that this came from Erica. So it is of course, plausible, always plausible that she lied, but I can confirm that she said it to multiple people. Not to me, but to multiple people. I have evidence of
that.
In the
Speaker 204: weeks following Charlie's assassination, she shared with people that Charlie and her were due to sign updated end-of-life documents on September 15th.
Let me say
Speaker 204: that again.
Charlie and
Speaker 204: her had an appointment and a date to sign updated end-of-life documents on September 15th, the Monday after he died.
Speaker 205: Hey, Daisy, can you find that countdown post on Instagram? I just thought of something while I was watching it.
That weird countdown post where her mom was
Speaker 206: in it.
Why would you sign updated
Speaker 207: end-of-life documents?
Speaker 138: end-of-life documents being
a
Speaker 138: A will, a proxy, a healthcare proxy, a living will.
Well, most people's
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): living wills don't change.
You either do or don't
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): want end-of-life treatment.
Some people
Speaker 209: have a living will
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): that says DNR. I don't want to be on an intubated. I'm terminal. I don't want to be saved just to be miserable
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): and be panicked. That's not how
I want
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): to go out. So some people will
do a DNR. If I
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): die, just
let me
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): die.
That
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): would be an end-of-life document.
Some people have a
Speaker 59: living will that says, hey, I'm a young father of eight kids.
Plug me
Speaker 59: in on the off
chance I
Speaker 59: make it. I'd like to be around to raise my kids.
But most people don't change
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): that absent some sort of terminal illness. Like you either do or don't. Your living will is kind of either theologically or politically or just personally. It's sort of is what it
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): is. So you're not going to change that. Okay.
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): Your last will and testament typically
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): will, most
of the
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): time, if you have a spouse and kids, sort of be set up to,
you
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): know, maybe put a bunch of stuff in with a trust with the
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): kids and give the rest to my spouse.
or
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): maybe if you're very, very wealthy, give the rest to my
Speaker 62: spouse, but cut off a little bit and give it to my university or cut off a little bit and give it to my church or cut
off a
Speaker 62: little bit and give it to maybe TPSA or some sort of
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): 501c3 organization you really believe in, right? Give them a hundred grand, give them a million, give them 10 million, however much money you have. And
so you probably
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't update those if you
were
Speaker 16: intended to remain married. And
your healthcare proxy,
Speaker 125: though, might change.
Speaker 125: Because your healthcare proxy usually names somebody by name that you want making that call for you
Speaker 210: at your, in the event you're unable
to speak,
Speaker 210: you're out
of it. Like
Speaker 211: a durable power
Speaker 11: of attorney or a healthcare proxy, somebody who can sign documents
on your
Speaker 11: behalf, somebody who can, you know, a durable power of attorney, if it's constructed right, they can sell your real estate, they can access your bank accounts, they can buy and sell stocks,
Speaker 16: there's a lot of things they can do. They can withdraw money, they can, I mean, they can do it, they can act as you.
with a
Speaker 16: durable power of attorney. The
Speaker 93: healthcare proxy, they can kill you. That's morbid, not to be morbid, but
they can
Speaker 93: kill you. Like they can pull the plug on you.
Speaker 212: They have the healthcare proxy. They're making healthcare decisions on your behalf. So
if you're planning to
Speaker 16: get divorced, you
might want to update your
Speaker 16: last will and testament. You might want to update your healthcare proxy.
but I can't
Speaker 179: think of any other reason you would want to necessarily update them absent some major development of some sort. I
mean,
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): typically, if you're married with kids, you
don't name
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): the kids individually in the will unless there's some reason you're cutting one of them out. You just say, to all my kids,
Speaker 213: divide evenly or put it in a trust and it's for their health, education, and welfare, you know, some sort of.
trust
Speaker 214: that will take care
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): of them. And then, you know, the corpus at some point will burst and the money will be distributed to the trust, to the beneficiaries.
That end of life
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): thing was weird.
Update
Speaker 215: the end of life documents.
What if it wasn't the end
Speaker 215: of life documents?
What if it
Speaker 120: was something else?
Because I
Speaker 120: just thought of this while I was watching this.
I'm going to
Speaker 120: play it on mute, I think,
if I can. Yeah, this is
Speaker 216: interesting. So this was
some sort
Speaker 216: of a
Speaker 187: countdown. See this here? This is her Instagram page, 10 days the way, September 16th.
Well, he was going to sign
Speaker 51: end-of-life documents
on September
Speaker 51: 15th.
Speaker 51: So, what was September 16th?
What
Speaker 217: is that countdown for? And
why is her
Speaker 217: mom in it?
When I just heard that
Speaker 98: just now, I
wondered if
Speaker 98: that was the first day of her new life. Like, we're
Speaker 179: going to sign...
Speaker 179: papers, and it's just going to be my mom and me again after this on September 16th.
Speaker 218: Like, if Candace was right, and they were citing papers on September 15th, September 16th would be the first day of
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): her new life if those papers weren't really end-of-life documents, they were end-of-marriage documents.
I don't
Speaker 219: know.
I just
Speaker 219: thought that just now while we were looking at that.
Because I
Speaker 220: remember that
being about
Speaker 220: the same time, September 15th, September 16th.
And then Daisy found what she believes is their
Speaker 165: last public appearance together prior to
Charlie being
Speaker 11: taken out.
Speaker 11: Now, there may be a more recent appearance, but we've been unable
Speaker 179: to find one.
This was at
Speaker 179: the Young Women's Leadership
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): Summit at the Gaylord Texan Resort and Convention Center in Grapevine, Texas, back in June. This was taken on June 13,
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): 2025. June 13, 2025. I don't know why. It's a weird getup, but whatever. She's dressed in this
Pink
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): flowy thing.
I
Speaker 52: haven't seen where they were together after that. Not
seen in
Speaker 52: public together.
You
Speaker 221: know, it has a podcast. It's right in their hometown.
Is it possible
Speaker 222: that truly was their last public appearance, that they weren't seen the rest of June, all of July?
Speaker 222: All of August and the first 10 days of September. I mean, we're talking parts
Speaker 120: of four different months. Talking July, August, September, almost three full months, 90 days.
Where they weren't seen together. And then there's the biggest telltale
Speaker 224: sign of them all.
Ladies and gentlemen, let
Speaker 224: me tell you, when you start seeing this on social media,
people
Speaker 224: are in trouble. I
Speaker 158: find social
media
Speaker 9: posters come
in three varieties. You have people
Speaker 9: who live a little bit more
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): of a public life and their spouse
is a
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): little more private. That's my situation. I've been public now
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): for,
I don't
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): know, 10 or 15 years where I sort of post as a public person. I don't post a lot of my kids.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): I don't post a lot of my wife because I don't want them harassed out if they're out somewhere in public.
And I don't, I don't know, it's just the way
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): we've always been.
So you have those
Speaker 10: people. Then you have people who post everything together.
Like you
Speaker 10: go to their Facebook page and they've got 40 profile pictures and every
Speaker 27: single one is a picture of
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): them together and like every fifth one is a wedding picture because women look great with their wedding. I mean, that's like for most women, that's the best they've ever looked. So they love putting that one
up and you
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): keep swiping on it to look
Speaker 10: for a profile picture of them alone and you can't find one.
And
Speaker 10: every
Speaker 41: picture on every single post is them together. It's them, it's them and their kids, it's them on vacation, it's them. And then like every fifth or 10th post, it's them on their wedding day. That
tends to fade
Speaker 98: with time after you've been married 20 or 25 years. You don't really go to the wedding photo anymore. But someone who's only been married four years, the wedding photo is a very common post.
Particularly women, they love
Speaker 98: posting the wedding.
Well, Charlie was
Speaker 98: a bit this way.
He
Speaker 98: had his personal posts where
he might be
Speaker 16: giving a
Speaker 3: speech or something like that, but he had a lot of posts of him and Erica together, him and Erica and the kids, him and Erica here, him and Erica.
You know, when you
Speaker 3: come across
Speaker 226: somebody like that and all their posts are together and then all of the sudden
it's just
Speaker 227: them and the kids, guess what's happening?
Speaker 227: I mean, guys, this is as sure as the sun is going to rise tomorrow, what I'm
Speaker 16: telling you right here.
When you have
Speaker 16: a friend and they have a pattern, a pattern and practice, to
Speaker 61: borrow from legal terminology, the pattern and practice of your friend is to post couple pictures or
Speaker 5: couple pictures with kids, and that's all they post.
And then all of a
Speaker 5: sudden, they're only posting pictures of them and their kids. They're getting divorced.
They
Speaker 5: just are, like 99.9% of the time. It's
so sure that if
Speaker 5: you were to bet money on it, you would become a trillionaire if you could find someone stupid enough to take that bet. And
you just
Speaker 7: kept taking that bet,
Speaker 228: kept taking that bet, kept taking that bet.
You would become a
Speaker 228: trillionaire. That's how sure it is. Let
me show you
Speaker 229: Charlie Kirk's last two posts.
On Instagram. Guys,
Speaker 230: this is the divorced dad post. Like that's, I mean,
Speaker 231: like, hey, here's
me and
Speaker 231: my daughter. So that's one.
And then
Speaker 231: you get this one.
These were
Speaker 232: his last two posts on Instagram.
Okay.
Speaker 159: Now, notice he tagged Erica in the first one, but not the second one. Now,
this is the picture of
Speaker 159: him and the boy.
Erica always talks about
Speaker 233: Gigi, rarely talks about Mac. Almost never. But
that's the
Speaker 234: old...
I don't want to
Speaker 234: spoil all the guys' secrets, but when they're
Speaker 105: posting pictures of how good of a cook they are, how clean they are, how great their
Speaker 6: job is, here's me and my kids, look what a great dad I am. They're advertising, guys. Ladies, I'm just telling you, that's the way it is.
They're on their
Speaker 6: way out.
and
Speaker 232: so you
Speaker 59: put all this together you you get the selling of the house for no reason the
Speaker 17: house they lived in for like 18 months a multi-million dollar mansion but
selling the
Speaker 17: house
Speaker 231: and moving into a condo then
you get the jesse waters
Speaker 231: interview he wasn't wearing his wedding ring he wasn't sleeping in the room he didn't tell her goodbye then
you get
Speaker 235: the note she found on the desk. We're talking about kids first.
Speaker 236: consumerism, materialism, careerism. That sounds like he's kind
of
Speaker 237: pushing back on somebody who materialism is sort of her thing. Consumerism is sort of her thing. I mean, just look at her jewelry.
Then you go to
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): the, oh, we're changing the end of life documents on September 15th. Well, that's weird. Why
would you
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): change those?
and now
Speaker 76: you add to that what we've dawned on me tonight is the in the weird countdown nobody ever explained
Speaker 78: and nobody ever talked about which was erica kirk announcing something in 10 days with her mom almost
like it's
Speaker 187: gonna be us again you you know you and me mom then
you go to their last
Speaker 187: public appearance together was almost 90 days before he passed
away
and then
Speaker 187: you go to his last two social media pics were
just him
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): and the kids. And
the last one
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): didn't even tag her. I
just get this
Speaker 178: sneaking
Speaker 238: suspicion that they were in trouble. I
mean, real
Speaker 238: trouble. I
don't know that
Speaker 238: you can...
Speaker 187: know for sure based on this stuff but I mean what is what
is an
Speaker 187: investigation but looking for things and saying
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): oh that sure seems to point this way let's look into that further I think that sure seems to look as if he was leaving
her or
Speaker 240: that she was leaving him I
don't know
and
Speaker 241: to me it
I don't know anyway I had one
Speaker 242: more thing
I wanted to
Speaker 33: show tonight it's the most emotion I've ever seen her display and the only time I ever think I've seen her
show
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): real emotion
this is again
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): from Project Constitution I stole this from his ex his
Speaker 244: watermarks on here so it's
not like
Speaker 244: I stole it too much it's
the most emotion
Speaker 6: I've ever seen Erica display
Speaker 245: I'll
Speaker 167: see you
Speaker 41: next time.
there's
Speaker 245: been a lot of questions about, well, she's not acting like a grieving widow. She's laughing at emojis. Oh, look at the emojis. Look at the
Speaker 167: little thumbs up. Five days after he's dead. Oh, hat sales, merch sales. Oh, everybody's
Speaker 41: weirded out by all this stuff. And we can't quite figure it out. We don't quite know what it is. We sort of are struggling trying to identify what's
Speaker 17: happening here. And
it sure
Speaker 17: looks like a lack of emotion. And then Thank
you.
we finally
Speaker 17: find a video where
Speaker 10: she shows real emotion.
And it
Speaker 10: is, well, I'll
Speaker 246 (lower-pitched voice): let you be the judge of what the emotion's about. If
you have trouble
Speaker 246 (lower-pitched voice): hearing it, I'll tell you what it says. My
Speaker 247: husband, as tradition, would donate his entire paycheck back into the organization. I am following suit.
It is
Speaker 247: my honor and deepest
Speaker 248: pleasure
to pledge my entire paycheck back into this organization. We found her
Speaker 249: emotion. We
found her
Speaker 227: emotion.
her
Speaker 227: emotion is when she has to donate her entire paycheck back
to the
Speaker 227: organization.
Speaker 97: That's when she cries. I'm telling you, we just figured it out. Now, she'll laugh five days after he passes
Speaker 61: away. She'll laugh about emojis. She'll brag about hat sales. She'll use the first
Speaker 76: opportunity that she speaks publicly on his death, all in white, standing beside his chair.
Stop
Speaker 12: talking. She
was up
Speaker 12: talking there, by the way.
It's my
Speaker 12: great privilege, my honor,
to donate my entire paycheck back
Speaker 12: to the organization.
But she cried about
Speaker 250: it. I think that was genuine emotion. This
is the
Speaker 250: first time I've seen genuine emotion from Dr. Kirk. This
is the first
Speaker 250: time I've seen Dr. Kirk
Speaker 251: have any real emotion.
and I
Speaker 93: believe she was torn up. I
think she was
Speaker 93: crushed. I think they told her you should do this, and she's like, oh, are you kidding me? It's like half a million dollars a year. Over
five
Speaker 252: years, that's two and a half million bucks. Erica,
honey,
Speaker 82: darling, your husband did it. You should do it as well. And
then she
Speaker 82: cries, and
Speaker 82: cries.
so
Speaker 82: that ladies and gentlemen was real emotion from dr
newly dr kirk but
Speaker 82: dr kirk
Speaker 154: nonetheless if you
have not taken the
Speaker 55: opportunity to like the video yet please by all means now would be an excellent time to take advantage of the opportunity i'm getting you
to do
Speaker 6: that this is my first show back i hope
I'm as
Speaker 6: good as a grandfather as I was as just a father of eight. I hope it met
your
Speaker 71: expectations. It was a little longer than normal, but I wanted to get through all that.
If you
Speaker 71: have any
Speaker 253: questions, you ever want to reach out to the show,
you can
Speaker 253: you're more than
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): welcome to email real baron call a real baron podcast excuse me
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): at uh at gmail.com real baron podcast gmail.com please don't email any other emails i have several other emails i've used for work over time um and and
personal emails
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): don't don't email even if you see them occasionally pop up on the screen don't don't email um it's uh it's annoying because i have to
go i
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): don't read
Speaker 254: them i just go through and block everybody
so um
Speaker 254: that would that would that would be wonderful if you would do that uh but i do want to take a time to get through some of your comments honestly
being
Speaker 49: able to interact with you is the part i missed the most over the last week i genuinely miss being able to um
reach out
Speaker 237: and uh answer questions and interact i'm gifting memberships to the best podcast
Speaker 49: on any network or bp are you saying mine is the best
on any
Speaker 49: network
and
Speaker 49: then you dropped five memos on people's heads just like that. Very kind of you, thank you. Very kind of you. Kimberly, thank you. I
will be
Speaker 49: doing a member show this week. I'm not sure if it'll be Tuesday or Friday, but I am going to do a member show this week. Not sure which day. We missed you.
Speaker 27: Congrats, granddad. Many prayers to the Coleman family during this special time. Christ is king indeed. It
is a
Speaker 27: special time. It
Speaker 27: special
Speaker 11: time. Congrats on becoming a grandfather.
Speaker 11: Thank you. It is not a baby boy. You were wrong.
But as a
Speaker 49: psychopath hunter, I don't think you're... I mean, you may be wrong a
Speaker 7: lot, but no, you were definitely wrong. You had a 50-50
shot, and you
Speaker 7: missed it.
You guessed heads, and
Speaker 7: it was tails.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): You guessed tails every time. Congrats, Granddad. Welcome to baby Coleman to the Grand Jury. Yes, yes, yes. The youngest is going
Speaker 76: to be a member of the Grand Jury, no doubt about it.
Speaker 76: Congratulations on the new baby and welcome back. Have
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): you noticed that Victor Marx is hanging the flag of ISIS underneath the lion picture?
Speaker 51: What a moron.
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): Christ is king indeed. I did notice that, but I was afraid someone would ask him about it and he would tell some weird story about how he infiltrated some ISIS cell and wrestled him to the ground and ripped it out of their
back. That was a weird
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): interview. I almost
did a
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): whole show on that.
That was a weird
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): interview.
of
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): Victor Marks and Candace Owens. That was,
I have a lot of
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): opinions on
Speaker 256: that. Congratulations, Granddad. Thank you, thank you. Congrats, thank you all
Speaker 257: you do. God bless you and
your
Speaker 99: family. Thank you for all you do. Thank you, Morfar. Yes, I am a Morfar. A real one,
a real
Speaker 99: one. Not a Farfar parading around as a Morfar. No, I'm a Morfar.
A
Speaker 72: mofo? No, a Morfar. Morfar. Congratulations on becoming a Granddad. Grandbabies are the best. So happy you're back. We missed you. I missed you.
Speaker 72: I missed you, and they are the best.
Not a lot of
Speaker 72: money, but God bless
that
Speaker 51: new grandbaby. Many, many blessings. Follow them all the days on Pentecost 2. Blessed is in the name of the...
I see a little
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): cross sign. I'm not sure what those other two are. Thank you, though.
Thank you. Congrats on the
Speaker 211: new addition.
Speaker 131 (lower-pitched voice): Welcome back. Christ is king
Speaker 211: indeed. Congrats on
Speaker 63: becoming a grandfather from the grand jury. Thank you. Thank you.
So happy
Speaker 63: you're back. Thank you. Happy to be back. Asking for some prayers from fellow Christ followers as I'm quitting
Speaker 211: my job to open up a faith-based shop and need his direction. What
is
Speaker 258: that emoji?
Speaker 211: Coffee?
Un
Speaker 258: coffee? Un
Speaker 259: coffee? Yes,
yes, you're
Speaker 259: opening a coffee shop.
Speaker 260: That's amazing. Best of luck to you. And
Speaker 46: prayers headed your way.
Speaker 260: Shabbat shalom. Granddad's home.
Speaker 261: Yes, yes, yes.
That's
Speaker 260: funny.
Speaker 11: Congrats to 25. My parents are now 40 years. Love is unconditional. A little something for a new baby. Missed you. Love from
Speaker 237: London. Checking in in the middle of the night over there. Thank you. Thank you.
It's a
Speaker 237: different kind of love. Congrats, granddad.
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): It
is a
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): different kind of love.
And I
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): just figured that out this weekend. I did not know that.
I've heard that, but I
Speaker 179: did not know that until I experienced it.
Speaker 179: congratulations on
Speaker 178: your family's new bundle of love so excited for you all hope your daughter's doing well could bless your new uh your beautiful family she's doing
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): amazing man she bounced back she's amazing
she is
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): fantastic she's a great already already uh
Speaker 105: congratulations gramps i'll allow it
i'll allow
Speaker 105: it you can call me gramps not gonna offend me uh you look so happy
Speaker 254: love to see it so glad you're back i'm ecstatic over the moon
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): operating on almost no sleep, and you wouldn't know it because of how happy I am, truly.
Speaker 263: Travperk needs to go. I don't know what that means. I
want to
Speaker 263: say Travperk.
So glad
Speaker 264: you're back. Congrats on
Speaker 184: your little grand bundle of joy. Hope mom and baby are well.
Edge, mom and baby
Speaker 184: are
Speaker 213: fantastic.
Mom and
Speaker 213: baby are fantastic.
Speaker 50: congratulations welcome the grandparent club now you understand the crazy different love we have for our grands god is good and christ is king yeah
it's different i thought
Speaker 237: having a five-year-old at home and a seven-year-old at home it wouldn't be that much different it just is it's just hard to explain but it is congrats
to you
Speaker 237: and your family baron grandkids are the best i've got a three-year-old grandson and another grandson coming in july congratulations sounds like your heart is full
uh
Speaker 105: congratulations grandpa and congrats to the new mommy yes yes she's amazing
you're
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): now officially old. I was old before. I
put a picture
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): of me in awe of the new little bundle on X. If you've not seen that, you can go over there and look at it. But you want to talk about feeling old?
Look at a
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): picture of you in awe of your grandchild with
a gray beard
Speaker 20 (lower-pitched voice): wearing hearing aids. I'll
pull
Speaker 265: it up. It just doesn't get older than this. This is like
Speaker 265: This is peak old.
Let me see if I
Speaker 265: can find it. Yeah, here it is.
You just don't get older
Speaker 265: than this.
As old as it gets
Speaker 265: right here. How do
Speaker 100: I?
Check this out. You want to
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): talk about old.
Look at this. This is
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): your humble host being as old as he can possibly be.
You see that? You see that?
that
Speaker 266: beard is 90% white now I got little hearing aids skizing
Speaker 41: in over here over the
ear and I
Speaker 41: got, you know, the 46 plus years of, of, of, uh, furrows,
but I couldn't be
Speaker 267: happier. I mean,
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): I was just
in awe
Speaker 268: absolutely in awe. So
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): yeah, one of those days, one of those days um
Where
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): was I here? Is
this you? God is
Speaker 270: good. Christ is king indeed. Was
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): that? I don't remember where I was. Congrats to the new mommy. Yes, yes, yes. Congrats. You're now. Oh, that was it. I'm officially old. Yes, I'm old. And from Latvia. We're huge.
Speaker 50: Huge in Latvia. Did Mrs. C doula. I'm a doula with two daughters and curious what's that like. Totally different, but also same. I'm sure
would love to
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): hear about it.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): she did doula as a matter of fact there actually another doula was there as well so she was doula'd up
like the
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): whole room was full but it was great it was a great experience
she
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): was doula'd up there was a hang on a second
Speaker 271: the there was a moment where Yeah.
Speaker 272: where,
you
Speaker 273: know, your kids are always your kids. No
matter how
Speaker 274: independent they are, living on their own, all the
coming parents. But I was kind
Speaker 275: of off to the side, minding my own business.
Speaker 275: And,
you know, it
Speaker 276: was getting down to go time, and I was trying
to stay
Speaker 276: out of it, looking at my phone,
like not watching. And,
Speaker 276: gosh, I don't
know if I should tell this story. Yeah,
Speaker 278: probably. But in a...
in a
Speaker 278: fit of
I don't
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): know if it was fear
or anxiety
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): or desperation or what
you know when your
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): kids fall off
Speaker 279: a bike or something and they
go
Speaker 280: daddy and
Speaker 279: they're like scared and you come running over and
everything's
Speaker 275: alright I'm
sitting there and I'm kind
Speaker 275: of like trying to stay out of it and
I hear
Speaker 281: daddy and
I was
Speaker 275: like
Oh, my. So I try to comfort
Speaker 151: the
Speaker 284: best I
can and stay out of it at
Speaker 284: the same time.
But it
Speaker 284: was a very emotional moment.
It was always
Speaker 284: your kids.
Always your
Speaker 285: kids. But
totally
Speaker 286: different. You
do love
Speaker 286: her more, but it's okay. Well,
Speaker 47: not more, different. I love her differently. I
love my
Speaker 47: kids all the same.
uh
Speaker 47: but i love them differently
you
Speaker 287 (lower-pitched voice): know um that's just reality like you have a different relationship with your oldest than you do your youngest you have a different relationship with your middle child you
Speaker 214: have a different relationship with your grandchild but you know your love is
love each child
Speaker 214: it's it's amazing someone told me
this when i
Speaker 214: first started having kids and it's true each child actually grows
Speaker 49: your capacity to love and you didn't realize that was possible but it does
it does um
Speaker 49: congrats granddad my first grandchild was a girl and was born on 5 22.
She
Speaker 49: turned 19 this year. Grandchildren are the best. Prayers for the whole family and super. Congrats to all. Wearing my pink for you. Thank you.
Real DD61. Thank you. Thank
Speaker 62: you.
Speaker 288: 19.
Wow. Time
Speaker 288: flies. My
first child is 19. I make
Speaker 289: custom rosaries. Do you accept customs to grow your business? I make them. So many people and love to grow a larger
Speaker 290: audience as well.
But
Speaker 290: I'm not doing any advertising, if that's what you're asking. But I
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): actually
have a
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): customer, a listener or viewer. I don't know what we call people on podcasts. But sent that rosary there, and I
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): hung on it. It's beautiful. And I've used it. But,
Speaker 291: yeah,
I'm
Speaker 292: happy to...
Take a
Speaker 293 (lower-pitched voice): look at it. I don't accept gifts well. I'm sorry. I'm terrible. I'm awful at it.
Always
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): have been. First Super Chat ever.
Speaker 294: We missed you so much. That's so exciting. A new baby girl. You both deserve time away. Thank you for sharing your opinion on the CK
Speaker 95: investigation. It's greatly valued. Looking forward to many more life triumphs with you. Thank you, Kimberly. That's awfully kind of you.
Speaker 295: Yeah.
Speaker 296: Like I said, we had our time away so that
Speaker 296: It would be far enough
Speaker 209: away from the delivery. Mrs. Coleman and I snuck off for two or three days, three days,
three or
Speaker 209: four days, that it would be far enough away from the delivery that we could get back to life. But it was the next morning. It was
Speaker 82: not far enough away at all, at all, because you're different. Oh, I don't know what that was to, but I appreciate it.
I hope I'm
Speaker 297: different from someone who's bad.
Speaker 298: Love, love, love being a grandparent. There's nothing like it. Enjoy every morning. I'm trying. I'm soaking it
Speaker 105: in. I'm doing my best.
Speaker 105: You have no idea the love you'll feel until it happens. Congratulations. Hide your credit cards. You'll be wanting to buy her everything. Oh, oh, oh,
Speaker 299: gosh, is that true?
That's going
Speaker 299: to get bad.
Baron, it's so good
Speaker 245: to have you back. Been a
Speaker 10: tough week without you, but for a grandbaby, I'll allow it. Congratulations to you and the even larger Coleman family. Christ is king indeed. Yes, indeed. Thank you so much.
uh
Speaker 294: blessings to you baron just know we all missed you as well but glad you got some well-deserved time off but all the
time
Speaker 76: you can with your grandbaby hope you are refreshed
what a week
Speaker 76: christ is king indeed it was a week
Speaker 7: it was uh the most eventful week i've had in a long time
so long uh what's
Speaker 7: about a time you told us
Speaker 168: about having to let surrender happen pray hope don't worry padre pio yeah
Speaker 33: padre pio uh don't compare me to a saint obviously but um
Speaker 33: yeah yeah
Speaker 300: that's that's great advice pray hope grandparenting completes the emotions of parenting i hadn't thought about it that
way that's interesting congrats
Speaker 222: granddad god certainly had a perfect plan for you to be back just in time for your sweet granddaughter's arrival i missed your show so much i'm
Speaker 294: elated to be here love you be i love you too miss jackson sorry miss jackson But we didn't go far. We didn't go far. We
stayed in
Speaker 179: town.
Speaker 179: Uh, for that reason,
Speaker 301: I mean, she was eight months along and you never know. So we didn't want to be gone, gone, but we, we found a nice place close.
Uh, your heart
Speaker 179: just grows a new chamber when you become a grandparent. Congrats to the family, a new chamber. That sounds,
sounds
Speaker 213: medically damaging.
Four chambers
Speaker 213: is all I want. I don't
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): want a fifth chamber. I don't know how that would work.
I've given birth to two
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): beautiful babies.
One
Speaker 10: just eight weeks ago, completely natural. It
was the
Speaker 10: best experience I've ever had. Motherhood is a gift from God.
And
Speaker 233: yeah, it's always amazing because I forget people don't have natural babies because that's been
Speaker 253: my only experience with my wife. And
when you
Speaker 253: talk to people, very few people have had natural babies. And
when you go to
Speaker 253: the hospital, you realize how few people have had them because people want to come in and observe. They don't
see a
Speaker 253: lot of them.
So you end
Speaker 253: up with a full room of people wanting to see the natural delivery process.
Yeah, I
Speaker 253: know a lot is happening in this
Speaker 62: world, but the arrival of his precious new baby fills our hearts with hope.
We'll fight like
Speaker 62: warriors for her, fiercely protecting her with unwavering
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): love and strength. Yeah, that was one of the things
I, that was one thing going
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): through my head that night,
is what's the
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): world going to be like? What
am I
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): giving this girl? Post
office is going to
Speaker 76: love you now with incoming baby gifts for the little princess. Congratulations, my B. Oh, I forgot about the post office. Yeah, they don't like me too much.
They
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): liked me at first. They thought it was cute. I'd show up at the desk, and they'd hand a couple packages over.
Now I
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): show up, and they're
like, go
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): away.
Speaker 302: Congratulations,
Speaker 76: Baron, and God's blessing on your daughter and granddaughter. Christ is king indeed. Yes, thank you. Thank you. Grandpa Baron, God
Speaker 62: is good.
Christ is
Speaker 62: king indeed. God is very good. God is good, like good.
Not like
Speaker 62: good like
we think,
Speaker 62: but like
Speaker 160: good.
My
Speaker 160: 11-year-old saw your face and said, he must be a granddad now. Look how happy he is.
I am
Speaker 160: happy. It's
a
Speaker 253: different type of happy, but I'm very happy.
Bless you in
Speaker 253: the fan, Baron. Thank you for sharing the joy. Thank you.
Grats on the new bundle of
Speaker 303: joy and beauty. So happy for everybody. Glad Ms. Coleman got her anniversary vacation and a new baby. Happy early anniversary and all the blessings to you and
Speaker 62: yours. You think I look like I'm glowing? You ought to see Mrs. Coleman these days.
She
Speaker 62: slept even less than I have, and she is, like, glowing.
Yes,
Speaker 304: my B, we're in a scary place right now with the White House chaos yesterday.
Eh, I mean,
Speaker 304: yeah,
Speaker 190: I mean,
people lost
Speaker 190: their life. That's tragic.
But shootings happen
Speaker 305: in major cities every day.
It's just, you
Speaker 305: know, shooting
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): near the White House isn't any scarier than...
a
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): shooting in Philadelphia or Chicago or
Speaker 179: Detroit or Nashville or Houston or Phoenix or Los Angeles, you
Speaker 306: know, it's
Speaker 222: tragic. Shouldn't happen,
but they
Speaker 222: do. Biggest congrats, granddad. Much love.
Speaker 27: Congratulations from Papa D to Papa B. Blessings on your new addition. God is good. Thank you, Dana
Speaker 235: Vision. I don't know what Dana Vision is, but.
I don't
Speaker 235: want it. I
Speaker 307: like your
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): comment, though. Thank you.
We're just
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): so happy for y'all. Thank you. We're very happy. We are
Speaker 309: very happy.
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): Congrats, Granddad. You're beaming. Vandy's great.
Speaker 257: Worked as an RM at Vandy's Children's Hospital and Recovery Room for five years. Then SICU at Vandy. I
Speaker 310: don't know what SICU is. This sounds terrible. You're
so
Speaker 99: sick, you have to go to the SICU. I don't know what that is. I know what the NICU is. I
know what
Speaker 99: the ICU is. The SICU?
Speaker 99: you're toast if you go to the sick, you're
Speaker 54: sick. So happy and may Christ bless you and growing family. Congrats to the entire family. Yeah. Vandy was great. I was not expecting it because it's I've always had a hassle there
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): whenever I've had to
go there.
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, no, not sick. Oh, I'm looking up what sick. You
looked up
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): sick. Oh, oh, surgical intensive care unit. I guess
Speaker 311: you're pretty sick there too, though. I
think I would call it
Speaker 311: something else.
Like you don't
Speaker 312: want to tell someone, You're going to the sick you.
You kind of
Speaker 311: want to keep
Speaker 313: their spirits up if they're going somewhere, right? I would think.
I
Speaker 231: don't know. Congrats, Grandad Baron. Only 19 more to go. No, no,
Speaker 266: no, 39 more to go.
I made my kids
Speaker 266: promise me 40 grandchildren. With eight kids, that's not unrealistic.
It's only five
Speaker 314: apiece. They're getting off easy.
They're getting
Speaker 314: off easy. I want 40.
We
Speaker 314: have 39 to go.
No
Speaker 9: pressure. I can already see you going live in the hospital, Jennifer Joy. How good that you behaved well. I know. It was tough.
You know how
Speaker 9: badly I
wanted to
Speaker 9: go live when I held the baby?
Speaker 237: Yeah. I'm one of five kids. My mom took more and more, and my dad had Farfar on their license plates to cover all their sons and daughters. Kids, P.S., this is my family, too. I'm certain we all missed each other. Congrats.
I
Speaker 315: love the license plate. I think more far would be dynamite
Speaker 62: license. I hope
it's not
Speaker 62: already taken. I don't know how many Swedes there are in Tennessee. Happy for you. Congratulations. It suits you well. You're made for
Speaker 187: this. Your granddaughter will be blessed to have you and Mrs. Coleman. Yes, yes, yes. Thank you. Mrs. Coleman's amazing. She's going to be an amazing grandmother.
Speaker 298: They're all man up.
About
Speaker 298: natural birth, eight times, bold choice,
Speaker 2: LOL, as a natural birth mama,
Speaker 99: respectfully. No man could, love you. Time off is so well-deserved. You know, we could, honestly. I'm
just messing
Speaker 99: with you. I know women don't allow that.
Like, that's one
Speaker 99: thing men can't do, so women are like, you'll never be able to handle
it.
and
Speaker 316: I probably, you know, for the sake of peace, I'm going to agree with you.
I'm going to, I'll agree with you
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): for the sake of peace, but thank you for that. Thank you.
Congrats to the Coleman
Speaker 254: family. Hope mom and baby doing great. Great to have you back. They are doing amazing.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): Well, thank
Speaker 254: you. Thank you.
Barron, there is a
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): delightful lightness and
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): happiness about you today. Welcome to the club. I am five grandchildren in and absolutely understand what you're saying.
Speaker 318: glory b for the addition of your special one yeah it's i if you've
Speaker 296: noticed i'm lighter it could have been the time away but it's the
grandchild it's never
Speaker 296: ever superheat
but i
Speaker 296: wanted
Speaker 27: to confirm being a grandparent is like falling
in love there's nothing like
Speaker 27: it congratulations and blessings to you and your
entire family never ever superheat oh
Speaker 27: super chat i bet you
Speaker 78: meant i
don't superheat
Speaker 78: like that's not something i do i did get
in a sauna I don't know.
I love
Speaker 78: Asana, but I don't superheat,
but I've been
Speaker 78: known to super chat. From Helen, I'm
a
Speaker 179: new Grammy. My grandson, Luke, is such a blessing. These are
the words you
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): are looking for. Nothing can prepare you for the joy of your first grandbaby. God bless. I was unaware that nothing could prepare me, but it's true. It's true. Congratulations on becoming grandparents to my favorite couple. While I'm glad
Speaker 50: you are hopefully able to decompress,
It's a
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): relief to see some nice hair again. Blake has been doing too much. What?
Do I have good
Speaker 319: hair? I've always hated my hair.
Never been a fan of
Speaker 319: my hair.
Thank
Speaker 253: you. Congratulations, Grandpa. God bless you, your beautiful new granddaughter, and all the Coleman
Speaker 49: family. Yes, thank you. Thank you. Being a nana has
been the
Speaker 49: greatest blessing in my life. My mama didn't have the opportunity, so it means so much to me.
Speaker 49: congratulations to you and family.
Your mother
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): must have passed young. For that, I'm sorry. Because if you have children, your mother would have been a grandmother, but she must have passed young. I'm sorry to hear that. But it's amazing.
Speaker 320: Amazing.
Speaker 321: Charlie Kirk, not a fan of Governor Cox. For
Charlie
Speaker 11: Kirk tweet, March 7, 2022. I don't know how you could be a fan of Governor Cox. He seems like a monster. If
I'm being
Speaker 11: honest.
uh
Speaker 11: jesus christ
Speaker 179: blessed you with a beautiful grand baby enjoy every moment he did indeed he did indeed
and
Speaker 321: two natural births
at home i
Speaker 321: also used a used to be a doula and i've cried at every birth
Speaker 179: except my own extreme hormone surge highest in a woman's life and that affects everyone around the mom uh your
humble host got a
Speaker 179: little emotional a couple times i
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): didn't boo who, but my eyes missed it
up.
i didn't
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): do the erica kirk you know i didn't do that but
i got a little
Speaker 237: misty a little misty um thank you a generational love and it's
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): emotional especially for men because it's your lineage right there in your arms it's awesome enjoy it welcome to the grandparent club ah thank you happy to be part of
it
Speaker 53: congratulations blessing the coleman family from papa and mama murphy
God
Speaker 53: is good all the time, and
Speaker 323: all the time God is good. Christ is king indeed. Thank you, Papa and Mama. I
don't know what all that
Speaker 51: means. I
see Morfar
Speaker 51: in there. Congratulations, granddad and granny. Oh, this must be sweetie talk. Oh, from Denmark. I am
more
Speaker 324: and more to a four-year-old girl, and I absolutely love getting to see her grow up, my daughter
being a
Speaker 324: mother. I
love that
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): your culture, your Scandinavian culture
all
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): use the same word. I love that. There's no like sugar pie honey bunch or something. You
Speaker 318: know, some of these people choose grandparent names that are like a little weird.
I watched that podcast
Speaker 44: a few days ago. The tell was who instructed them to remove the dirt and pave it over. Yeah, the FBI. That
Speaker 179: was the weird part. That was the weird part. Congrats, granddad. New mom and Mrs. C. I don't know
Speaker 193: her name. Preference?
Tell my Mrs. Coleman. Oh,
Speaker 193: grandma.
That's your
Speaker 294: grandma. We missed you. Fortunately, my S.A. Spurs
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): are in the playoffs entertained in your absence. I'll be honest. The Spurs game was
on in
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): the room at first, and
then it
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): got turned off
when
Speaker 214: things got serious. Might have been watching.
Might have been watching
Speaker 27: it, and then it got shut down. Can a citizen
or local
Speaker 27: state law officer police sue the FBI for obstruction? Citizen, no. Almost assuredly not.
you'd
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): have to show some violation of some civil right that's statutorily outlined. Like section 1983,
Speaker 293 (lower-pitched voice): 84, 85, I don't think you'd be able to do that. Local state law office, I doubt it. I don't know. Not
my forte,
Speaker 293 (lower-pitched voice): but I don't
Speaker 10: think so. My husband and I went on our anniversary trip a week before last to Belize. Well, we did not go to Belize.
I fell
Speaker 10: off a cliff, literally got four stitches in my knee, rough trip, but never missed an episode of your kids. I
Speaker 325: can picture you in the
Speaker 96: hospital
Speaker 326: anesthetized some guy, some Belizean, whatever they call themselves in there, surgically repairing your leg. And you're like, the
principal's
Speaker 327: talking.
uh
Speaker 167: bizarre
Speaker 178: grade slope height now inaccurate makes laser shot recreation wholly unreliable bureaucracy will never correct himself much unelected oh i see what you're saying now
Speaker 146: that everything's changed they can't go recreate the that's a good point
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): and consider that
nice try youtube and
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): blocking super jazz what were they blocking cohen film what
were they blocking i like
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): your super chats
Speaker 237: B, thoughts on Victor M and Hunter B interviews. Also, I'd love to see Daily Fredo on Membo's show. She's great. Actually was going to play a clip of hers today and
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): did not. I may get
to that tomorrow. I
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): like Daily Fredo. I've been watching her here the last couple
months. Like
Speaker 163 (lower-pitched voice): most people, I can't watch everything she puts out, but I do like her stuff.
And
Speaker 163 (lower-pitched voice): she had a piece up the last couple of days I really, really liked and was going to play a piece of it tonight. Like I said, I may play it tomorrow. The Victor Marks interview,
Speaker 332: the guy's a psycho. I mean,
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): there's no other way around it. He's a dishonest actor. He's like, I feel
bad for
Speaker 324: everyone around the guy.
The Hunter Biden interview. I don't know.
I
Speaker 333: mean, it humanized him, which is fine. I
Speaker 334: mean, he's a human.
But I have a
Speaker 335: little trouble with Hunter Biden. I have
a little trouble with Hunter
Speaker 27: Biden. I don't know.
Speaker 27: because of the gas board
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): and the 10% kickback for the big guy and all that kind of stuff.
Like the crack stuff, I
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): mean,
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): people make mistakes. I always tell people I don't want to be judged by my lowest moment. I don't
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): want to judge people by their lowest moment. And I
think if
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): you're a crackhead, that's probably your lowest moment, if we're all being honest with each other.
That's a
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): personal low moment, and I don't want to judge him on that. And I don't. I've never held it against him that he struggled with drugs or alcohol.
I'm
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): happy to see he's no longer struggling. But I don't see a sense of repentance from him for
what I
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): believe is just blatant corruption, and it bothers me a little. I would have loved to see out of him contrition for
some of those
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): things. I think it would have been a
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): wonderful opportunity in front of a friendly interviewer
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): I mean, obviously, she doesn't agree with him. I don't think politically on a bunch of stuff, but
it would have
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): been a wonderful opportunity
for him
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): to say,
and
Speaker 235: another thing, and then, you know, repent. Say, hey,
I
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): used my dad's name to get a bunch of stuff and to get wealth and power, and
we had
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): arrangements in the family that,
and I
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): shouldn't have done it, and I feel bad for doing it, and I wish other people didn't do it. Because what he's done is basically give the Trump kids a free pass.
Speaker 337: frankly uh
Speaker 27: thank you
uh while the
Speaker 27: photographers when they were repaving um probably because it was a famous
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): crime scene and they were
repaving it
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): excavating it and repaving it paving it not repaving it it wasn't paved they were paving it paving over the crime
Speaker 62: scene it's like a a metaphor for corruption
Speaker 62: Congratulations, Grandpa. We genuinely missed our humble host. You and Mrs. Coleman deserve all the love and happiness.
Christ is King
Speaker 63: Eddie. Thank you. Thank you. Congratulations on a new baby. Parenting is love. Clean your room. Get your homework done while we are
going
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): to work. Grandparenting is love. Undivided attention. Spoil more love. Cookies and ice cream. Best title ever.
Oh, I'm going to have to buy some cookies
Speaker 338: and ice cream. Ha,
ha, ha,
Speaker 65: ha, ha.
Speaker 65: You're going to have to invest. If that's grandparent, I need to invest. We don't have ice cream.
Well,
Speaker 339: sometimes we do. Not usually.
Can you help
Speaker 254: me understand why this isn't a mistrial from the jump, please? I've never seen such blatant cover-up ever. How can
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): this not be an issue in the trial? Well, we don't have a jury.
You can't have a mistrial
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): before you have a sworn jury.
Everything
Speaker 253: that's taking place now is really irrelevant when
it comes
Speaker 253: to the jury because we don't know what the judge is going
to let in.
And we
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): don't know what the motions in lemony were, and we don't know, you
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): know, are going, not were, are going to be because they're not, we haven't had them yet. And so it can't
be a
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): mistrial.
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): That's something that happens at trial. We're not at trial. If you're asking why isn't
Speaker 340: this thrown out
or whatever, it's
Speaker 340: because, you know, the judge has tremendous power to try to conduct a fair trial. Let's give
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): them an opportunity.
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): But Baron, congrats on becoming a granddad. My husband is
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Jermaine, a German, and I watch every
episode of
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): yours. God
bless you and
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): your family. Or is he a granddad that goes by Jermaine? Wasn't
that one of Michael
Speaker 341: Jackson's brothers, Jermaine? I
don't think it was
Speaker 32: spelled that way, but I think, wasn't that
one of
Speaker 32: the Jackson? Sitting here with my third grandbaby. There's no love
like a
Speaker 32: grandchild. Well,
figuring
Speaker 57: that out.
Random
Speaker 57: lady of the night would get more of an investigation than CK got because the government wouldn't know who did it and would need to find out. Yeah.
Speaker 342: 911. Ship's already there to take away the debris. Oh,
Speaker 343: 9-11. Oh, were they
Speaker 186: already there?
I haven't looked into
Speaker 186: that part.
There's a lot wrong
Speaker 186: with that.
Is
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): this the same construction you called who hung up? No, no, no, no, no. That
was a
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): different one. That was the division of facilities and construction management.
They did not
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): want to talk.
Granddad Baron,
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): we
Speaker 72: missed you. Glad you were able to take some time off with the missus.
And congrats
Speaker 72: again on your new grandbaby. You are blessed.
Christ is
Speaker 72: king indeed. Thank you. Thank you. I feel very blessed.
Speaker 11: Happy 25th.
Speaker 296: Congratulations on 300,000. Congrats on your first grandkid. What a month. May has been a month. I forgot the other one.
Speaker 296: I already forgot the 300 was in the month of May. Just 49 more
Speaker 194 (lower-pitched voice): to go. A 39. Let's not put too much pressure on the kids.
God bless you
Speaker 63: and your beautiful growing family.
Thank you.
Speaker 63: Congratulations on becoming a granddad. The tunnel where Princess Diana died was opened only four and a half hours after
Speaker 253: the crash. Seems ridiculously quick considering who she was.
Speaker 344: yeah but that was a traffic accident I mean I get that you can't shut off the
main
Speaker 160: artery forever shut it down for weeks that
I
Speaker 155: kind of get they didn't pave over the tunnel that'd be like them entombing the
tunnel
Speaker 78: in concrete we don't have a tunnel that's
more of
Speaker 78: the app comparison unfair to Gary Melton he made
Speaker 254: many helpful gaffes that is true that wasn't the only good thing he did it's
Speaker 76: a good point
and he
Speaker 76: blinks a lot gratis more far congratulations grandpa oh gratis indeed i didn't know what that
meant thank you it's a
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): menorah shaped area uvu how kabbalah yeah i call
it the
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): menorah because that's
Speaker 65: obviously what it looks like interesting how there seemed to be more detailed pictures of the cleanup than on 910 also a huge congratulations on being a granddad candace was cooking You're doing
it.
Speaker 65: While you were out, glad to have you back.
She
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): was, she was now Mrs. Coleman and I made a deal. We weren't going to be on social media and watching
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): YouTube videos
and podcasts
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): and all that.
Your humble host
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): might've sneaked
in a
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): little of the principle here and there, but I
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): was pretty
Speaker 345: good. Other than that, pretty good. Other than
that, just a
Speaker 345: few minutes here and there, particularly the Victor Marks thing. I had to
know, but yeah,
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): she was cooking.
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): Um, yeah, I'm very concerned by the lack of
Speaker 49: photography and videography on 910 itself, because I saw a lot of cameras up at
the moment
Speaker 49: of the big bang.
Speaker 209: And I see very few images
of it need paver
Speaker 160: emergency merge. Ah, that's a good one. Congratulations, granddad. God bless. Yes, that's
a great one. We
Speaker 160: do need paver emergency. We
have a paver emergency. You never
Speaker 160: know.
stay out
Speaker 266: of my curtains erica
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): you may sit on the couch but don't play my curtains yeah forgot about that she's
welcome to
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): come over but she may not play in the curtains curtains expensive you're messing up uh happy to
have you
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): back congrats
Speaker 35: on becoming grandparents it's wonderful lovely stage of life blessing to your daughter and new little family
take care julia uh well thank
Speaker 269: you julia
I always
Speaker 209: believed in God logically and wished I could feel it emotionally. I'm 35 years old after giving birth to my daughter who's nearing two years old. I feel it physically and feel I'm closer
Speaker 10: to God every day.
Speaker 237: Yeah. My wife
chastised me
Speaker 237: the other day. It was not St. John
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): of God who wrote Dark Night of the Soul. It was St. John of the Cross. Anyone going through a Dark Night of the Soul should
read about
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): it. It's amazing.
Puts it
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): very nicely. I knew it. I knew that my parents loved being grandparents more than being parents. I didn't get no
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): dang cookie every day. Congratulations, Grandpa Baron. Well, don't take it out on me. I was not your grandpa.
But I don't blame him. Love doesn't belong
Speaker 346: to any one religion or those without religion.
Speaker 347: Love belongs to everyone and can be felt by everyone. That's correct.
Speaker 27: But love, I believe, is evidence of a higher being,
Speaker 348: higher power.
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): Love is
not a collection of
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): electrons floating around in your brain. I mean, I
just, that's not love. Love is from the
Speaker 349: higher being. Congrats, B.
hold on oh my back
Speaker 292: end told me that YouTube crashed but it
does not look
Speaker 292: like it did I
got
Speaker 169: the big that happens when YouTube crashed
Speaker 321: congrats Barron for Super Chat just hearing
Speaker 2: you share the love for your first grandbaby pulled on my heart strings to want to give a little something to support your family may God bless you all thank you mama bear I don't
know.
Speaker 2: I love a good mama bear. That's good. Congrats, Morfar. I
Speaker 159: have 16 grandkids. That's a blessing. That is a blessing.
That is a
Speaker 22: blessing. Barbara Child's Coaching. I don't know what Child's Coaching is, but thank you for sharing
Speaker 76: that. 16, that's amazing. I
paid for
Speaker 76: 30 years in northeastern Nevada.
We
Speaker 10: contracted to the city of Elko.
Only once did we have
Speaker 10: an emergency job. Water break.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Throws a main street afoot. We paved it four days later. Monday.
Oh,
Speaker 233: Monday. I bet you meant Monday. Lunes. Lunes. Yeah, there's
no
Speaker 105: such thing
as a
Speaker 105: paver emergency. That's
not a
Speaker 105: thing, guys.
Just in case
Speaker 105: I wasn't clear about that, there
was no
Speaker 105: paver emergency.
There's no such thing
Speaker 105: as a paver emergency.
Speaker 105: I told you
Speaker 245: off subject, but I've listened to your show as I study since September. Love the faith, the vibes, the chat, the laughs. Just want to say I finally graduated this past Friday. Christ is king indeed.
Speaker 350: Congratulations on the family edition. Well, that is wonderful news. Noah, thank you for sharing that.
Glad we
Speaker 350: could get you to graduation.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): I
like to believe you
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): wouldn't have gotten there without us.
That's not true. You
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): sound like a bright
kid.
Speaker 294: Gary.
Can
Speaker 294: you imagine TR getting on his cell phone in jail and
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): coordinating the removal of soil at UVU to make sure that it was paved over by Monday? Oh, Lord, help
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): us, please. Christ is king indeed. Yeah, it's an evidence of a cover-up. Let's just be honest.
I have one
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): beautiful 20-month-old
Speaker 105: granddaughter. Couldn't wait to be called Grandma, but she calls me Gaga. I'll take it. So
here's my
Speaker 105: thought on that. I
bet you she can say Grandma
Speaker 105: today, right? Yeah.
Speaker 296: so make her say grandma that's my thought i don't think the baby's going to come out and say grandad is his first word or her first word but eventually
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): she'll be able to say it and i'm not i'm not getting stuck with some weirdo name but gaga's not weirdoing
i didn't
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): mean that in a bad way
but i mean no one speaks perfect with
Speaker 210: perfect diction right out of the womb
I'm going
Speaker 210: to be welcoming my very first grandbaby
Speaker 65: any day now. Your story about your own grandbaby brought tears to my eyes and inspired me to send you my very first Super Chat. Love you, Baron. Thank you. Alan, I'll
pray for you. Or
Speaker 317 (lower-pitched voice): Allie. Are you Allie in or, Alan? Either way, I'll pray for you because it's an experience. I was
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): not expecting it, to be honest with you.
We need an
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): APB on where the dirt was taken. Someone knows. Congratulations on the granddaughter. Christ is king indeed.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): yes yes yes yes yes yes um congratulations
Speaker 253: mr and mrs on your first grandchild prayers to your daughter as she begins this beautiful journey she's blessed to have you and mrs
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): coleman and family so close by yeah we're very close um we all live very near each other and she's
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): got a great grandmother very close
as well
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): so plenty of plenty of family right here
uh baron i heard
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): that up talk Yes.
I
Speaker 351: know it was tragic sorry we
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): feel like part of the family too congrats Granddad Baron Kristen thank you Critter I really appreciate that you are part of the family not like the TPUSA family we don't
we don't remove
Speaker 352: people from this family tales
old
Speaker 37: time FBI doing things without looping in C.I.
ah
Speaker 353: You're
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): welcome.
A worst
Speaker 37: communication can't get their story
Speaker 353: straight because each wants to be the large member.
Speaker 354: Yeah, maybe, maybe.
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): Congratulations. Thank you, Lazarus. I appreciate that. Very kind of you. Thank you. Grandchildren opened up a new chamber of your heart that you never knew
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): existed. It's a whole new love. Congratulations to your family. Crisis King. I'm a little concerned with this chamber business. I don't need any cardiac incidents.
the
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): heart is perfectly designed with its four chambers ventricles atria
Speaker 324: i don't need anything
else here
Speaker 324: we're uh
i don't yeah open up a new
Speaker 32: hole in the heart you may go throw a clot
or something
Speaker 32: uh glad you're back and congrats on your new baby grandkids are
the absolute best yes
Speaker 355: indeed yes indeed
Speaker 355: thank you
uh
Speaker 356: congrats on your baby having a beautiful baby congrats on your baby having a
beautiful baby
Speaker 50: holding your grandbaby is holding the future in your arms the legacy you are blessed to have and love there's something philosophical there
there's
Speaker 63: something there about like when you hold your kids that's that's you right you know spine responsibility race you hold your grandkid it's
Speaker 357: like this is the
future of the
Speaker 357: world right here it's wild
Speaker 179: congrats uncle b my meemaw is my whole world and i'm honored to be her primary caregiver nothing like that bond super happy for coleman fam's new chapter thank you thank
you um yeah there's something beautiful
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): about taking care of aging parents and grandparents i annoyed you
when i
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): said charlie was looking to catholicism so he could have an
Speaker 179: annulment or an exorcism wasn't trying to be mean i'm serious i
don't think
Speaker 179: that's mean
I don't
Speaker 193: think it's mean at all. We own a landscaping biz. We remove one inch
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): greater than the depth of the paver. You don't want to replace under with new soft soil. You set them on old packed dirt. And for stability, never
be a reason
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): to remove 10
Speaker 359: inches. Well,
that's what I'm
Speaker 359: told they remove.
How big
Speaker 359: is a paver? Two or three inches? I mean, they're not small.
Congratulations,
Speaker 326: Baron and Pham. When I saw this interview while you were away, I was like, OMG.
Speaker 326: Barron's going to be all over this. Keep
Speaker 294: going, Max, Christ is king indeed. You talking about the interview with the paver? Yeah, I was. I was.
Speaker 33: Moon got us. I hope you're doing well. FBI guilty of planning
Speaker 360: the assassinations. Notice how she dropped the G. That's because we're family.
You don't
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): have to use fancy G's at the end of your words here. No.
No.
Speaker 179: Participle gerund, just throw that G in the trash. We don't need it.
Speaker 179: Guilty of planning the assassination. That's
how
Speaker 72: we do it here. We planning.
Being a
Speaker 72: grandfather is wonderful. I'm waiting for number four in the next two weeks. Congratulations, Baron, and love
Speaker 222: to your family. Thank you. I appreciate that. Cash doesn't strike me as a landscaper. Maybe stoned, Mason.
Speaker 43: Congrats,
Speaker 361: J-L-Y. Oh, Jesus loves you, Grandpa.
Thank you.
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, I don't
think Cash does a
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): lot of manual labor.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): It's not really his thing.
Cox
Speaker 49: and data centers and Romney influence. Oh, my. Tim Ballard wants Romney's job, then immediately accused of crimes. Suspicious.
Speaker 27: David A. Nielsen, LDS Church Charity, billion-dollar scandal, whistleblower, connected. I don't know about that last sentence, but the first
Speaker 363: sentence makes a lot of sense to me. Yeah.
Glad to have you
Speaker 364: back, Grandpa.
Blessings upon
Speaker 365: blessings. Blessings,
Speaker 366: blessings.
May I
Speaker 365: ask your denomination?
Speaker 49: I'm a baby Christian learning Catholic-Protestant differences. I want to start going to church. Don't know where to go. Any advice? Insight?
Christ is
Speaker 49: king. Eternal. Indeed. I'm Catholic. My advice is go where you feel comfortable and loved and study and learn
about
Speaker 179: your faith.
Talk
Speaker 367: to
Speaker 179: people and pray. That's my advice.
Go love on
Speaker 368: Jesus.
Go
Speaker 368: follow, follow the commandments.
That's what he said. If you love my
Speaker 369: father, you follow his commandments. The Bourbon Street New Year's Eve mass
murderer had a
Speaker 369: reporter walking
Speaker 72: around his apartment about two days later. Crime scenes is suspicious.
Speaker 179: Murder is recently not very sanitized. You know, that's funny you mentioned that. I forgot about that. She was in his apartment just wandering around
Speaker 370: grabbing stuff. I remember that. I forgot all about that.
What a weird day
Speaker 257: that was.
What a
Speaker 257: weird story that was.
Hey,
Speaker 257: Barron, can we talk about Burt
Speaker 63: Coffin, an 85-year-old Navy veteran
Speaker 305: in Florida working Uber Eats to pay off medical death? Google his name, has a GoFundMe. I've
never
Speaker 371: heard of him. Sounds tragic, though.
Why would a Navy veteran have access
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): to the VA
if it was
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): going to be expensive? I don't
know how
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): that works. But yeah, thank you for bringing that up. Congrats, great, Ed.
Way
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): back when EK took a year off, wasn't she with someone named Eileen Victor's
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): bride, perhaps? I don't know who she
Speaker 39: was with.
That's the first
Speaker 39: I've heard a name attached to it.
But yeah, I've
Speaker 39: wondered that. To
pick our battles, I can find
Speaker 39: agreement on public
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): crime scene being photographed, collected, and et cetera, and then cleaned up quickly.
Class was due
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): back on Monday, but method and lack of planning is odd.
You can clean
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): up a crime scene without tearing out 10 inches of dirt and
Speaker 372 (lower-pitched voice): paving over it.
Like
Speaker 373: there's a happy, that's the fallacy of the excluded middle.
It's in this book here. You don't have to give
Speaker 374: me two extreme options.
Leave crime
Speaker 86: scene alone, totally destroy it. There's, there's, there's middle ground there. And if you exclude the middle, that's a fallacy, a logical fallacy. I
had a data breach after my
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): first super chat last week. I live in AK with a PA number and the call started at 5 0 1 AM.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): uh i hope they weren't related i've not heard that from anyone
Speaker 253: else but i'm sorry that happened to you
my new
Speaker 253: mug idea i'll pull good for dogs not for humans yeah yeah
uh congrats
Speaker 253: granddad she'll be high IQ as you one day we missed you oh she'll be very high IQ i can assure you
that fbi isn't
Speaker 65: finding donna mitchell from hope indiana
either
Speaker 65: Missing same month, county highway dig on boyfriend's property, still unchecked six years
Speaker 49: later. Crisis king indeed. I've
been to
Speaker 49: Hope,
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): Indiana. There's a cool pizza place in Hope, Indiana. I used to eat there called Pizza King.
Yeah, the
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): Pizza King
in Hope,
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): Indiana on Highway 9, State Highway 9, a great area.
Speaker 237: I
had a
Speaker 237: cousin that lived in Hope.
I want to say
Speaker 237: their high school was like the Jets or something right there. I can't remember. Dan
is lying when
Speaker 237: he says he doesn't know the
Speaker 65: name of the guy who did the excavation. Video from CC, November 11, TS, 10, 17 minutes. Edward Thomas left Dan a glorious Google review for
his help with
Speaker 375: the paver. Oh,
the guy's name was
Speaker 375: Edward Thomas.
Speaker 375: Well, maybe he didn't know at that
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): time of the interview. Or maybe he's lying, and he's a lying liar who lies. I don't know. I'm
not telling you
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): what to think. I'm just telling you my
Speaker 155: thoughts.
Where did you
Speaker 155: get the papers on
the
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): weekend with delivery? Who ordered them and when? Usually delivery takes more than
a day
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): to get in the schedule. Sounds like they went to Lowe's, picked them up themselves,
and then took them
Speaker 23 (lower-pitched voice): back, the ones they didn't use.
Speaker 17: Excavation depth to remove the explosive residue from grass and soil is six inches.
For
Speaker 179: recent surface deposited energetic residue, this is the firing rate standard, but greater with time, weather, etc. Well, that's interesting. I
did not know that. I totally
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): believe you, but I didn't know that. But bear on, I used to own a construction
Speaker 35: company. We only demoed out eight inches of dirt to pour back in concrete for roadways.
Congrats on
Speaker 35: granddad, crisis king indeed.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Well, they do 10 inches for crime scene cover.
Speaker 96: Congratulations, Grandpa Baron. Thank you for all
Speaker 105: praying a few weeks ago for me. Found an apartment and a job, too. Praise God. Christ is king indeed. Chat
Speaker 376: while
I drink tea. That's an interesting
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): username. Congratulations, and thank you for sharing that with us. Shawnee. Guess who's back?
Speaker 8: Shawnee's back. Thank you, Shawnee. Happy anniversary.
Speaker 51: Congratulations to the newly minted granddad and grandma.
Very
Speaker 51: best wishes and blessings to you on the first
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): of many grandchildren.
Your riches
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): beyond measure in this life, Shani.
Thank
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): you very, very much. Always so kind and has
a knack
Speaker 377: with your words as well.
Yeah, many,
Speaker 377: the first
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): of many grandchildren. Children, are you watching this? I don't know if the Coleman kids are watching, but if you're watching,
what Shani's
Speaker 214: saying here is very important. Pay attention, pay attention.
Speaker 65: Agreed. I think it's a while you're out here.
I don't know
Speaker 65: what that means.
Congrats
Speaker 27: on 25 years and becoming your granddad and 300,000 subs. Cheering emoji. Still
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): laughing about daughter Daisy. Love the show and community. Crisis King. Indeed, you would be surprised how many of those emails I get. I
Speaker 378: completely
get
Speaker 76: it. Just had my first granddaughter five
and a half
Speaker 76: weeks ago. Amazing. Congratulations. Or that could be, I
Speaker 209: guess, 51 over two weeks ago, which would be, what, 26 and three quarters? I'll
Speaker 27: see you
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): next
Speaker 137: week.
Or
Speaker 209: 25 and three quarters weeks ago? That's probably five and a half. But thank
Speaker 27: you. Thank you. As evil as CK's muck duck was, it brought millions to Jesus. It did not pass away in vain
because
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): the response to evil was a divine
Speaker 137: recruitment of people committed to truth and justice to fight evil. I will
Speaker 32: admit
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): there's been some sort of a resurgence in the church lately.
all
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): churches, not just one denomination or another. I mean, Christianity's on the
Speaker 222: comeback.
Could be the contractor
Speaker 222: has an account with certain suppliers, subs, or Home Depot Lowe's. I do construction defect. I think we can figure that out. I think we figured it out. It was Lowe's.
They probably chose
Speaker 222: Lowe's for the
Speaker 27: pavers due to likely having enough stock and being open on Sunday since wholesalers wouldn't be.
Christ is
Speaker 27: king indeed. Another reason not to do the job on Sunday. Wait till Monday.
Or
Speaker 27: don't pave over
Speaker 379: the crime scene. Greatest
man I
Speaker 379: ever knew was my granddad. I
hope my granddaughter
Speaker 380: says that.
I'll have to get
Speaker 381: started on
being a
Speaker 381: better person. I
Speaker 382: also think
Speaker 324: it's odd they just bought even upturn in the market. Too much going on to sell and move. They weren't hurting for money. No, they weren't at all. And
now that he's
Speaker 11: dead, she's building a house.
Hello,
Speaker 219: Baron. Welcome back, and congratulations, Granddad. Regarding the red pavers and red fence,
Speaker 137: school colors, rivalries.
Speaker 383: Oh, I didn't even think about that. I
didn't even think
Speaker 137: about the University of Utah being red. I guess they wouldn't want blue either, but who does blue pavers? That's
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): weird. Baron,
if they bought tiles
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): at 430, but the guy couldn't get a hold of his guys all Sunday, when did they look at the site or actually start?
Great
Speaker 285: question.
I kind
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): of took it to mean he got called in the morning and then he got a crew together and by mid-afternoon they were out there examining. Congrats, granddad, lucky man, former paver, current
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): human here. If I got that call, I'd have made a YouTube channel instantly blowing that whistle ASAP.
Yeah. Death,
Speaker 191: divorce, disease, and debt for a new house.
Yeah. I forgot to
Speaker 384: add debt. I should have added
that.
When
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): Barron wears his dressy vans, then he wears his wedding ring. Oh, can I tell you something? My daughter
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): commented, I wore my dress vans to the delivery. It was that kind of an
Speaker 370: experience. I wanted to look good. I
can't meet my
Speaker 370: granddaughter in old beat-up vans. I had to wear the dress
vans, and
Speaker 370: I did, and
they looked
Speaker 370: great. I
was
Speaker 296: fancy. I was fancy. I was walking up and down the halls of the hospital. People were noticing, are those dress vans?
Those
Speaker 78: suede vans? Oh,
Speaker 32: yeah, they were.
A
Speaker 32: explosive residue would contaminate clothes of those handling Charlie and cause skin burns, irritation. Frank Turk said they quickly changed into scrubs due to being covered
Speaker 219: in blood. I don't believe them. I don't believe him either.
No, I don't. He's a
Speaker 219: liar. He's been caught many times lying. I don't see a man like CK, newly
Speaker 254: married with babies, going for divorce if it was just infidelity. Odd text the night before, didn't mention EK.
I don't
Speaker 294: know that it was infidelity. I mean, it might have just been tired of being looked at with those eyes.
Did you move
Speaker 385: the ketchup off
of the
Speaker 385: second shelf in the fridge? Can
you
Speaker 386: imagine? Terrifying. As
Speaker 387: far as the
text the night
Speaker 387: before, I don't
Speaker 253: know about Erica's component.
Speaker 253: professionalism, professional concrete masons, et cetera, have actual accounts with big concrete companies like the guys that show up
with a
Speaker 253: concrete truck.
They don't use
Speaker 253: credit
Speaker 213: cards. They have charge accounts. Well, if they're doing it
on Sunday at Lowe's, they do six of them
Speaker 213: last
Speaker 65: podcast from his home office. He looked to his left and had an angry look. The divorce rumor makes sense to me. Seemed as if he was looking at someone.
Speaker 388: Yeah.
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): uh good question here stacy mikey eliza in that condo complex yeah among the others among others
Speaker 389: um
congrats on the new grandbaby
Speaker 179: listening tonight it dawned on me how interesting a convo between you and charlie would have been i think it would have been
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): interesting i never met him uh i think it would have been
interesting i would have been
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): uh thrilled to have that conversation
Baron,
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): our children have gone no contact with us, which is an epidemic right now for parents and grandparents. We're cut off from 13 of our sweet grandchildren
Speaker 390: asking
for the
Speaker 390: Baronite family to pray for us. Christ is king indeed. Why is that an epidemic? That's
the first time I'm
Speaker 390: hearing this. Are
people cutting off
Speaker 77: their parents? Like not talking to them?
Why? I'm very sorry to
Speaker 224: hear that.
I can't
Speaker 224: imagine what that feels like, and I'm sorry to hear that.
I'll pray
Speaker 224: for you.
A grammar
Speaker 326: request, government records access management account. I got government
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): records right. I just didn't know what the Access and Management Act was. Formal request used in Utah to access government
Speaker 11: public records. It's the state-level equivalent of the FOIA. Yeah, I knew that part. I just didn't know what it stood for. Thank you. Salon. Thank you.
Speaker 49: Lord, bless and keep you. The Lord make his face shine upon you and be gracious to you. The Lord turn his face towards you and give you peace. Lord, let this blessing
Speaker 287 (lower-pitched voice): rest upon this newborn grandchild forever. Amen. Oh, beautiful. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Can't
Speaker 293 (lower-pitched voice): pray enough for my family. Nor
can we pray enough
Speaker 293 (lower-pitched voice): for your family.
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): Well, thank you.
Thank you. But bear
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): on this one's for the amazing Daisy. Thank God for Daisy. Yes, she does a great job.
It
Speaker 255 (lower-pitched voice): was a great job.
I hope she enjoyed
Speaker 391: her week off.
I didn't ask
Speaker 372 (lower-pitched voice): her. Daisy, did you enjoy your week off? I truly enjoyed not
only your
Speaker 372 (lower-pitched voice): content, but your humor and honesty. Bring it home for me. Thank you, Crisis King indeed. Thank
Speaker 392: you. Thank you. I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Speaker 393: Thank you, Michelle, my bill.
Or is it,
Speaker 394: well, well, well, my Michelle.
Speaker 394: That's Guns N' Roses for you uninitiated.
Speaker 222: Congrats, Granddad, on your new blessing. That compare list is so sad to me. In the past, I've had to do those in different types of relationships. I
was wearing my dress
Speaker 63: pants. I'll
Speaker 253: be the first to admit it. Baron, sorry if this has been discussed, but UVU being a public university would be subject to FOIA. Could request related communication.
Speaker 222: Those...
Those
Speaker 222: requests have already been filled. That's where I got the text message. Somebody had filed a grammar request.
That's the state
Speaker 222: equivalent. We just discussed
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): that. They actually wouldn't be subject to FOIA. That's a federal request. But most states have their own sunshine version. A
lot of
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): states, you have to be a citizen of the state. And so you'd have to find someone in Utah to do it.
But that's
Speaker 160: new, the blank, the weapon.
and or
Speaker 160: divorce was imminent, so wanted power of attorney in case it wasn't clean.
Speaker 210: Ugh.
It was worth
Speaker 210: more.
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): Oh, unalive to her for the money and attention.
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): Couldn't keep up facade. Won fame, money, freedom. Yeah, that list sounded like a list about her. If I mean, the list on the right-hand side of the screen that I showed sounded like her.
Congrats, Baron
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): and Fam.
Charlie
Speaker 65: Kirk's last public interview with that foodie.
Speaker 65: convention in the morning at 9 10 the speaker asked him wife kids
charlie kirk
Speaker 65: replies kids yeah i found out very telling
oh i
Speaker 30: didn't
Speaker 52: catch that i'm gonna have to go back and watch that make a note of that daisy let's go find that christ is king indeed that's interesting
but bear on this one's for the
Speaker 52: amazing nurse lindsey
who's
Speaker 395: nurse lindsey
Speaker 396: nurse casey christ is king
Speaker 260: indeed i'll allow it
you change my sister's name
Speaker 260: that's okay
i'm sure
Speaker 260: she's been called worse things
today when becoming a
Speaker 260: parent one is
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): overwhelmed by the love balanced by enormous responsibility by contrast being a grandparent is all love for me that's the
Speaker 27: difference prayerful congratulations thank you i think that has a lot
to do with it
Speaker 27: because you're
Speaker 397: like oh it's so wonderful here
you walk away drive home seem to recall
Speaker 398: that charlie texted someone said it's over
everyone always thought
Speaker 398: it was the israel
cause but i
Speaker 398: always thought it meant their marriage.
Maybe
Speaker 253: that's what he meant by no choice but to leave the pro-Israel clause. Maybe his wife was the pro-Israel. I
Speaker 328: kid, I
Speaker 253: think.
I kid, I think. I think I kid. Erica
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): also has another countdown where she and Charlie were walking together holding hands. She said nothing happens by coincidence.
Thank you for sharing family's joy
Speaker 209: with us tonight, including us and this precious Coleman family.
Speaker 209: First, in allowing us to celebrate with you all, you created a very special place here and we're all better for it. Thank you and congrats.
Yeah, this
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): place is incredibly special.
It
Speaker 399: really
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): is.
Speaker 253: I'm telling you, I knew it was special because in my old jobs,
when I
Speaker 253: would take a week off, I was
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): dread going back to work
and I
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): could not wait to get back in here and talk to you.
Like, I
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): couldn't wait.
And I
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): never, in an old job, if I took three or four
days off,
I would
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): have sat around missing it. I'd have been like, oh, finally, a day I don't have to
do
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): anything. I missed it every day. Like,
I kept
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): thinking, I could go live
Speaker 400: from this room. I'm
sure Mrs.
Speaker 400: Coleman would love that. She'd come back from sunning and be like, what are you doing? I'd be like,
Speaker 401: nothing.
Nothing at
Speaker 400: all. I'm
certainly
Speaker 402: not going live,
Speaker 403: talking to the grand jury. Certainly not.
Ah, let's see
Speaker 404: here. Let's see here.
Speaker 404: checks
all
Speaker 405: right congratulations
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): granddad
difference between
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): kids and grandkids is the feeling you would
hurt someone
Speaker 160: that would hurt your kid but you would burn the city down for your grandbaby new grandma here
well okay
Speaker 222: okay
uh
Speaker 222: there's a video by joseph tittle
where he
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): channeled uh i don't channel i don't channel i don't do that uh felicidades
e bendy can't read that
Speaker 407: oh bend
is
Speaker 233: the honest congratulations and blessings christ is king indeed yeah sorry
i can
Speaker 233: barely do english at that size
the uh in
Speaker 76: espanol at that size
No hablo. No
Speaker 349: hablo muy bien, anyway. Not at that size. What if they
sold the
Speaker 408: house for downsizing?
Charlie
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): Kirk knew he was losing donors, and this is where issues with marriage started. He
did not
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): need to downsize for money. That was not the reason
for the downside. Thank
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): you, Sandorian.
All
Speaker 65: just clicked. I wonder if they were signing divorce papers. Everything else makes sense. She acted like a woman who was miserably married and relieved.
That's kind of what I
Speaker 65: was wondering.
Speaker 409: I'm not suggesting it. I'm not saying it. I'm not stating it as fact.
But I
Speaker 410: wonder now, putting
it all
Speaker 65: together, I wonder, do
we know what
Speaker 65: the caption on her countdown post said? Congrats on grand fatherhood,
Speaker 411: Baron.
Christ
Speaker 412: is king indeed. Yeah.
It
Speaker 412: said, oh,
hold
Speaker 413: on. I got to move this out. It
Speaker 41: said, I wanted to make sure you were the first.
Maybe that's when she went and told
Speaker 414: her.
Speaker 415: Interesting,
Speaker 51: interesting. B, B.
Speaker 51: A few months back, you posted a vague pic of
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): Erica with an arm full of bracelets and said you had a theory on it and we'll talk about it soon. Never heard your
theory on it or
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): refresh my
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): memory, please. Oh, yeah, I kind of skipped. I'll tell you, but I skipped it out of politeness more than anything.
So here's my
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): theory is with all the jewelry.
And ladies, don't take
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): this wrong if you like a lot of jewelry.
this has
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): just been my experience. People who
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): wear a lot of jewelry are very insecure people, in my opinion. That's
just the
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): people I've met. Maybe it's
Speaker 53: not true across the board. But they're hiding behind the massive rings. It's like they're covering themselves up.
That's been my
Speaker 82: experience with people who wear a ton of jewelry. And she wears a lot.
A
Speaker 82: whole
Speaker 334: lot. B. Oh, that was the same one. Has
Speaker 237: Daisy looked for divorce filing? 90-day waiting period. Minimum is norm from original file date to finalized. I know, three times divorce, at least in Washington. It is. Moon
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): Goddess, I don't think such evidence exists. I'm
confident
Speaker 416: that would have been uncovered by now.
Speaker 155: Congratulations, Mr. and Mrs. Coleman. Grandchildren are an extraordinary blessing, and may you continue
to be blessed
Speaker 155: beyond measure with many, many extensions
Speaker 160: to your family free. Christ
is king
Speaker 160: indeed. Yeah, we want lots of limbs. I
want limbs
Speaker 160: and branches and
Speaker 417: twigs. Limbs, branches, and twigs.
Speaker 417: and leaves
and little
Speaker 417: flowers. I want a family tree that flowers,
Speaker 210: something beautiful. Like a dogwood. Guys, make me a dogwood. You
were really
Speaker 294: missed, Baron. Next, the divorce angle makes sense as to why Erica would have to create the illusion that Charlie wanted her to take over.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Turning point, because that would be the last wish he'd have.
Yeah, I
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): don't think for a second he wanted her to take over.
Did they
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): maybe sell at a buyer while building a new home and moved into a condo between sale and completion of a new home?
Congrats on
Speaker 105: Grant, baby. I have seen no personal evidence they started
building
Speaker 246 (lower-pitched voice): a home before he passed, but I could
be wrong. You're not going to
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): believe this, but when I saw this video, I was like, OMG, she's literally crying real tears over giving her paycheck. Yes. The
first real tears
Speaker 419: I've seen her cry.
Speaker 420: Like, she got so choked
Speaker 421: up she couldn't talk. When's the last time that happened?
I've never
Speaker 421: seen it.
Literally never
I think the
Speaker 347: comparison list was more of an example of what
I wanted
Speaker 347: versus what I got.
The look of regret on
Speaker 347: Erica's face after she realized
Speaker 9: what she'd read aloud said it all. Oh,
Speaker 422: my goodness. I think
you might be on to something. Here's what
Speaker 106: I was looking for.
Here's what I got. Wow. What did
Speaker 423: it say between Erica's fingers on the list? Well, let
me go back
Speaker 424: and look.
Here it
Speaker 425: is. Between her fingers. I don't
Speaker 426: know. Pfft.
Speaker 426: something some parenthetical
Speaker 427: reference though but
i can't i can't
Speaker 427: read it maybe 60 61 are those sixes i don't
know that's a good question you people
Speaker 11: are sharp
uh in
Speaker 11: the clip of erica in office holding ck's list she
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): wasn't wearing wedding ring unless it's a mirror image if that makes sense no she wasn't
No, she
Speaker 284: wasn't.
And
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): it's not a mirrored image because you can tell the hats and the football that says ducks are going in the correct angle.
Yeah.
Speaker 429 (lower-pitched voice): No, no.
She also mentioned a letter
Speaker 429 (lower-pitched voice): for his daughter for the future. He knew he wouldn't be
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): around.
Congratulations on becoming a
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): grandfather. Your family is so lucky to have you. I truly think you're amazing.
We
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): missed you.
Speaker 430: Well, thank you.
Thank
Speaker 431: you. I
Speaker 214: appreciate that.
That's very kind
Speaker 214: of you.
Oh,
Speaker 27: those are kind words. Congratulations, Morphar. I'm doing my best out here. Proverbs chapter 13, verse
Speaker 159: 22. I will
look that up, just
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): in case you're insulting me.
I don't
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): want to let an insult go without getting back at you. Matlis, if that is your real name.
Speaker 432: Checking. We are checking. That's a Formula One
Speaker 158: reference for you people. The good leave an inheritance to their children's children.
But the
Speaker 32: wealth of the sinner is,
is
Speaker 32: stored up for the just.
You put a lot
Speaker 433: of pressure on me, sir.
Put
Speaker 33: a lot of pressure on me to leave an inheritance. Glad you had a great vacation. Congrats on the grandbaby. Glad to have you back. Well, thank you. Very kind. Short to the point. Very kind. If
Daisy were
Speaker 209: to marry one of your sons, she could give birth to a future Coleman grandbaby and glow accordingly at that time?
Speaker 434: Well, that's a lot of ifs there.
Speaker 435: daisy what say you no she's already married you know
i don't think that
Speaker 194 (lower-pitched voice): would work very well
that would
Speaker 194 (lower-pitched voice): require more than one spouse and i'm not sure that's that's a thing
uh but
Speaker 194 (lower-pitched voice): thank you thank you thank you
uh thank
Speaker 194 (lower-pitched voice): you meme
hi my b she's got my
Speaker 304: high q outfit shirt was so excited inspired me to take a shower today
please
Speaker 27: don't forget you promised us that deep dive into Dr. Kirk's nose. I
Speaker 76: did not forget. I was looking at
Speaker 436: it while I was on vacation.
Speaker 4: Encouraged
you to take a
Speaker 4: shower, Ashley?
Speaker 104: A regular bathe should be part of your routine. You shouldn't have to get a new shirt for that. But
I will
Speaker 257: allow it.
Ha ha ha.
I
Speaker 257: don't forget the photo of Charlie in his office the night before where he looked mad and it looked like he was giving someone the
Speaker 437: stink eye. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I saw that.
I saw
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): that. I'm losing my mind anymore with the uptalk. My CIO up talks. Thanks B. Thanks B.
Speaker 438: Yeah.
Speaker 253: The uptalk is getting out of control. I, I know she's working on it too. She, when she talks now, you can see her. She's like,
Speaker 439: don't talk up at the end, end,
Speaker 440: end.
She's working
Speaker 440: on it. She's working on it. I say she because the picture of her holding that letter is
still up on my left. This is a good
Speaker 440: opportunity. Here,
Speaker 441: let me show you something. I shouldn't do this. Every
part
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): of me right now is saying don't do this, but I'm about to. So
you guys wonder what
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): I'm talking about with the knuckles?
That's what I'm
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): talking about.
like
Speaker 340: your upper finger should not be bigger than your, like this part, this first part of your knuckle here, this first, this first part of the digit shouldn't be larger than this part here. The finger should
not be shaped
Speaker 53: like a cone. That's, that's, that's, I shouldn't have done
that. I
Speaker 442: should have done that.
You know how
Speaker 154: many people just look down and went, what are
you talking about? That's,
I didn't want
Speaker 443: to be the one to say it,
but here we
Speaker 443: are. You tune in because
Speaker 444: I don't BS you. I'll just tell you the truth. Did
you see the
Speaker 444: interview Charlie did, which he named the pros and cons list verbatim? Seems
like it
Speaker 444: was notes for a show. No, I didn't see that. I would love to see that.
Speaker 65: Congratulations, and welcome back. And my brother in Christ, we missed you and love your work and show. Christ is king indeed. P.S., we've got a postscript, ladies and
Speaker 245: gentlemen. Tune
Speaker 19: in.
Stop
Speaker 19: what you're doing.
This is a
Speaker 19: donation towards your diaper fund.
Oh, I'm not
Speaker 296: buying diapers. That's her business. Hope you don't
think I'm
Speaker 296: buying the diapers. No, I'm just here to hold the baby. That's her baby. She can
Speaker 213: buy her own diapers.
No, I'll buy some
Speaker 213: diapers. Isn't that what grandparents do? You're supposed to buy diapers occasionally. Congratulations on your
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): anniversary. Many blessings to your beautiful granddaughter, Grandpop Baron. Thank you, Denise.
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): and thank you want to glorify God both you very kind very kind a big congrats
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): to your family
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): you're the class I never could find a college I learned so much you
know what I found
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): when I went to law school it
was the first time like I had a few classes in
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): college this way where I really dug in and and just loved it I loved the professor I love the material I
but it
Speaker 49: wasn't until I went to law school where it was pretty much every class was that. I loved my professors, almost all of them universally. There
were a
Speaker 49: couple of duds here and there, but
most of
Speaker 49: them I adored.
And I
Speaker 49: love the material. I
Speaker 209: love the way the classes were structured. I hated homework. So I loved that there wasn't any, it
was just
Speaker 338: like, Hey, and I don't know if you guys have been to law school, but, and I don't know if they're still structured this way, but
when I
Speaker 338: went 20 plus years ago,
you
Speaker 49: got one grade you took one test and that was your grade for the semester um
so if it's a four-hour class you
Speaker 13: like went monday tuesday thursday friday or monday tuesday wednesday thursday
and you you
Speaker 287 (lower-pitched voice): were there for an hour and you watched and you participated and they they give you suggested readings and it was very smart if you would do it it would help you obviously pay attention
and
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): know what's
going on but
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): no one checked you know if you didn't do it whatever. I
did my
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): homework. I never missed class. Like I was a good student.
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): Um, but
there were people
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): who didn't and they did fine. They got good grades because it was all down to the last test
Speaker 13: and you
would take a test and your
Speaker 13: test usually roughly was the number of hours of your class. So if you
had a
Speaker 13: four hour class, it was a four hour final exam and you would show up and it was all, I don't know what it is today, but it was all handwritten in books. Like
you would like no
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): multiple choice, no true, false, just all essay.
and you
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): would fill up two, three, four of those blue books, and I don't know, they have eight or ten pages each, so you'd write a lot over the course of three or four hours. And that was your grade.
There were no
Speaker 209: quizzes. There were no tests. There were no pop quizzes. There were no homework assignments that got graded. There was no busy work. It was like, we're going to be studying these pages tomorrow in class. I hope you're
prepared
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): and have read them before we show up. If not, pay attention.
And then at
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): the end of the semester, you sat down and took a test, and that was your grade. And I loved it. I loved it. The responsibility is on you. Pay attention. Their
wedding photo
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): was removed
Speaker 429 (lower-pitched voice): from Charlie Kirk's office in Mikey's video. Missed RBP this week. Welcome back. Christ
is king
Speaker 429 (lower-pitched voice): indeed. Thank you.
Can you please
Speaker 209: explain why Charlie's honorary doctorate doesn't make him Dr. Charlie, but
Speaker 82: Dr. Eric, I'm confused. Congrats on Bubba Coleman.
I
Speaker 82: don't think she's really Dr. Eric. I just call her that.
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): Congrats, more far from a far, far. Hope the email was useful. Is
this where
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): I tell you I haven't checked emails in a while? I
Speaker 95: will maybe look at some of them. One lucky little girl to call you granddad. Enjoy this
Speaker 294: experience and prayers for your family always. Thank
you for
Speaker 294: sharing your life with us. Christ is king indeed. Yeah, I might overshare at times and I might have overshared a little bit tonight. I might get...
Speaker 294: yelled at when I get off here. I'll
just
Speaker 445: say, hey, this is a grand jury. It's not like I'm just telling just anybody.
First time
Speaker 65: Super
Speaker 11: Chat. Honor the new life and also because now I can listen to you again on my long run tomorrow. The Spotify shows keep me going, Max. Ah, it'll
be up in the morning. Count on it.
Speaker 190: Anyone, if you guys ever
miss a
Speaker 190: show, Spotify is great. It's
a
Speaker 446: great platform and if you
uh,
If
Speaker 446: you, yeah, it's great.
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): I don't know anything. They've been great partners. They're great people. I've really enjoyed being on their platform. Anyone following CK and EK before
Speaker 209: knows how intentional he was when he left their house. EK even said on stage at that Grapevine Texas talk, he just grabs me and he's like one minute
Speaker 126: before he leaves. Not
that day
Speaker 126: he wasn't.
Welcome
Speaker 126: back. Welcome to the Grandparent Club, Baron and Mrs. Baron. You
might be offended by
Speaker 126: that. She's
Speaker 213: Mrs. Coleman. So happy you're back. I got mad at my husband for interrupting me listening to you. Headphones on.
Said I've
Speaker 213: been waiting all week for this.
Sir, settle down. The show's on. She'll be done
Speaker 224: in a few hours.
It
Speaker 447: happens to
the
Speaker 32: best of us.
Congrats, new
Speaker 32: grandpa. Love it. Yes, yes, yes. I do as well.
Speaker 32: Baron, the list in CK's office was from a Fox hit
Speaker 49: with Laura Ingram right before going to Utah.
Videos on
Speaker 49: YouTube. I'll try to find that. Thank you. It doesn't change the fact that it exists.
There was
Speaker 49: speculation of
Speaker 137: the D word. So early on, I wonder how many things will come full circle. Certainly interesting.
What do
Speaker 137: you think? Who do you
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): think was leaving? Well, I don't even know that anyone was leaving. I'm just adding it up and it kind of looks like it to me, but it's a speculation. Conjecture.
What do you
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): think
Speaker 10: about the Fox mask dude? That's the psychoist story I've ever seen.
That dude was
Speaker 211: 100% wearing a mask and no one will ever convince me otherwise. And I want to know why. I don't know why someone would wear a silicone mask of themselves. Himself. I'm
weirded out
Speaker 211: by it. I don't like it. I'm wondering now who else wears masks on TV. Why do
Speaker 209: people wear masks? I'm...
I
Speaker 209: don't like it.
We filled my
Speaker 209: parents' home with eight
Speaker 237: grandchildren to celebrate the holidays. And
I pray my husband
Speaker 237: and I are blessed with a family tradition of many children for generations to come. Congratulations.
Just Jessica,
Speaker 237: that's beautiful. That
Speaker 190: truly is beautiful. And I hope
Speaker 285: that, I hope
it comes
Speaker 285: true for you. I do.
Speaker 449: AP report quotes AK that the majority of CK's
Speaker 65: annual earnings was from Charlie Kirk's show.
She's
Speaker 65: got to have big money if she's donating back salary. Speculating a truth social, Salem, Daily Wire, M&A,
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): largest conservative media company, maybe she's in if so.
She's got
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): plenty of
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): money.
She's got plenty of
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): money. She's not worried about money.
I mean,
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): don't cry
for her,
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): Argentina.
Speaker 77: Might be watching as we speak
Speaker 237: or she, I didn't mean to speculate. Card red
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): penalty. Please smash that like fam. Let's get
the goat to
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): 20,000 tonight. A
lot of other
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): things going on there. Thank you. Thank you. Very kind of you.
Did you see
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): Alex Clark trying to come for Candace over the weekend on
Speaker 452: X and embarrassing herself? Yes, she does that often.
she's
Speaker 209: tragic. I'm so sick of these E-trad girls who are not trad girls at all.
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): Like, I don't mind an E-girl who's a trad girl who's a real trad girl. But
trying to play one, I
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): mean, come on.
Amy
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): Cologne, thank
Speaker 11: you. Congrats, mate. Sending huge hugs to your entire family. Exciting times ahead. See, I said mate.
Speaker 11: That's because I speak Australian sometimes. A few words, un poco.
But, but,
Speaker 11: but, but,
Speaker 33: granddad, congrats. That actually
made me laugh. Thank you. That
Speaker 33: actually made
Speaker 7: me laugh. Thank you. Hey, granddad, congrats. On the wedding photo subject, we want to know who Charlie was looking at when he was interviewed in his home office, where he looks off to the camera at someone angrily.
Was it
Speaker 7: EK? We don't know.
I don't
Speaker 293 (lower-pitched voice): think we know. I
think
Speaker 454: there's been speculation of
a few different people,
Speaker 454: but we don't know. I also thought the CO
Speaker 211: interview was weird and thought it was odd to dig her claws into the cat story of all things. I love her, but that was weird and
a little
Speaker 211: off. No,
I
Speaker 455: understood, but that
part didn't bother
Speaker 213: me at all. And I didn't have many problems at all with the Victor Marks interview. I didn't have a problem necessarily with the Hunter Biden interview. I
Speaker 222: just, I'm not a big Hunter Biden fan because of the corruption. Like,
I feel bad he was a
Speaker 222: crackhead. And it was interesting hearing
I
Speaker 222: mean, it personalized him. It was very effective for that purpose. But
I just look
Speaker 222: at Hunter
Speaker 179: Biden. I'm like, you know, your corruption sort of paved the way for what we're seeing now
with the new
Speaker 179: president's family, and I don't like it.
But the digging the claws into
Speaker 224: the cat story, that's a nice use of the English language there. I like that, Chris.
I
Speaker 54: like that. I like that approach because
Speaker 54: What it showed was he's full of bull butter and
has
Speaker 213: been for a very long time.
Congratulations on
Speaker 213: the new addition. I'll be a first-time grandma in August. I can't wait. I got my Crisis King shirt and
Speaker 189: love it. Thanks, Candace,
for the
Speaker 189: introduction of the best podcast on the air. Oh, don't tell the principal that.
Don't tell
Speaker 189: her that.
Crisis King
Speaker 189: indeed.
Speaker 294: Hey, be careful
with that
Speaker 294: in August business,
because I
Speaker 294: kept telling everybody I'm going to become a grandparent in June.
Speaker 160: May late
Speaker 245: in May I became a grandparent another great episode congrats on becoming
Speaker 65: a granddad we will be celebrating our 25th anniversary next year I told my husband we will have to go away somewhere this time he agreed thanks yeah
we went
Speaker 65: away for the first time
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): and again we didn't go far because of the situation we were
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): in but it's nice living in the Nashville area the beautiful places around here
to go
uh i'm way
Speaker 456: late
Speaker 51: it's okay
had
Speaker 457: to finish
up
Speaker 65: the pot roast and green beans do laundry and feed new laying chicks popping
in before i
Speaker 65: hit the dinner dishes to say congrats and welcome to the world
Speaker 179: little
one uh janice you
Speaker 179: listen whenever you want you're a great listener um and great participant here so you just take
your
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): time where no one's going to
judge you the pot
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): roast sounds - It sounds
delicious.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Silver foxes are beautiful. Watching my husband go gray only makes him more irresistible than ever.
What if only the
Speaker 239 (lower-pitched voice): beard goes gray and the rest of it sort of maintains its color? Like I have some grays coming in the temple,
but the rest of it's
Speaker 182 (lower-pitched voice): still maintained its natural color. But this beard is out of control. I'm
not sure a
Speaker 93: gray beard is like what you call old people.
Speaker 189: Data centers, AI counterfeit, omnipresent, cancer, false tumors, false cell tumor destroys all that is natural and holy, building body for disembodied spirit.
Christ is
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): king indeed. I don't know
that I
Speaker 322 (lower-pitched voice): follow that entirely, but thank you.
Your
Speaker 458: majesty, king, baron, congrats
on
Speaker 95: your new title, modur afi.
You're speaking Icelandic. Okay.
What
Speaker 459: a beautiful language. God
bless
Speaker 460: baby Coleman and all the family in the grand jury. Missed you in the fantastic time we
had
Speaker 342: together. Yes, we do have great
time
Speaker 461: together. It's
Speaker 462: wonderful. For our friends
Speaker 463: south of the border.
Speaker 463: Congrats,
Speaker 314: Coleman. The episode
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): quickly made me recall M. McCoy's photos of the little gateway he and E. McCoy took with the Kirks shortly before C.K.'s death. Last
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): try to make it work, maybe?
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): Precious King indeed. That was my... I didn't want to even bring that up tonight. But I thunked it.
Forgot to say I
Speaker 303: received my introduction to logic book the other day. Kai?
you're
Speaker 303: about to be a brilliant thinker nothing's going to get past you
Speaker 464: not sure if i'm the only one but just noticed ek isn't wearing her wedding ring
in the
Speaker 464: still pic you showed from the glenn beck show that's correct that's
correct congrats granddad also
Speaker 51: thanks for your great work once again ek also has post from nine two for the
one with her
Speaker 51: mother that says what if childhood
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): could hold eternity 15 days i am 916 yeah Yeah.
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): something's
Speaker 465: happening something was happening
uh my
Speaker 11: ex-mother-in-law used to say if we knew grandkids were so much fun we'd have had them first i learned that when my first grandchild
was born
Speaker 11: amazing oh but
but but you
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): can't have the you can't have the grandkids doesn't
work that
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): way
Speaker 466: uh congrats
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): gbc may god shine bright over your growing family granddaddy looks good on you no old age jokes from uncleivan glad you're back you might have been missed christ is king indeed i
missed you tooivan i missed you
Speaker 468: too um i
thank you
Speaker 326: thank you
Speaker 468: i appreciate that i don't need any old jokes from unc
Speaker 326: Congratulations, granddad and family. Grandkids are the best. We have six.
Speaker 27: I'm a retired labor and delivery nurse. Fabulous career. Love those babies.
Christ is
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): king indeed. Yeah, God bless those women who have to listen to
mothers giving
Speaker 46: birth. I
Speaker 469: find it
very
Speaker 46: odd. The paper guy observed Sunday, but then cursed as much as he did. I've never heard an LDS member who participates in Sunday family
Speaker 294: day speak like that.
I don't
Speaker 294: know, but that's weird. Maybe he just wants a day off, and Sunday's his day. I
don't know. Baron,
Speaker 6: Christ is king indeed. Did you know that the vehicle that Thomas Matthew Crooks drove to the
rally
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): in Butler is still in possession of the government? I did not.
Wasn't it a Hyundai or something? Hyundai,
Speaker 470: like Sunday?
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): Congrats, Baron. I questioned why I wasn't as awesome as a mom
as I am
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): a grandma.
Now you get
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): it.
Two, it's a
Speaker 211: complete different love. Plus, you get to hand them back after spoiling them with gifts and sweets. I don't
do a lot of
Speaker 211: sweets. So
I got bad
Speaker 464: news for the grandbaby. She's
going to have to
Speaker 464: be spoiled with other stuff. I'll
give her
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): sweets. I'll have some Werther's. You know, you're going to have Werther's on hand. If
you're going to be
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): old, you got to carry Werther's around, right? Here's
to that creamy
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): caramel.
Or
Speaker 199 (lower-pitched voice): butterscotch, whatever. It's caramel, right?
Hey,
Speaker 30: granddad. I need some hard candy. If I'm going to be a granddad, doggone it. I need hard candy. I'm
going to have to invest in some bonbons. Hey,
Speaker 245: granddad. You are glowing, and I'm so happy you were able to
be off
Speaker 245: to spend precious time with the missus and also your daughter. Much love and God's blessings. Christ is king indeed. Thank you.
Speaker 51: Sarah. Wow. Congratulations to the whole Coleman family. Happy to have you back. It's wonderful that you and Mrs. Coleman
Speaker 51: We're able to get away and come home to a wonderful present. I'm
sure your
Speaker 179: family is so blessed.
Thank God
Speaker 179: bless you all. Christ is king indeed. You know what the best part was? It wasn't even me getting to hold the baby or Mrs. Coleman getting to hold the baby. It was wonderful seeing my daughter hold her own baby.
But
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): seeing the aunts and uncles, my other children, holding that baby.
Speaker 178: Oh, my gosh.
I took
Speaker 178: pictures. I took pictures of every one of them.
And it was
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): beautiful.
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): that that makes you glow right there
uh congrats
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): coleman family i wonder when charlie figured out the 10
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): million was missing from
tp usa
Speaker 156 (lower-pitched voice): to lf that led the doge initiative last straw of marriage
oh i don't
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): know i don't know i haven't
seen any of
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): that documented i've just seen that uh speculate uh
the red railing
Speaker 471 (lower-pitched voice): they were likely because the uu colors are red white black and UVU color is gray. That could be.
could be
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): grand status unlocked thank you i don't give a
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): dom i've been looking to level up you went more far max as some would say you went far far
Speaker 47: away over the new moon and back this weekend
finally a
Speaker 47: lunar trip i can actually believe happened
Speaker 159: congrats on the only recent landing that's real
yeah all
Speaker 159: that's
Speaker 472: true i'm a real morfar
a
Speaker 472: real Morfar,
Speaker 398: and it was real,
unlike
Speaker 253: the Artemis II fake mission. My
high IQs, my son
Speaker 245: started a Christian clothing line. Seventh Day Basics, please check it out. So proud of him, just a few products, but more coming. Thank
you,
Speaker 473: thank you, good luck to him. Spouse
is a
Speaker 473: priority, but your children are a covenant.
your
Speaker 474: spouse is a covenant too.
If it's
Speaker 433: done properly, the spouse is also a covenant. But I understand what you're saying, Katie. Thank
Speaker 245: you, Carrie. Just drive-by donations. Congrats to Morphar and Mormor and Mormor mother to the little girl. Well,
Speaker 370: thank you. I
forgot she's a
Speaker 475: Mormor.
I don't
Speaker 179: think you call a woman a more-more, though. Not
one that
Speaker 221: speaks English, because that sounds bad. Like, more, more. That
gets you in trouble. Congrats,
Speaker 65: missed. You found it odd that AK texted shot for sure when responding to Candace's inquiry about Charlie Kirk's condition on 9-10. Yeah,
I
Speaker 69: noticed that. That was
a little weird, but he's a
Speaker 69: weird guy.
Speaker 69: I laid to the party, but
Speaker 189: did you see diligent confirmed TR family took him to Washington County Sheriff's office on 9-11? Not only did I see it, I retweeted it. I retweeted it.
I think I did. Yeah,
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): I did. Diligent's done great work on that, by the way.
We'll talk about
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): that more this week.
Only do one show at a
Speaker 476: time.
Speaker 477: Edge. Oh, thanks for the edge. I missed it. Forget age. My hubby was older than you are
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): currently with our son. Everyone thought grandfather. Of course.
That
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): is also the reason he won't buy any theories. Yeah, yeah,
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): I get it. I was holding the baby one
Speaker 214: time, and one of the nurses walked in. He's like, and what is your relation? I'm
Speaker 478: like, I'm
the
Speaker 214: old guy.
Congratulations to
Speaker 245: you and your family. Best wishes. Thank you.
My gifted
Speaker 245: membership expired. Even though times are tough, I had to break down and buy my own.
Speaker 245: Thank you for all you do be in congrats on the grand baby crisis King and Jesus loves you too. Well, you're going to get value out of that. And thank you Holly for saying that. Cause I am going to do a member show this
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): week. I missed it last week, obviously because of the baby. But I try not to miss those each week. Thank you, Zach.
My profile
Speaker 173 (lower-pitched voice): pick is one of 11 grand babies.
Speaker 479: Congrats. That's beautiful. 11. It's beautiful. I'll say
Speaker 53: congrats. Granddad Baron. FYI, I call myself grandma
Speaker 237: to my first granddaughter. They are,
Choose
Speaker 237: your name. She named me Mama. I'm
going with
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): Granddad. I
don't care if she's 11
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): before she learns how to say it.
I'll be
Speaker 6: like, no, you call me what you want. Granddad. Granddad.
Speaker 65: Congrats, Big B, with all these super chats rolling in lately. When you and Mrs. Coleman disagree on something, do you ever hit her with the, you know, people pay me.
Speaker 219: No.
That would not go over
Speaker 219: well.
Speaker 219: No, I don't say that at all. I
might make sure
Speaker 235: she, I might like send her a timestamp of the show and be like, oh, I didn't mean to
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): send that timestamp. I meant something else, sorry. I might send that comment, but no, I'm not, no,
I did not
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): say that. Regarding the AI voice, Charlie was too smart to say appoint Erica
Speaker 245: rather than endorse or recommend for the board to decide.
Speaker 245: No way there's a video. P.S. Mrs. Coleman may need a hair tie on the battle bun cap.
Attached it
Speaker 350: in a hurry at the post office. It's held up. It's held up.
So we're good. No hair tie
Speaker 350: needed, Renee.
Speaker 480: And thank you for that. Very thoughtful.
Very, very
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): thoughtful. Back to this one. We decided a long time ago. There's no, what's mine is hers.
So.
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): there's no
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): division there. Did you see CK's parents wouldn't look at Erica at funeral and stand near her at coffin move? I lost my partner and squeezed hands in grief. Daily Fredo, 5-5, 7-20 minutes. I
did see
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): that. I haven't seen Daily Fredo's take on that, but I have seen that.
Speaker 481: Yeah, I've made a decision. I'm not going to talk about his parents if I can. I
mean,
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): it could change, but for right now, that's kind of my call.
Congratulations
Speaker 198 (lower-pitched voice): on the
Speaker 160: Morfar. Thank you, Candice,
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): for Morfar and Farfar equating us. Thank you. Yes, what a wonderful community we have that everyone instantly knows what we're talking about. I
have a
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): USA sock company. Love to make Barron socks for you. Where do I send them?
Speaker 222: XOXO Zach. Zach, I'll show you
this real quick. There's a
Speaker 246 (lower-pitched voice): P.O. box in here somewhere where
you can
Speaker 246 (lower-pitched voice): send stuff. The post office people love it.
They
Speaker 351: absolutely love it. They can't get enough
of the
Speaker 482: fact that
people
Speaker 349: send stuff. Yes, yes, they love it.
Oh, and
Speaker 349: fully natural, checking
Speaker 1: in.
Oh, the
Speaker 1: birth. Oh, okay. Edge, I thought you were giving us way too much information. I was
going to have to have a
Speaker 1: conversation with you off air.
But
Speaker 219: now that you said that,
that makes a lot of
Speaker 219: sense. Thank you. We
almost got
Speaker 219: really awkward up in here, Ed.
Speaker 27: No mercy
Speaker 324: for Hunter B. He talked about crimes most struggle with, but not the crimes that corrupt America. Yeah,
that was
Speaker 324: kind of my thought. But
I understand
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): Candace kind of letting him go where he wanted to go. He was a guest. And if you invite someone on your show, you don't,
you
Speaker 483: know, kind
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): of let them go where they want to go.
Speaker 183 (lower-pitched voice): Congrats on your sweet grand girl. I'm
Speaker 428: a single mom of 13 kids. Oh,
Speaker 484: gosh.
Dad
Speaker 428: passed 12 years ago.
Speaker 484: Wow. 13 kids.
That's
Speaker 485: amazing. Sorry to hear about your loss. I'm a grandmother of 49, a great-grandmother of four. Every
one of
Speaker 485: them is awesome. Life is crazy. Christ is king indeed.
What a
Speaker 238: wonderful life.
Speaker 238: wonderful life. Oh, beautiful. Thank you
for
Speaker 486: sharing that. Thank you, Elaine.
And
Speaker 486: thank you, Jerry. Sherry, Sherry.
The left of that paper was
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): Charlie. The right was Erica. Look at the honest contrast of who they are and the kids not in the below the pad means both important
Speaker 95: to both.
The kids seem
Speaker 95: to be on the left-hand side of that list, if you're
Speaker 179: right. What are some situations where you think it'd be a good thing a judge didn't let cameras in the courtroom or kept a very tight ship? I gave an opening statement on
that.
on
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): that doctor case in Cleveland where the media was just totally out of control? I mean, you can't... I don't think you can close the courtroom. You have
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): to let the court be public. People have
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): to be able to come in and to be able to report. But as
far as
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): recording it and letting people clip it out and, ah, see, I told you he's
Speaker 487: guilty. I think that, you know, I understand the defense's position.
a
Speaker 488: wonderful opening statement equals granddad story also grand baby pink replaced bean paste hoodie oh
thank
Speaker 487: you thank
you for all
Speaker 254: you're doing for the investigation keep going max christ is king indeed it's going back to bean paste next time i wear it though
uh congrats my mom
Speaker 179: recently passed and she loved all 17 of her grandkids your show in this community has helped me hang
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): on to christ
is
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): on my side and hearing you describe my mom's relationship with my kids. Oh, thank you.
Gosh, I love
Speaker 480: this community. I cannot tell you how much I love this community. Thank you for sharing that. Thoughts on Tulsi's exit. I'm of the belief the Kirks were
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): on track to divorce. Congratulations, granddad and the entire Coleman crew. Christ is king indeed. I'm going to take her to word that
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): she has a husband who's in a horrific situation with bone cancer. What a horrible, horrible disease.
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): and that
Speaker 489: she would rather be with him.
And I think
Speaker 11: it's beautiful.
First Super Chat
Speaker 11: live ever. I watched on Apple Podcast. You
watch it or
Speaker 11: just listen? I thought it was only audio. Congrats on grandbaby and anniversary,
praying
Speaker 490: for fast recovery and 25 more years
of
Speaker 491: marriage. Well,
25, I'll still be
Speaker 77: pretty young. Maybe we'll go for more than that.
I'll be in my early
Speaker 77: 70s, 25 more.
I'm hoping
Speaker 160: to get more out of life than that.
I'm going to have
Speaker 160: children listening
to describe
Speaker 160: the arrival of Bub makes me emotional.
Speaker 492: Congratulations, Mrs. C. Yeah.
It is.
Speaker 493: It was very emotional. I'm sorry to hear that. Thank you. I
had my first
Speaker 473: daughter at 22. She had her daughter at 22. That makes me a 44-year-old grandma. I feel
like we need
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): to get back to having kids in our 20s. Congrats.
Yeah, I'm all
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): for it.
The
Speaker 69: more the merrier. Charlie Crook's list was who he thought E.K. was versus who E.K. actually is, maybe? What
was her
Speaker 69: hand covering
at the
Speaker 69: bottom of the note? I don't know what the hand was covering. But
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): yeah, maybe
that's
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): what it was. I don't know.
Congratulations, Grandpa and Grandma
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): Coleman. My husband and I are blessed to have five children and ten grandchildren,
Speaker 237: hoping for at least four. That
means one of
Speaker 237: your five is not going to have another one.
Ha, ha, ha.
You must
Speaker 237: have that one picked
Speaker 57: out. First super chat. I hate to
tell you
Speaker 57: that the little blessing will decide what to call you and will adore you and you will adore whatever it is. Congratulations. You're a blessing from God. That
love is unexplainable. You guys
Speaker 57: say that,
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): but like.
I had
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): grandma, grandpa and granddad. Now, unfortunately, my other grandmother passed away before I was born.
But I guarantee
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): you, I
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): couldn't say grandma, grandpa or granddad.
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): before when I was little. But I probably said something and my parents were like, no, no, no, it's a granddad. Grandpa.
Grandma. Look,
Speaker 453 (lower-pitched voice): I'm not knocking other people. Do
Speaker 237: what you want. I'm just talking. Shawnee's back. Is it possible she found out about his appointment and what it was for but wasn't invited? Just said she was.
Speaker 494: It's also that she needed to make sure the appointment ever happened. Ooh, ooh.
I
Speaker 422: don't know, Shawnee.
Speaker 495: That's a really good thought. I had not even considered as much. I
just assumed she
Speaker 290: was being honest, but I don't know why I
would assume
Speaker 290: that about her. Happy
Speaker 460: anniversary and congrats on the family's new addition. If the grand jury
could find
Speaker 460: it in their hearts, there
Speaker 340: are a few
members of
Speaker 340: my family that use a few prayers right now. Christ is king indeed. Well, chop rock, guitars, and gear. Hey, Lord,
when they're praying
Speaker 340: for chop rock, guitars, and gear, they're praying for that guy.
You could
Speaker 340: remember that.
Speaker 154: Congrats. I had all five. My babies naturally and no audience.
Although when I
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): had my first
at barely
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): 18, my dad held my hand the whole time. Such a special time for your family. I cannot wait to
be a
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): grandmother. Yeah,
I didn't want
Speaker 496: to get too personal, but I was a hand holder. And
Speaker 277: yeah,
I was definitely handled. But thank you,
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): Rachel, for sharing that.
and
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): I'll tell you it made my heart swell to hear her call out for me honestly congrats grandma and granddad I love being a nana also
Speaker 231: got two whole please mugs in the mail for my hubby love them oh
I just took my
Speaker 231: whole please mug back in the kitchen but just imagine I'm
holding it coming
Speaker 231: in way behind the night because family came to
visit unacceptable
Speaker 497: did you tell them it was showtime I
don't
Speaker 231: know how many
Speaker 235: sent this to you but I was one of
them
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): baby congrats thank you more than one
uh new no
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): new chamber in heart trust me b you don't want any
Speaker 336 (lower-pitched voice): problems uh p.s still hating physical therapy but i'm going so don't shake finger at me congrats to
grandpa
Speaker 498: keep going keep going you don't have
to love it just do
Speaker 498: it just do
Speaker 222: it like like thank you uh for your new grandbaby congratulations thank you that's
Speaker 39: very kind of you cindy
As the story goes, I named
Speaker 39: my penka.
Because
Speaker 39: I couldn't say grandpa. He was Panker forever.
He was
Speaker 39: awesome. Congrats, Coleman family. I'm not knocking other people
for doing
Speaker 39: it. I'm just going to keep telling
Speaker 213: her. Granddad.
Speaker 499: Congrats,
Papa Baron. And
Speaker 213: my first grandchild at 39, second at 41. I,
Speaker 179: too, am a 46-year-old grandfather. Definitely a different feeling when your own child is having a child. It sure is. Thank you for sharing that.
My mom
Speaker 179: and dad had 12 kids and
Speaker 37: had 28 grandkids. 10 great-grands so far. Congrats on the new baby girl.
Will she be
Speaker 477: granddad's girl? Of course. Of course. King Quack. That reminds me of Quack Quack Quack. Grandpappy Baron.
Speaker 350: God is so good and life is so sweet. New life is so sweet. May God bless and protect you and your growing family. Thank you. Holy mackerel. We're over three and a half hours.
uh
Speaker 500: estrangement is an epidemic oh no 27 of families more than one in four that's crazy
driven by
Speaker 429 (lower-pitched voice): social media algorithms should ask who runs algorithms and how they benefit from destroying
families
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): oh christ is king indeed um i
had no idea that was happening no idea that was
Speaker 245: happening i got
a new
Speaker 237: chair guys and i gotta say this is amazing
That's why I
Speaker 237: didn't know it had been three and a half hours. I'm not uncomfortable. My
old chair is
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): right here just in case
I had to
Speaker 225 (lower-pitched voice): switch back mid-show. I wasn't sure. CNE's
last public
Speaker 361: appearance reminds me of when Scarlett O'Hara wore
her mother's
Speaker 497: draperies to score money from Rhett.
Charlie seemed
Speaker 497: visibly annoyed when
she pushed
Speaker 497: back on having kids after 30.
Speaker 501: Yeah, she was over 30 when she had both her kids, right? Pretty
sure I'm right on that. Thank
Speaker 502: you. CK figured out EK was his handler.
So glad you're
Speaker 502: back. Congrats on the new baby. Crisis King indeed. I don't
Speaker 157: know. Maybe. Just got caught up and not sure if anyone said this, but I'm in landscaping. An excavation of 9 and 12 inches is standard for paver.
Speaker 157: Yes, but is excavating
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): a crime scene standard? That's the operative question here.
Please
Speaker 504: pray for our family. We lost our mother yesterday. Oh, gosh.
How much we owe her. She
Speaker 450 (lower-pitched voice): was the rock
of our
Speaker 450 (lower-pitched voice): military family. Ugh.
I'll pray for
Speaker 450 (lower-pitched voice): you. I'm sorry to hear that.
Gosh, I'm sorry to
Speaker 505: hear that.
I would like to
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): correct my previous super chat. Granddad. Oops. A lot of families became estranged over the jab.
Speaker 179: Prayers for those who are still failing, falling for the deceptive plot. Christ is king, indeed. You
got a
Speaker 179: strange over
Speaker 137: the jab?
Don't do that. Congrats on
Speaker 137: the bundle of joy. You can see the hearing aids. You
Speaker 270: can't see the hearing aids at all.
Speaker 506: Christ is
Speaker 270: king. Indeed, yes, you can. It was the first thing I noticed when I took the picture or
when I
Speaker 270: looked at the picture. Okay, Grandpa, either put on the
Speaker 507: glasses or increase the font size.
i would but the
Speaker 76: glasses are in my travel bag back here behind me
i
Speaker 51: have to dig through it and find
them uh yes
Speaker 51: brother b glad you're back behind the wheels of steel thank you thank you congratulations
Speaker 189: granddad so happy for you we missed you but family is life take time pick off all the time you need to spend time with your new blessings your grand jury will always
Speaker 137: be here christ is king indeed thank
you
Speaker 137: Congrats to you and Mrs. C on the grandbaby. I'm celebrating a milestone birthday today. The big 5-0.
Thank you for all
Speaker 372 (lower-pitched voice): you do. Putting a great show every time. Love this community. Crisis King indeed. Ramona, 50 is an amazing accomplishment. You'll
Speaker 186: start getting mail now from AARP. That's the best reason to turn 50 I can think of. Thank you. Usually,
Speaker 184: yes. But if it was last-minute job, the supply yards probably weren't open on Sunday
and no
Speaker 184: other place to go but those. Oh, oh, oh.
Be
Speaker 375: careful. Watch Savvy Savvy's Live today. You are in jeopardy. All commentators are being subpoenaed.
By
Speaker 508: whom? I'll
have to watch
Speaker 508: that. Let me open that up right now.
Savvy Savvy. I'm not being subpoenaed. In my last message, I
Speaker 65: meant the last thing Charlie would want
Speaker 184: us to have Erica in charge of turning point. That
may also
Speaker 184: explain the divorce angle legal appointment.
yeah congrats
Speaker 509: Coleman fam I've seen a video that Charlie read the list for an interview on the differences from the right wing versus
left wing views I don't know if I
Speaker 509: can
Speaker 86: remember who
it was with
Speaker 86: Price is King indeed some people are saying he referenced that list on Megyn Kelly so I'll check that out
I'm a great grandma
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): and my parents are enjoying being double G's lots
of love to you and your
Speaker 237: family great great grandparents not too many of those out there
we could
Speaker 237: all be so lucky. I raised my younger sister who moved in with me when she was 14. She's now
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): 26. That's two beautiful children. The
love I
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): have for them takes my breath away. So blessed to have them all in my life. That's a beautiful story, Terry. First. Thank you. Thank you for. For
Speaker 510: that. Thank
you for sharing
Speaker 510: that. Um,
Hold
Speaker 510: on, I'm looking for something.
But
Speaker 511: yeah, thank you for sharing that.
The list in Charlie's
Speaker 73 (lower-pitched voice): office was points he brought up on last interview with Laura Ingram. Yep, that's what I'm hearing. Congrats on the new
Speaker 245: grandchild. Well, great-grandchildren. Count towards the 40 grandchildren to man. Christ is king indeed. No, I need
200 of
Speaker 324: those.
Like
Speaker 324: we're starting a clan.
Not with
Speaker 324: a K, with a C. We're starting a clan. We're starting
Speaker 294: a tribe.
The tribe of
Speaker 294: Baron. I
Speaker 512: don't
recommend
Speaker 126: it. We're not really. That was a joke.
Christ is
Speaker 126: king indeed. Thank you.
You are
Speaker 324: going to be the best Morphar that little girl could ever ask for. So glad you're back. Missed
you a
Speaker 324: lot. Well,
I missed you,
Speaker 324: Maude.
We have
Speaker 324: two-month-old niece, and my husband hands
Speaker 294: her to anyone else when she starts crying.
Saying, okay, the fun
Speaker 233: part's over. Congrats on the grandbaby. Christ is king indeed. I had a little of that thought myself when I was changing the diaper. I was like, hey, wait a minute. This
isn't my
Speaker 233: job anymore.
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): I kid, happy to do it, happy to do it.
Maybe
Speaker 187: it
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): says 106, January 6th.
Speaker 187: So she strategically found an old one to
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): miraculously find life.
I don't think
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): it says that. It looks like it says 606 something. Might
be like a
Speaker 262 (lower-pitched voice): pen number. Maybe
Speaker 513: that's
how
Speaker 349: you get into his bank account.
Did you just
Speaker 35: say while you were on vacay, you were looking at the EK nose? Always on the case. That is why we love you, B. Congrats on the first of 40 grandkids. I actually was.
I had a whole
Speaker 495: bunch of pictures that I texted myself. Different noses.
Yeah.
uh but
Speaker 237: bear on granddad adding to your purpose in life has to feel amazing glad you're back and had a much
Speaker 294: deserved break with your family baby girl is perfect congratulations b she's perfect indeed
letter for the
Speaker 294: daughter but not one for the son yeah that poor
Speaker 237: son gets so left i'm not sure what's going on with
the son it's like he
Speaker 237: never references like she never references the
son and he did
Speaker 237: have that picture
up
Speaker 233: with the son
Uh,
Speaker 213: yes, it's happening now that kids are cutting off their parents. I haven't seen my son and three grandchildren in five years. Two who were born during the five
Speaker 98: years. So never met prayers needed to crisis can you need for what? What is that? What is happening? Why is this happening? I've never heard of this. Is there like a, a reason I've learned
so much
Speaker 296: about plants this last week, but I'm good now. Back to my back to regularly scheduled high IQing.
You, you took the time off to study
Speaker 218: about your plants.
I'm
Speaker 218: okay with that. That's time well spent.
Read a
Speaker 218: book. Read up on plants.
So
Speaker 179: happy you and your growing family, granddad. Enjoy it. Granddadding is the best. Agreed. Agreed. So far. Only on day two, but so far I agree with you. Just started watching
Speaker 211: this and the paver guy said that he listened to the voicemail and then said he answered the call. That was the second to last clip. Just
makes me
Speaker 211: think about his story. Or
maybe
Speaker 233: he texted back and said, hey, I'm free now. Call me. And they call. I don't know. Yeah, given the benefit of the day.
Might
Speaker 233: be a stretch, but Charlie not talking about his son makes me
Speaker 514: think the possibility when the dad found out couldn't accept it. Separation.
I mean, I don't want
Speaker 515: to go
Speaker 516: there. I
don't
Speaker 515: know. I mean, you're free to go there, but I
don't want
Speaker 515: to go there.
Speaker 63: Granddad Baron is my favorite. Tonight felt like a throwback episode. Oh, oh, you like Granddad Baron?
Speaker 159: congrats granddad we missed you glad you're back may god bless your family crisis king indeed thank you thank you dr sebastian gorka salem media talent was advocating for
Speaker 294: replacing joe kent i'm concerned he might try for tulsi's job now well
Speaker 517: that'd
be a
Speaker 222: disaster god bless you and yours grandpa thank you thank you happy to uh uh
hey good good
Speaker 222: good gramps congratulations y'all are so blessed sadly my dad never got to meet my daughter and vice versa as he passed several years Friar.
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): um i told you i was in that same boat my uh grandmother
Speaker 66 (lower-pitched voice): uh passed away before i was born and um i've heard so many wonderful stories about her that i feel like i've missed that part of my life everybody seemed to adore her and uh sorry i never got to meet her
kindly
Speaker 11: asked for a prayer tray you became a new grandpa this weekend well
i met my
Speaker 11: biological father for
the
Speaker 63: first time ever 38 and introduced him to his granddaughter
prayers for
Speaker 16: the new granddad's christ is king indeed congrats what a beautiful story cory um
i'll pray
Speaker 16: for you certainly what a beautiful
Speaker 518: story
thinking about
Speaker 518: the dates did he need
to go
Speaker 518: before signing
Speaker 452: on the 15th what
was she
Speaker 449: going to lose well that's the question
also i can
Speaker 452: relate to the comment regarding kids not communicating with parents my now 31 year old daughter is like that for no apparent reason. What is happening? This
Speaker 98: is weird.
A
Speaker 260: person commenting about shower could be going
Speaker 98: through depression. I've
been
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): there. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I didn't even consider that. I'm sorry if that's the case. I didn't mean to make light of it. I
would never
Speaker 362 (lower-pitched voice): make light of that.
Speaker 519: Congrats. Hard to believe that seven months ago I didn't even know you existed, and I missed you every day that you were gone. Welcome back.
Speaker 520: Thanks for your amazing work. Christ is king indeed. I missed you every day I was gone.
Speaker 521: K-D-V-N-D-E. Dearly. Dearly.
i'm glad
Speaker 233: you're here
a day
Speaker 233: or so after jfk a passerby found a portion of
the skull on the
Speaker 522: side of the road they had to call police uh i found some skull really
huh welcome back congrats
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): hard to believe so oh
i love
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): your work too christ is king indeed i don't know if you meant
this in too but you did you did
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): uh i wanted my in-laws to be mama and papa they are knee-yaw and poop-ah.
Ten
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): years now.
Speaker 99: Well, look, I'm all for letting the kids have a say in it, but I will not be Pupaw.
I will not be. I'm no one's Pupaw. You cannot call
Speaker 99: me Pupaw.
No
Speaker 477: one can.
My worst
Speaker 477: enemy, I would not wish Pupaw. I'm kidding. Pupaw sounds beautiful.
Sounds great. Estrangement from
Speaker 460: parents became a big thing during...
Speaker 460: C-19, when children demanded
Speaker 344: their parents take the jab or be cut off from the grams. Epidemic.
There are social media groups
Speaker 344: on this topic. Is that what caused it?
What a weird
Speaker 524: thing. That's over. Come back.
Come back home. Welcome
Speaker 210: back. We need more digging on French infrastructure mogul link to greatest ally. Oh, yeah. French aided with them in the Damona nuke project, and Corsican
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): snipers took out JFK.
first I've
Speaker 525: heard of the Corsicans from
the
Speaker 180 (lower-pitched voice): blessing may his favor be upon you and a thousand generations and your family and your children and their children and their
children.
Speaker 233: Yeah. I'll allow it. Thank you.
We could use the
Speaker 233: blessings. Congrats on anniversary, new
Speaker 294: bundle of joy and 300,000 subs. We missed you. Not as much as I missed you. I'll pack a Renee. You've been around a long time.
I don't think
Speaker 254: estrangement's an epidemic. Me and sis don't speak to our mom for abuse, verbal, physical. Maybe society makes it more acceptable for children to choose
to
Speaker 222: break toxic cycles instead of labeling this as an epidemic. Oh, I
guess there's
Speaker 222: two sides to every story, isn't there? Dad was Bupa, then turned to Papa. It is possible to get kiddos to change what they call you. Yeah.
Speaker 369: Granddad. No, granddad.
oh so
Speaker 222: funny story real quick i'll tell uh we're going on four hours but i'll tell the story so my daughter the
new
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): mom uh we did a little sign language she was a kid you know food water the whole nine
years and i
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): was trying to get her to call me dad dadda
Speaker 214: because she would call me mama because she was with her mom all day then
i would
Speaker 214: come home from work and she just thought parent meant mama i guess she's used mama
and i
Speaker 214: say no dadda
And so she
Speaker 214: starts
Speaker 527: doing this and going, dad, dad. I'm like, no, no, no, no, no. Not you, me, me, dad, dad. Yeah, gosh,
that
Speaker 528: seems like a few years ago. Holy mackerel, that was 19 years ago.
It was fast,
Speaker 287 (lower-pitched voice): guys. I know it's cliche, but it's true.
It goes
Speaker 287 (lower-pitched voice): fast.
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): Congrats, Granddad Baron. Best ever.
Speaker 243 (lower-pitched voice): Having my one and only son at 44 years old. Now,
Speaker 65: Graham's at 65 two years ago. Now, two grandkids. I'm excited for Nashville NASCAR next weekend with my pit pass. My
Speaker 186: camera's nephew is Gas Man, number 23.
That's the car owned
Speaker 529: by Michael Jordan, isn't it?
Who drives that? Was that... Is that Bubba Wallace? Ah,
Speaker 530: somebody.
Speaker 175 (lower-pitched voice): Um, well, congrats
Speaker 471 (lower-pitched voice): on that. That'll be fun. You'll have a good time.
Uh, my B everyone
Speaker 471 (lower-pitched voice): heard you say Arizona is beautiful.
Speaker 321: Oh, I got caught. It's
a beautiful kitty
Speaker 321: litter. It is beautiful. I've been to Arizona. Um,
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): my wife and I spent some time on the Navajo nation reservation and it's beautiful. It truly is. Uh, we climbed a little
rock
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): called nose rock
Mesa outside
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): of pinion in
burnt Corn
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): Valley.
and we
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): got up to the top, and it's a couple
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): thousand feet above the
rest of
Speaker 176 (lower-pitched voice): the terrain, and it's beautiful. The sea is just forever because it's flat,
and there's no
Speaker 64 (lower-pitched voice): trees. I kid. Well, I don't kid about that, but it's true. Didn't the Kirks have a visit from a
Speaker 166 (lower-pitched voice): priest the night before the
Speaker 52: big event, marriage counseling? Well, that's the rumor.
That's the
Speaker 52: rumor.
Speaker 52: Cindy, checking in. Hadn't heard from you in a while. Cindy Yates, congratulations. Grandkids are a blessing. We missed you. Glad
Speaker 50: you're back. I missed you. Glad you're back. Bye, baby girl, something.
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): Let her know the YouTube fam always keeps y'all in our prayers. I
will let
Speaker 79 (lower-pitched voice): the whole family know that.
And
Speaker 468: thank you. Genuinely, thank you. And
we'll
Speaker 532: return the favor. We'll pray for you tonight, Cindy.
Thank you. Uncle
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): B, or?
I
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): guess it's Grandpa Uncle B now.
Thank
Speaker 533: you, Frank.
Happy for
Speaker 308 (lower-pitched voice): you, the fan. Missed you and glad
Speaker 167: to have you back. Baby Coleman isn't aware she already has an entire fan base and isn't even a week old. She ain't even two days old?
Speaker 534: Is she not three days old?
Yeah, she's not even
Speaker 534: two days old.
She'll turn two
Speaker 534: days here in a few hours.
And she's perfect. She
Speaker 535: really is. Oh, gosh.
she
Speaker 266: really is like, I'm telling you, I look at people's babies and I'm like, look
like a space
Speaker 536: alien. And then I look at that one. I'm like, wow,
y'all
Speaker 416: missing out.
I have a Facebook group
Speaker 444: with 2000 moms estranged. 27% of moms aren't toxic, abusive, narcissistic, but those
are the
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): accusations pushed in social media. I have lots to say, very painful, very damaging. Gosh,
This is one
Speaker 330 (lower-pitched voice): of the worst
Speaker 537: things I've ever heard. KTV and DE.
Congrats,
Speaker 82: granddad. The first grand wraps their roots deep around your
Speaker 179: heart. It's a precious relationship. Very excited for you and grandma from
this grandma
Speaker 179: of 10, soon to be 11 in July. Deep-rooted circle of love.
We were right
Speaker 538: about the 10.
We
Speaker 538: said that when we were trying to figure out what your name meant. Remember the University of Tennessee grandma named Char with 10 grandbabies?
Speaker 178: Didn't we guess all that? Or is it Utah or University of Texas?
We had
Speaker 178: this whole conversation.
Thank you. Thank you. Epidemic
Speaker 365: started under C-19, excelled by social media, expanded during election. I can't go to Thanksgiving with
Speaker 540: someone who voted against my rights.
well i wouldn't go to
Speaker 541: thank you with them either anymore
i
Speaker 542: can't i can't i would i would i would uh thank you
Speaker 179: renee uh satan finds new
ways to rip
Speaker 179: families apart a lot of kids are super liberal and reject their more conservative parents it's
really sad
Speaker 179: christ is king indeed this
said that's
Speaker 179: why i say don't
ever let
Speaker 179: politics come between you and friends and family just just talk about something else
My papa was
Speaker 179: a cantankerous and hypocritical Cuban,
Speaker 178: but he was still my favorite person. She will love you unconditionally, even if you are saucy. Me? Saucy? Christ is king indeed. I don't
Speaker 16: think
Speaker 63: so. Congrats, granddad and Mrs. C. A week of blessings
for your
Speaker 63: fam. The paver guy needs a trustworthy security team and defense needs to subpoena. Stat.
Speaker 231: Agreed. On both.
I'm
Speaker 231: the person commenting about the shower, and I'm lazy, not depressed.
Speaker 543: Good, because
I was feeling
Speaker 231: bad for a second
Speaker 534: there. But thank you for the concern for the community. Ashley, tighten up.
Hygiene's
Speaker 314: important. Now, granted, people in the old days used to go six months without a shower.
But it's not
Speaker 314: the old days.
Speaker 77: The whole world smelled like poop back
Speaker 314: then. So
a
Speaker 77: stinky person didn't really add much to the equation.
these
Speaker 77: days it
Speaker 86: smells pretty nice and a stinky person sticks out like a sore thumb. So Ashley, you need your tight number,
tighten up, get in the
Speaker 65: shower and you got plenty of time now because the show has ended
guys. I've
Speaker 65: appreciated it. This has been an
Speaker 35: amazing, amazing time. This is
what I
Speaker 35: missed. I'm telling you, I missed this the whole time.
And thank
Speaker 35: you for your concerns
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): and your congratulations and your prayers and your well wishes and all that. Um,
This is an
Speaker 28 (lower-pitched voice): amazing community. I truly,
Speaker 82: like, I've never missed being out of work. Like, if I took a week off of work, I never missed it.
But I missed it
Speaker 67 (lower-pitched voice): this week. Like, I genuinely missed it. So thank you. Thank you. This has been an amazing, amazing day to cap off a truly amazing week. So thank you.
Speaker 35: Thank you. Thank you. Hit the like button. You can hit the subscribe button. And if you're not getting the notifications, you can click.
The
Speaker 35: notifications, you can do like notify this or notify all. You can click notify all and see if that helps. I was listening
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): to, I
think it
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): was Trigger Smart that
was telling
Speaker 162 (lower-pitched voice): me that little
Speaker 113 (lower-pitched voice): secret. When people say they don't get the notifications, tell them to click notifications all. So if you do want the notifications and you click notifications, make sure you got the all selected and that should help. But
Speaker 544: don't forget,
Speaker 545: don't.
Jesus loves
Speaker 545: you.
He
Speaker 368: does so
Speaker 546: much. And
when you
Speaker 368: look at that little bundle of joy, you realize how much Jesus loves us all.
So thank you so much. Thank
Speaker 35: you so, so much. I'm about to go back
to
Speaker 50: granddad duties. So wish me luck.
Wish me
Speaker 50: luck. I got to do dad duties first and then back to granddad duties. So wish me
Speaker 32: luck. Wish me luck. And I'll be back with you guys tomorrow night.
Have a wonderful evening and
Speaker 32: we will check in soon. Bye guys.
Thank you.